<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0118"/><productType value="0102"/><productId value="2056"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-15070007</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The TKB Z-Wave dual wall switch is switching attached loads and is controlled either by the local switching paddle or remotely via the Z-Wave wireless protocolIt is included and controlled in a Z-Wave network by a remote control, a wireless control centre or any other kind of Z-Wave controller including a PC-software.Beside the local switch the unit can control other Z-Wave units remotely in up to three additional Z-Wave groups, which are associated with this device. Tipping one time or two times the switching paddle performs the control. The left paddle controls the local load while the right paddle remotely controls Z-Wave associated devices only. The association of further Z-Wave devices needs to be done by a Z-Wave controller. The unit is powered by 230V power and needs a pattress box with 230 V power wires for installation. The unit is shipped completely with electronics, switching paddle and mounting frame in white style. It is designed for use within a 3-wire system, which means that a neutral wire is needed for operations.</lang></description><productName>TKB Switch TZ56D</productName><brandName>TKB Home</brandName><productCode>TZ56D</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0086" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC08-15070007"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
