<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="013C"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0012"/><libType value="Enhanced 232 Slave"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-14110001</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en"> This in-wall dual relay switch module is a transceiver which is a Z-Wave Plus enabled device and is fully compatible with any Z-Wave enabled network.Mini size design let the module can easily hide itself into the wall box and that will be good for the house decoration. There are many kind of application by using the module to switch AC power On and Off, one main application is the light control. The new smart relay calibration technology can reduce the inrush current caused by the load and let the module work perfectly with many kind of light like incandescent, fluorescent and LED light.This in-wall switch module is able to detect Instant power wattage and overload current (7.5A) of connected light or appliances. When detecting overload state, the Module will be disabled and its On/Off button will be lockout of which LED will flash quickly. However, disconnect and re-connect the Module will reset its overload condition to normal status. </lang></description><productName>In Wall Dual relay(1 way) switch module</productName><brandName>Philio</brandName><productCode>PAN04-1A</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">For group 1, the Switch will report (1) ON/OFF status of Relay1 and Relay2 (2) InstantPowerConsumption(Watt)ofRelay1andRelay2(3)Accumulated Power Consumption (KWh) of Relay1 and Relay2 to Group1 node.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Forgroup2,theSwitchwillreport(1)ON/OFFstatusofRelay1(2)Instant PowerConsumption(Watt)ofRelay1(3)AccumulatedPowerConsumption (KWh) of Relay1 to Group2 node. </lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Forgroup3,theSwitchwillreport(1)ON/OFFstatusofRelay2(2)Instant PowerConsumption(Watt)ofRelay2(3)AccumulatedPowerConsumption (KWh) of Relay2 to Group3 node.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="720" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Watt Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en"> If the setting is configured for 1hour (set value =720), the PAN04 will report its instant power consumption every 1 hour to the node of correspond Group. The maximumintervaltoreportitsinstantpowerconsumptionis45hours (5s*32767/3600=45hr). </lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Each value is a 5 second period.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">ExistenceofEndpoint3</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multi-Channel Command is a good way to control relay1 and relay2 of PAN04 individually. The endpoint3 of PAN04 is related to both relay1 and relay2. In some condition it becomes redundant in Multi-Channel Command Class. When the Existence of Endpoint3 is set as 2, the endpoint3 will be disabled. The default value is 1. Endpoint1 and Endpoint2 are fixed, only Endpoint3 is dynamic. </lang></description><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">No Endpoint 3</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Endpoint 3 exists</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="6" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">KWH Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en"> If the setting is configured for 1hour (set value =6), the PAN04 will report its Accumulated Power Consumption (KW/h) every 1 hour to the node of correspond Group. The maximum interval to report its Accumulated Power Consumption (KW/h) is 227.55 days (10min*32767/1440=227.55 days).</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Each value is one 10 minute period.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="3" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Selected Relay </lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If Controller not using Multi_Channel command class to access the relay of PAN04,youmayconfiguretheselectvaluetoreacttheBasicCommand ClassBinary Switch Command Class or Meter Command Class V3.</lang></description><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Relay2 can be controlled and will report</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Relay1 and Relay2 can be controlled and report.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Relay1 can be controlled and will report.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Edge orPulsemode orEdge-Toggl e mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Edge mode: this mode is suitable for the bi stable wall switch that has indicator pointon the switch, and the same position correspond to same state of relay1 and relay2. if the PAN04 relay change the state because of receiving Z-Wave RF command, it may need two times of change (switch on to off or switch off to on) to let relay back to the correspond state.Pulse mode: this mode is suitable for the toggle type wall switch to swap the state of Relay1 or Relay2. Edge-Toggle mode: this mode is suitable for the normal bi-stable switch, every time when change the state of the wall switch will also swap the state of Relay1 or Relay2. </lang></description><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Pulse mode</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Edge-Toggle mode </lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Edge mode</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="2" default="750" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of current for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the current of load over the preset threshold value, if the setting value is 750, when the load current of Relay1 or Relay2 over this value, PAN04 will send current meter report to the node of correspond Group, the Range of the setting value is from 10 to 750, and the default value is 750.</lang></description><value from="10" to="750"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Each value is 0.01A, e.g. 750*0.01A = 7.5A</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="2" default="10000" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of KWh for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the KWh of load over the preset threshold value, If the setting value is 10000, when the Accumulated Power Consumption of Relay1 or Relay2 over this value, PAN04 will send KWh Meter Report command to the node of correspond Group, minimum value is 1KWh and default value is 10000 kWh. </lang></description><value from="1" to="10000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">KWh Load Caution Meter Report threshold value</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Restore switch state mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever the AC power return from lost, PAN04 will restore the switch state which could be SWITCH OFFLAST SWITCH STATESWITCH ON. The default setting is LAST SWITCH STATE.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Last switch state</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Switch on</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Switch off</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto off timer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever PAN11 switches to on, the auto off timer begin to count down. After the timer decrease to zero, it will switch off automatically. However if Auto off timer is set as 0, the auto off function will be disabled. The default setting is 0.</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Each value is the number of seconds for the auto off timer.</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable auto off function</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">RF off command mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever a switch off command, BASIC_SET BINARY_SWITCH_SET SWITCH_ALL_OFF, is received, it could be interpreted as 4 kinds of commands. 1. Switch OffIt switches to OFF state. The default setting is Switch Off. 2. IgnoreThe switch off command will be ignored. 3. Switch ToggleIt switches to the inverse of current state. 4. Switch OnIt switches to ON state. </lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Ignore</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Switch toggle</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Switch on</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Switch off</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-14110001"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
