<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="014F"/><productType value="4C42"/><productId value="3133"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15080025</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Smart Retrofit Lightinh Kit with Z-Wave radio.- Control lights remotely and save energy- Compatible with smart home systems supporting Z-Wave- 65 Watt equivalent light (650 lumens)- Consumes only 8.5 watts of power- 2700K Soft White with frosted glass- Instant ON and fully dimmable- Functions as a Z-Wave signal repeater- Very simple to include in your network- Z-Wave Plus certified </lang></description><productName>Smart Retrofit Lighting Kit</productName><brandName>GoControl</brandName><productCode>LB65R6Z-1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LB65R6Z-1 supports Group 1 with up to ve devices for lifeline communication. Group 1 must be assigned the Node ID of the controller to which unsolicited notications will be sent. The Z-Wave controller should set this association automatically after inclusion. Lifeline association only supports the manual reset event. Please refer to the instructions manual of your remote controller or gateway for detail procedures on how these function can be set.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Dim level when the light bulb is turned On</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">You may select the Dim level whenever the light is turned back ON to be either full brightness (100% dim level) or be the same as the last dim setting when the light was previously ON.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The brightness level will maintain same dim level as the last setting when the dt Smart Bulb is turned ON again.</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The brightness level will be resume to full brightness when the dt Smart Bulb is turned ON every time.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="3" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Dimming/Brightening Step Timing</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">You may change the dimming speed quicker or slower by changing Parameter 10's value.</lang></description><value from="1" to="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">When the value is low, the step timing is quick. When the value is high, the step timing is slow.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Dimming/Brightening Step Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">You may change the dimming step level when you adjust the brightness by your controller/gateway.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">A low value provides gradual dimming and brightening, a high values makes it change rapidly.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-15080025"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
