<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="020E"/><productType value="5343"/><productId value="3132"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15100009</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Smart Switch Cover with Z-Wave radio.Built-in Z-Wave radio - can control Z-Wave Light Bulb and switches/dimmers remotely and wirelesslyPlug and play, simple setup. Fits over an existing wall switch.Manually turn on, off, dim your lights while keeping the smart light bulb always online in your home networkWorks with different types and brands of Z-Wave LED Light control devicesPowered by Z-Wave 500 Series module insideManual reset capabilityPowered by 2 pieces of standard CR2032 Lithium Coin Cell with long battery life</lang></description><productName>Z-Wave Smart Switch Cover</productName><brandName>GoControl</brandName><productCode>WA00Z-1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">WA00Z-1 supports Group 1 for lifeline communication. Group 1 must be assigned the Node ID of the controller to which unsolicited notications will be sent. The Z-Wave controller should set this association automatically after inclusion. Lifeline association only supports the manual reset event. Please refer to the instructions manual of your remote controller or gateway for detail procedures on how these function can be set.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">WA00Z-1 supports Group 2 with up to five devices as assciation group. Press and Release the top/bottom button, the devices in Group 2 will be turned ON/OFF.Press and hold the top/bottom button, the devices in Group 2 will be dim up/down. </lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">WA00Z-1 supports Group 3 with up to five devices as assciation group. Press and Release the top/bottom button twice (double click), the devices in Group 3 will be turned ON/OFF.Press the top/bottom button twice while holding down the top/bottom button in second press, the devices in Group 3 will be dim up/down. </lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Activation of Central Scene</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Valid Values can be set from 0 to 99.Each Valid Value can turn on two scenes. If the Valid Value is set to N, top button is assigned to control 2N+1 scene, and bottom button is assigned to control 2N+2 scene.For example, if the value is set as 4, Scene #7 will be activated when top button is pressed, Scene #8 will be activated when bottom button is pressed.</lang></description><value from="0" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ZSC control scene through central scene command class</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Control mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">User can set the WA00Z-1 to control other devices or they issue various scene activation commands to a central controller. When Value = 0, WA00Z-1 can activate the Scene which is pre-set by Gateway, and then control the associated Smart Bulbs in either Group 2 or Group 3. When Value = 1, WA00Z-1 can only activate the Scene which is pre-set by Gateway.When Value = 2, WA00Z-1 can only control Smart Bulbs in Association Group 2 and Group 3.</lang></description><value from="0" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Issue varies scene activation commands to a central controller</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Reverse Button</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">User can set the value to be 1, the function of top/bottom button will be reversed.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reverse Button</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-15100009"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
