<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0176"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0002"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15125004</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Personalise your experience and set up your very own smart home. With this gateway at the centre and adding other devices, your home will be smarter than ever before. This Z-Wave gateway with built-in 433 MHz transmitter combines the best of two worlds. Z-Wave provides high reliability, long range and two-way communication while 433 MHz provides broad compatibility.All configuration for the gateway is made in our cloud service, Telldus Live!. Schedules can be made at fixed times or depending on the sunrise and sunset. Event enabled control from incoming signals or sensors allows you to automate your home for real. The additional service Telldus Live! Pro gives you additional features, such as the ability to receive an e-mail or SMS when things happen in your system, such as data from a thermo or motion sensor. Schedules and Events runs locally on TellStick ZNet Lite even if internet is not available. The smartphone app Telldus Live! Mobile makes it possible to use your mobile phone as a remote control to the devices in your home, wherever you are in the world.</lang></description><productName>TellStick ZNet Lite</productName><brandName>Telldus</brandName><productCode>TZNetLite</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-15125004"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
