<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0232"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15110014</certNumber><rfFrequency>South Korea</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Smart Brain is an intelligent M2M/IoT gateway (Hub) for smart life and convenient life.The Smart Brain supports interconnection to a lot of devices with WiFi, Bluetooth, Z-wave, or infrared communication interface. Equipped with oneM2M platform, OMNIPASS, the Smart Brain also supports interworking with several IoT platforms such as AllJoyn and so on. It communicates with people through voice input on the Smart Brain App to provide useful life information like weather, currency, news and for controlling electronic appliances such as TV and air conditioner.The Smart Brain can construct security system used together with companion devices such as door sensor and supports home automation by presetting internal-external environments. Also, it can connect to Smart-Plug for efficient power management. It provides wireless Internet access point functionality too. The greatest advantage of the Smart Brain is that it can work together with various types of device from different venders to develop new smart M2M/IoT services.</lang></description><productName>Smart Brain</productName><brandName>Modacom Co., Ltd</brandName><productCode>MIT-SB100</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Smart Brain has support the Association Command Class.It has one association group, the u0022Lifelineu0022 group, which supports sending associated devices reset notifications when the device is factory reset.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-15110014"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
