<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0245"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0002"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15120005</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The wireless flush-mount switching actuator PSC132ZW allows you to remotely control electrical appliances. It features a metering function to measure the power consumption and the accumulated energy usage of connected equipment. The built-in metering unit is of high quality: it calculates the true-power and also works for small loads from 1W upwards. This feature is important to have a correct measurement value also for electronic loads like led lamps.The PSC132ZW has a built-in safety features that will switch-off the output in case of too high temperature or overload.Additionally the PSC132 has a feature to switch the load on at zero voltage and switch the load off at zero current. This leads to a very high number of possible switching cycles also for difficult loads like led-lamps or motors, e.g. pumps.</lang></description><productName>Smart Mini Plug</productName><brandName>permundo</brandName><productCode>PSC132ZW</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group1 Z-Wave Plus LifelineEvents/Notifications:(1)Sends COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC, BASIC_REPORT after every change of the output state (on/off). (2)Sends COMMAND_CLASS_METER_V2, METER_REPORT_V2 after every change of the measured energy or power value or after a timeout if the values stay unchanged. during If the energy or power value didnt change for a certain time.Min. time between 2 reports if the energy or power value changes: 1sTimeout for sending a report if the value stays unchanged: 15min.Min. change in value to trigger a report:4% power (mind. 2W) oder 1Wh energy</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Events/Notifications:Sends COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC, BASIC_REPORT every time the mechanical switch at the input S1 is operated.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="31" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Local Control Off</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If LocalControlOn is set (factory default state) the PSC132ZWs output can be switched manually by a mechanical rocker-switch or a pushbutton that is connected to the S1 input of the device. If LocalControlOff is set, the PSC132ZWs output can only be switched through Z-wave telegrams. In both modes the operational state of the mechanical switch is reported to association group 2. LocalControlOff is ment for using the switch-input functionality and the relay functionality separately. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Local Control On</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Local Control Off</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-15120005"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
