<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="013C"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0010"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16025010</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">This in-wall switch module is a transceiver which is a security enabled device which based on Z-Wave Plus technology, and it is fully compatible with any Z-WaveTM enabled network. Mini size design let the module can easily hide itself into the wall box and that will be good for the house decoration. Since PAN05 supports Security Command Class, it can learn with Secured controller. Its functionality and supported command classes is identical when included as a secure and non-secure device. There are many kind of application by using the module to switch Load On and Off, one main application is the light control. If connect the COM terminal directly to AC Line terminal, the new smart relay calibration technology can reduce the inrush current caused by the load and let the module work perfectly with many kind of light like incandescent, fluorescent and LED light. This module can also connect to alternative power supply like DC 12V to switch on/off 12V MR-16 light.Adding to Z-WaveTM Network In the front casing, there is an on/off button with LED indicator below which is used to toggle switch on and off or carries out add, remove, reset or association. When first power applied, its LED flashes on and off alternately and repeatedly at 0.5 second intervals. It implies that it has not been assigned a node ID and start auto inclusion. Auto Inclusion The function of auto inclusion will be executed as long as the in wall switch does not have Node ID and just connect the switch to main power. Note: Auto inclusion timeout is 2 minute during which the node information of explorer frame will be emitted once every several seconds. Unlike Add function as shown in the table below, the execution of auto inclusion is free from pressing the On/Off button on the Switch. </lang></description><productName>In Wall Single relay(1way) switch module</productName><brandName>Philio</brandName><productCode>PAN05-1B</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus LifelineThe Switch can be set to send reports to associated Z-Wave devices. It supports only one association group and the group has one node support. Group1 support SWITCH_BINARY_REPORT. For group 1, the Switch will report ON/OFF status of Relay to controller. </lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Edge / Pulse / Edge-Toggle mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Manual switch S1 and S2 can set to Edge mode or Pulse mode or Edge-Toggle mode, default value is Edge mode.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1Edge mode</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2Pulse mode </lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3Edge-Toggle mode </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="11" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Manual Switch Report mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever PAN11 is manually switch on or off, it will send BINARY_SWITCH_ REPORT to the node of group1. The default setting is Enable the function. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 : Disable</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 : Enable </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Restore Switch State Mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever the AC power reconnected to PAN05, it will set the switch to OffOn or Last switch state, default value is Last switch state.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 : Switch Off</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 : Last Switch State</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2 : Switch On</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Manual On/Off Mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The On/Off function of S1S2 and learn switch can be disabled or enabled by this parameter, default value is Enable. But the learning operation wont be affected. When manual On/Off function is disabled, the RF command can only switch On but not Off. This is useful function for keeping the device in switch on state. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0Disable manual On/Off </lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1Enable manual On/Off</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED indication Mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">1. Show switch stateLED on for switch on and off for switch off. The default value is Show switch state. 2. Show night modeLED off for switch on and on for switch off. 3. One Flash modeWhen the state of switch changes, LED will be on only one second, then LED keeps off. </lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1Show switch state</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2Show night mode </lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3 : One flash mode</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto Off timer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">When auto off timer is equal to 0, the auto off function will be disabled. Whenever the switch is set to on, the auto off timer begin to count down. After the timer counts to zero, PAN05 will switch off automatically. The default value is disable auto off function.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0Disable auto off function</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1-0x7FFF1 ~ 32767seconds </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">RF Off command mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever a RF Off command is received, BASIC_SETBINARY_SWITCH_SETSWITCH_ALL_OFF, it could be interpreted as Switch OffSwitch OnSwitch Toggle, or it would be ignored. The default value is Switch Off. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0Switch off </lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1Ignore</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2Switch toggle</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3Switch on </lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16025010"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
