<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0084"/><productType value="0473"/><productId value="0110"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16045038</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Information is power! With flow meter, you have the power to automate and manage water consumption and leak detection in your home or building.This is an integral part to a complete water management solution!Flow meter tracks water usage and reports in gallons.Track your households water usage!Drill into reports and find out where your peak consumption is and make changes to reduce your water bills.Flow meter also tells you if water is flowing or not. It knows if the flow is small (like a toilet running) or large (a garden hose left on). This can be used to detect leaks, faulty appliances, or fixtures left on. To add to it's capabilities, flow meter checks the temperature of the nearby surroundings to make sure the pipes don't freeze by sending you temperature reports.There's also a backup battery just in case power is interrupted. You wont have to worry about lost data or a lack of leak monitoring. Plumbed on the water main, flow meter is sure to be a valuable part of your home automation &amp; leak prevention system.</lang></description><productName>Flow Meter</productName><brandName>FortrezZ LLC</brandName><productCode>FMI</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus LifelineDevice Reset Locally (via 3 quick presses of the program switch)Multilevel Sensor Temperature ReportMeter Pulse Report (flow count)Notificationsu00a3Under temperature detectedu00a3Over temperature detectedPower (Voltage Drop/Droop)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Command with value = 0xFF is sent to the associated nodes to indicate that a Temperature High condition has been detected.When the temperature is back in the normal range, one additional report with value = 0x00 is sent.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Command with value = 0xFF is sent to the associated nodes to indicate that a Temperature Low condition has been detected.When the temperature is back in the normal range, one additional report with value = 0x00 is sent.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Command with value = 0xFF is sent when the meter count is incremented (i.e., flow has started). Do not set associations for this group if water flow is expected. When flow is not expected (for example, at a vacant vacation home), this association group can be set to perform various tasks such as commanding a water valve to open in order to stop the flow of water and/or commanding a siren/strobe unit to activate. Since the Basic Set Command (value 0xFF) is sent every 30 seconds while the water is flowing; this commanding should be turned off by removing the associations in this group if water flow is normally expected.Note that no command is ever sent with a value of 0x00 because the FMI cannot know if or when conditions have returned to normal.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="4" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Low Threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set threshold for Low Temperature trigger.Default set to 4C (39F)</lang></description><value from="246" to="69"><description><lang xml:lang="en">-10 to 69C</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="70" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature High Threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set threshold for High Temperature trigger.Default set to 70C (158F)</lang></description><value from="247" to="70"><description><lang xml:lang="en">-9 to 70C</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Meter Count </lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Meter Count reset back to 0 or set value.</lang></description><value from="0" to="2147483647"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 TO 2147483647count rolls over at 99,999,999</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="6" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Meter Reporting Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Meter Report Interval, while liquid flow is detected (in increments of 10 seconds). If 0 is set, then no continuous reporting during liquid flow; in this case, a report is sent every 10 hours whether or not flow is detected.Default value of 6 represents 60 seconds (1 minute).</lang></description><value from="0" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 to 2,550 seconds (0XFF)</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="50" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Meter Threshold (low vs High flow)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Use this to set the Gallons count per interval.Default is 50 (5 gallons).. If this number of meter counts is exceeded during the above Meter Report Interval, then General Multilevel Sensor Report (MLS) with value=255 and large threshold leak notification messages are sent.If less than the threshold, then MLS value=128 and low threshold leak notification messages are sent. If flow stops, then MLS value = 0 and inactive water notification messages are sent.</lang></description><value from="0" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 to 65535 (0XFFFF)</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">MultiLevel Sensor Report vs Notification Toggle</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Use this to toggle between Notification Command Class &amp; MultiLevel Sensor report.By default, FMI uses Notification Command Class (Water Flow).Set a Non-zero value to disable Notification Command class and enable the Multi Level Sensor report instead.Multi level sensor report will send (0, 128, or 255).Notification command class will send (Water Flow V7 w/ parm 1,2, 3)</lang></description><value from="0" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 = Notification, 1= MLS report</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16045038"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
