<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="010F"/><productType value="0D01"/><productId value="3000"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16045047</certNumber><rfFrequency>Australia and New Zealand</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">FIBARO Swipe is a revolutionary, battery or Micro USB powered gesture control pad that allows you to control devices through the Z-Wave network. Swipe your hand up, down, left or right in front of the pad, make circular gestures and use sequences of gestures to get full and intuitive control of your smart home.Installed device perfectly matches your interior design, as it resembles a picture frame. You can even personalize it with your favourite picture. Gesture controlled menu allow to add/remove or reset the device without dismounting it.The device is equipped with a buzzer that confirms performed gestures and other actions.</lang></description><productName>FIBARO Swipe</productName><brandName>FIBARO</brandName><productCode>FGGC-001</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lifeline reports the device status and allowsfor assigning single device only (main controller by default).</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Flick UP is assigned to moving the handup over the panel (sends Basic Set command frames).</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Flick DOWN is assigned to moving thehand down over the panel (sends Basic Set command frames).</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Flick LEFT is assigned to moving thehand from the right to the left side of the panel (sends Basic Set commandframes).</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="5" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Flick RIGHT is assigned to moving thehand from the left to the right side of the panel (sends Basic Set commandframes) .</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="6" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Circular AirWheel is assigned to circularmove of the hand clockwise or counter-clockwise over the panel(sends Switch Multilevel Start/Stop Level Change command frames).</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16045047"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
