<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0258"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="1087"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16055074</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">This product can be included and operated in any ZWave network with other ZWave certified devices from other manufacturers and/or other applications. All nonbattery operated nodes within the network will act as repeaters regardless of vendor to increase reliability of the network.In the front casing, there is button that is used to carry out include, exclude or reset factory default settings on PCB Board.When power is first supplied, the LED will flash on and off with yellow alternately every 1 second intervals within 5 seconds if the detector has not been added a ZWave network, otherwise the LED will flash on and off 5 times with cyan alternately every 300 millisecond. Please get familiar with the terms below before starting the operations.This Plug has function that remembers the relay states, the plug will turn on after power up next time if the plug is turn on before the power cutoff.</lang></description><productName>Smart Power Plug </productName><brandName>Coolcam</brandName><productCode>NAS-WR01Z</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">GROUP 1 is lifeline service that assigned to plug statusON/OFF. It enables the Plug to send reports and readings to ZWave Controller or ZWave Gateway. This Group Support:NOTIFICATION_REPORT_V4 METER_REPORT_V4 SWITCH_BINARY_REPORT DEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">GROUP 2 allows for sending control commands to associated devices such as Siren, relay module, lighting, etc. If current load is over the max current defined in parameter #3, the Plug will send a BASIC_SET (0xFF) to associated devices. When current load is normal, plug will send a BASIC_SET (0x00) to associated devices. This Group Support:BASIC_SET</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">GROUP 3 allows for Send Notification to associated devices in this group. This Group Support: NOTIFICATION_REPORT_V4</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16055074"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
