<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="018E"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0002"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16065093</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The HD-9ZW is a Z-Wave heat detector that triggers a 95-decibel siren when room temperature rises above the threshold value of 57C, or when the rate of temperature rise is greater than 8.3C per minute. Suitable for rapid fire-prone environments, the HD-9ZW delivers precise and effective early warning to eliminate potential fire hazards.</lang></description><productName>Heat Detector</productName><brandName>Climax Technology</brandName><productCode>HD-9ZW</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 for LifeLine:Notification CC,V4 (COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATION)Battery CC (COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC)Device Reset Locally CC</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> Group 2 for Basic Set:Basic CC, v2 (COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> Group 3 for Notification Report: Notification CC,V4 (COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATION) Trigger Report (high temperature detected) When the Heat Detector is triggered, it will transmit Notificationcommand (Notification Type:0x04, Event:0x02) to all nodes in Group1 and3, and Basic set (0xFF) commands to the nodes in Group 2. Restore Report (High temperature calmed) When high temperature cool down, it will transmit Notificationcommand (Notification Type:0x04, Event:0x06) to all nodes in Group 1and 3, and Basic set (0x00) commands to the nodes in Group 2.Low Battery Report When low battery voltage is detected, the Smoke Detector will transmitBattery command to all nodes in Group 1. When the Smoke Detector on low battery has its battery replaced, it willtransmit Battery restore command to all nodes in Group 1. Factory Reset When the Smoke Detector is reset to factory default, it will send Device Reset Locally to all nodes in Group 1.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16065093"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
