<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0039"/><productType value="0011"/><productId value="0002"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-11090003</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Honeywell, the number one choice of homeowners and the worlds leading brand for temperature control, continues their tradition of excellence and quality with the ZWSTAT Z-Wave Thermostat. ZWSTAT communicates with the 5800ZBRIDGE Z-Wave Energy Management Module to enable automatic control with Honeywells leading security systems, making it an ideal addition to any Z-Wave connected home or building. Precise temperature control enables ZWSTAT to provide better comfort, fewer temperature swings and conserve more energy. Users can create keypad lockouts in homes and businesses an excellent way to save money and energy by curtailing children and unauthorized personnel from adjusting the thermostat. Other notable features include the ability to alternate between heating and cooling based on temperature settings, alerts to change air filters and pads, fan circulation and more.Exclusive ZWSTAT FeaturesAdaptive Intelligent Recovery Allows the thermostat to learn how long the furnace and air conditioner take to reach programmed settings, so the temperature is reached at the scheduled time.Keypad Lockouts Optional range stops can be created to keep temperature settings limited to a minimum/maximum settingideal for retail and residential applications where employees and children may attempt to adjust thermostats.Reminders ZWSTAT can alert homeowners to clean and change air filters and humidifier/dehumidifier filters and padshelping to maximize performance and efficiency while conserving energy. ZWSTAT Z-WAVE THERMOSTAT</lang></description><productName>Honeywell - Opower TH8320ZW1026</productName><brandName>Honeywell Home</brandName><productCode>TH8320ZW1026</productCode></deviceDescription><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.security.honeywell.com/hsc/products/expacc/zb/316009.html"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
