<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="000C"/><productType value="0x03"/><productId value="0x02"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16075132</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The HS-WV100+ Z-Wave Valve Controller is a professionall grade Z-Wave Device that allows the water to your home or business to be automatically (or remotely) turned off when water is detected by water sensors connected to any Z-Wave capable controller. The HS-WV100+ Z-Wave Valve Controller is Z-Wave Plus compliant allowing you to use all of the functionality and programmability built into the new, Z-Wave Plus Controllers. It comes with a Stainless Steel Electronic Ball Valve.Design and Operation of The HS-WV100+ Valve Controller-Simply install the stainless steel Electronic Ball Valve on theorwater line where water enters your home or business, attach it to the HS-WV100+ by plugging in the RJ-11 telephone jack, and tell your Z-Wave controller about the HS-WV100+ and your home or business is protected. Standard telephone wires and connectors can be used to extend the Ball Valves wire so it is easy to locate the Electronic Ball Valve where you need it to be, and still have easy access to the HS-WV100+ Z-Wave Valve Controller. When any of your water sensors get wet, your Z-Wave Controller will tell the HS-WV100+ to turn the water off and Voil! No Flood!A fully capable Z-Wave device, you can also program scenes that allow your HS-WV100+ to turn the water off when you leave home and arm your security system and back on when you get home. No more worries about your house flooding while you are away.Also, for your convenience and piece of mind, there are two buttons on the HS-WV100+ that allow you to instantly turn your water off and on. No more looking for that water key and digging in the yard looking for your water meter!</lang></description><productName>HomeSeer Valve Controller</productName><brandName>HomeSeer</brandName><productCode>HS-WV100+</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lifeline group</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16075132"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
