<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="021F"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="1082"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16075143</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Dome Home Automation DMWD1 Door/Window Sensor does more than just monitor if a door or window is opened at your home. With a Z-Wave Certified Hub, this sensor can respond to real-time events by sending alerts to your smartphone when the garage door is left open or by turning on the basement lights automatically when you open the door to go downstairs. Your Hub can even alert you when cabinets containing dangerous cleaning supplies, prescription medication or alcohol are opened to keeping your family safe. A Z-Wave Certified Hub, such as Dome Hub is required to operate the Door/Window Sensor. Most functionality is also available when used with other compatible hubs. Extra-long wireless range (up to 150 ft) allows you to easily keep track of doors, windows and cabinets at your home. There is a 3-year battery life, so you can always be confident that your sensor has power. The sensor measures 2.75 in long x 0.8 in high x 0.8 in wide and the magnet measures 1.6 in long x 0.5 in high x 0.5 in wide. Dome DMWD1 Door/Window Sensor comes with a 1-year limited warranty. Dome Home Automation system gives your family peace of mind and security you can count on. With Dome, youre always connected and always covered.Monitors if doors/windows are open or closed, can send you reminders if you left your garage door openWorks with exterior or interior doors, garage doors, patio doors, windows, cabinets, safes, closet door, baby gates and other openingsZ-Wave Plus Certified. Requires a Dome Home Automation Hub or other Z-Wave Certified Hub to operateUp to 150-foot range and 3-year battery life (CR14250 Battery Included)Tested to work with SmartThings, Vera, Staples Connect, HomeSeer, Nexia, Piper, URC, Harmony. Not supported by Wink, DSC, ADT Pulse, 2Gig, Napco, Interlogix, Honeywell (Dome is not associated with listed brands)</lang></description><productName>Dome Door/Window Sensor</productName><brandName>Dome</brandName><productCode>DMWD1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 is the Lifeline group, which can hold five members, typically including the main Z-Wave controller. The Door/Window Sensor sends this group a Notification Report and a Binary Sensor Report when it is opened or closed. It also sends this group a Battery Report in response to Battery Get commands.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Door/Window Sensor sends a Basic Set command to association Group 2 (or the Control Group) to directly trigger devices (like a light, chime, etc.) in response to events. Then, after a preset delay, a BASIC_SET(0x00) command is sent to reset the device (e.g. turn off the light.) The value of the Basic Set command (e.g. brightness of the lamp,) and the delay time before the BASIC_SET(0x00) is sent is configured using configuration parameters 1 and 2 respectively.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 3 supports up to 5 members and the Door/Window Sensor sends it a NOTIFICATION_REPORT when the door either opens or closes.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 4 supports up to 5 members and the Door/Window Sensor sends it a SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT when the door either opens or closes.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">BASIC_SET Off Delay</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the delay time from when the Door/Window Sensor sends the BASIC_SET command to Association Group 2 and when the BASIC_SET(0) is sent. It accepts a value up to 65535, in seconds.</lang></description><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="99" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">BASIC_SET Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the value sent by the BASIC_SET command to Association Group 2 (for more information, see Association Groups.)</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Off/Cancel Alarm/Etc.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dim Level (for Multilevel Switch)</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">On (for Binary Switch)</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16075143"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
