<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="027A"/><productType value="0101"/><productId value="000A"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16085160</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Product features:- Manual and remote on / off control- Energy monitoring- Scene inclusion for custom automation scenarios when included to a Z-Wave gateway controller- LED indicator displaying Z-Wave signal strength and power usage- Security enabled Z-Wave device with AES signal encryption (requires a security enabled gateway controller for full functionality)- Z-Wave Plus with improved 500 chip for faster and safer wireless communication- Built-in range extender for a stronger, more reliable network - 2 USB charging ports for your smart phone or tablet (no Z-Wave functionality)- Built-in overload protection in Z-Wave outlet and USB portsProduct Specifications: Model Number: ZEN06Z-Wave Signal Frequency: 908.42 MHzPower: 110V, 60HzMaximum Load: 15A, 1800WUSB Charging Port Power: 1A and 2.4AOperating Temperature: 14104 FRange: Up to 130 feet line of sightInstallation and Use: Indoor onlyDimensions: 4 x 2.5 x 1.2Weight: 7oz</lang></description><productName>Zooz Z-Wave Smart Plug</productName><brandName>Zooz</brandName><productCode>ZEN06</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="151" size="2" default="50" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power Report Value Threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose how you want your Smart Plug to report power consumption to your controller and associated devices. The number entered as value corresponds to the number of Watts the appliance needs to go over for the change to be reported. So if 50 Watts are entered by default, the smart plug will report any change in power usage over 50 Watts (whether its at least 50 Watts more or 50 Watts less compared to previous report).</lang></description><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">number of Watts the appliance needs to go over for the change to be reported</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">disabled (it will not report power consumption based on value change)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="152" size="1" default="10" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power Report Percentage Threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose how you want your Smart Plug to report power consumption to your controller and associated devices by percentage rate. The number entered as value corresponds to the percentage in power usage change the appliance needs to go over for the event to be reported. So if 10% is entered by default, the Smart Plug will report any change in power consumption over 10% (whether its at least 10% more or 10% less power consumption compared to previous report).</lang></description><value from="1" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">percentage in power usage change the appliance needs to go over for the event to be reported</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">disabled (it will not report power consumption based on percentage change)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="171" size="4" default="30" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power Report Frequency</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose how often you want your Smart Plug to report power consumption (W) to your controller and associated device. The number entered as value corresponds to the number of seconds. So if 30 is entered by default, the Smart Plug will report power consumption every 30 seconds.</lang></description><value from="5" to="2678400"><description><lang xml:lang="en">number of seconds for the interval the Smart Plug will report power consumption</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">disabled (it will not report power consumption)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="172" size="4" default="300" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Energy Report Frequency</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose how often you want your Smart Plug to report energy usage (KWH) to your controller and associated device. The number entered as value corresponds to the number of seconds. So if 300 is entered by default, the smart plug will report energy usage every 300 seconds (5 minutes).</lang></description><value from="5" to="2678400"><description><lang xml:lang="en">number of seconds for the interval the Smart Plug will report energy usage</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">disabled (it will not report energy usage)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="173" size="4" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Voltage Report Frequency</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose how often you want your Smart Plug to report voltage (V) to your controller and associated device. The number entered as value corresponds to the number of seconds.</lang></description><value from="5" to="2678400"><description><lang xml:lang="en">number of seconds for the interval the Smart Plug will report voltage</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">disabled (defaultit will not report voltage levels)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="174" size="4" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Electricity Report Frequency</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose how often you want your Smart Plug to report levels of electrical current (A) to your controller and associated device. The number entered as value corresponds to the number of seconds.</lang></description><value from="5" to="2678400"><description><lang xml:lang="en">number of seconds for the interval the Smart Plug will report energy current</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">disabled (defaultit will not report electrical current levels) </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="20" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Overload Protection</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Overload protection will turn the Smart Plugs relay off once voltage exceeds 16.5A for over 5 seconds when this setting is enabled. We DO NOT recommend changing this parameters value as it may result in device damage and malfunction.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="21" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">On/Off Status Recovery After Power Failure</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose the recovery state for your Smart Plug if power outage occurs.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Smart Plug remembers the status prior to power outage and turns back to it (default)</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Smart Plug automatically turns ON once power is restored (it does not remember the status prior to power outage)</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Smart Plug automatically turns OFF once power is restored (it does not remember the status prior to power outage)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="24" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">On/Off Status Change Notifications</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Your Smart Plug will automatically send a notification to the controller and other associated devices if its status changes from on to off or the other way round. Choose when you want it to send the report.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">disabled (it will not send status change notifications)</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">sends notification if status is changed manually or remotely via Z-Wave (default)</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">sends notification ONLY if status is changed manually by pressing and releasing the Z-Wave button on the Smart Plug</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="27" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED Indicator Control</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">You can choose how the LED indicator displays power consumption on the smart plug.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED indicator will display power consumption whenever the device is plugged in (LED stays on at all times)</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED indicator will display the level of power consumption for 5 seconds only whenever the device is turned on or off (LED indicator will stay off for most of the time)</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16085160"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
