<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="027A"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="1087"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16085170</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Product features:- Local and remote on/off control of lamps and small appliances- Energy monitoring in live mode or over time (your Z-Wave gateway needs to support this feature)- Scene inclusion for custom automation scenarios when included to a Z-Wave gateway controller- Advanced configuration to customize LED indicator display and Z-Wave button functionality- Automatic status recovery after power outage- Timer option to turn off the device automatically (your Z-Wave gateway needs to support this feature)- Z-Wave Plus with improved 500 chip for faster and safer wireless communication- Built-in range extender for a stronger, more reliable network - Super small sizeeasily fits two in a standard double receptacle Specs:Model Number: ZEN07Z-Wave Signal Frequency: 908.42 MHzPower: 110V, 60HzMaximum Load: 13APower consumption: 0.13WOperating Temperature: 32104 FRange: Up to 100 feet line of sightInstallation and Use: Indoor onlyDimensions: 1(diameter) x 1 1/8 Weight: 1oz</lang></description><productName>Zooz Z-Wave Mini Plug</productName><brandName>Zooz</brandName><productCode>ZEN07</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus lifeline communication of on / off status to Z-Wave controller. Supported command classes:NOTIFICATION_REPORT_V4COMMAND_CLASS_METER_V4COMMAND_CLASS_SWITCH_BINARYDEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Status and overload communication to other Z-Wave devices in the network. Supported command classes:BASIC_SET</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Notifications to Z-Wave devices associated in this group. Supported command classes:NOTIFICATION_REPORT_V4</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Metering Report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose if you want the Mini Plug to send metering reports to the controller.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Metering disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Metering enabled </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Manual Control</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose if you want to use the Z-Wave button to turn the Mini Plug on or off manually or if you want to disable this function. If this parameter is set to 0 (disabled), you will only be able to turn the Mini Plug on or off remotely using your Z-Wave gateway controller.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">manual control disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">manual control enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="300" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Metering Report Frequency</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose how often you want the Mini Plug to send metering reports to the controller. The number entered as the value corresponds to the number of seconds. So if 300 is entered by default, the Mini Plug will report power consumption every 300 seconds (5 minutes).</lang></description><value from="1" to="65536"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Number of seconds metering report is sent to controller</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="13" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Overload Protection</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Use this parameter to adjust the maximum amount of electricity you want your Mini Plug to handle. The number entered as the value corresponds to the number of Amperes. Overload protection will turn the Mini Plugs relay off once load exceeds 13A by default. It will also send a notification (NOTIFICATION_EVENT_POWER_MANAGEMENT_OVER_LOAD_DETECTED) to the controller and all associated devices. LED indicator on the device will blink red until the load is disconnected. Press the Z-Wave button ONCE to switch the alarm off.The value set in this parameter needs to be greater than the value in parameter 4.</lang></description><value from="1" to="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Maximum number of Amperes to be accepted by the Mini Plug</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Overload Notification</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Use this parameter to adjust electricity value for LED notifications of heavy load. The LED indicator on the Mini Plug will light up yellow once electricity from the load is greater than the value set in this parameter. The relay will NOT turn off.The value set in this parameter can NOT be greater than the value in parameter 3.</lang></description><value from="1" to="13"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Maximum number of Amperes that will trigger overload LED notification on the Mini Plug</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED Notifications</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Use this parameter to turn LED notifications on or off.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="5" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power Report Percentage Threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose how you want your Mini Plug to report power consumption, electricity, voltage, and energy usage to your controller and associated devices by percentage rate. The number entered as the value corresponds to the change in percentage the appliance needs to go over for the event to be reported. So if 5% is entered by default, the Mini Plug will report any change in power consumption (W), voltage (V), electricity (A), or energy usage (kWH) over 5% (whether its at least 5% more or 5% less compared to previous report).</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Percentage of change in power consumption, voltage, electricity, or energy usage to be reported to controller by the Mini Plug</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">On/Off Status Recovery After Power Failure</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose the recovery state for your Mini Plug if power outage occurs.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Mini Plug automatically turns OFF once power is restored (it does not remember the status prior to power outage)</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Mini Plug remembers the status prior to power outage and turns back to it</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto Turn-Off Timer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter 8: Use this parameter to enable or disable the auto turn-off timer function. If this feature is enabled, the Mini Plug will automatically turn off after a fixed period of time (set in parameter 9).</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timer disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timer enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="2" default="150" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto Turn-Off Timer Settings</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Use this parameter to set the time after which you want the Mini Plug to automatically turn off once it has been turned on. The number entered as value corresponds to the number of minutes.</lang></description><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Number of minutes the Mini Plug will turn off after once the auto turn-off timer is enabled</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16085170"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
