<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="027A"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="1082"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16085181</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">PRODUCT FEATURES:- Reliable open/close detection for doors, windows, cabinets, and drawers- Wireless notifications and event triggers (when included to a Z-Wave gateway controller)- Scene inclusion for custom automation scenarios when included to a Z-Wave gateway controller- Low battery alerts- Z-Wave Plus with improved 500 chip for faster and safer wireless communication- Discreet compact design SPECIFICATIONSModel Number: ZSE08Z-Wave Signal Frequency: 908.42 MHzPower: 1 CR2 battery (included)Power Consumption: 0.13WOperating Temperature: 32104 FRange: Up to 100 feet line of sightInstallation and Use: Indoor onlyDimensions: 2xWeight:oz</lang></description><productName>Zooz Z-Wave Contact Sensor</productName><brandName>Zooz</brandName><productCode>ZSE08</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 for lifeline communication of open / closed status to Z-Wave controller. Supported command classes:NOTIFICATION_REPORTBATTERY_REPORTSENSOR_BINARY_REPORTDEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 for control command communication to associated Z-Wave devices in the network. Use parameter 1 and parameter 2 to configure this groups settings. Supported command classes:BASIC_SET</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 3 for notifications to Z-Wave devices associated in this group. Supported command classes:NOTIFICATION_REPORT</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 4 for notifications to Z-Wave devices associated in this group. Supported command classes:SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Trigger Delay</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set the delay time for turning associated devices OFF based on status change of your Contact Sensor. The number entered as the value corresponds to the number of seconds. So if 0 is entered by default, the Contact Sensor will report status change and trigger an associated device to turn off instantly, without any delay. If you change this setting to 10, the sensor will only trigger the associated device after 10 seconds the status change is reported - if your door or window is closed, the light will not go off for another 10 seconds.</lang></description><value from="0" to="65536"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Seconds to delay associated device to turn off after sensor changes status</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Trigger Action</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">You can choose if your Contact Sensor turns an associated device on or off when sending the basic set command. Use value 0 to turn the associated device OFF and value 255 to turn it ON. Adjust brightness level for a Z-Wave dimmer (Multilevel switch) by putting in any value between 1 and 99. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Associated device will turn OFF when triggered by the sensor</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Brightness level % the associated device will turn ON to when triggered by the sensor</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Associated device will turn ON when triggered by the sensor</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16085181"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
