<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="027A"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0083"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16085198</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">PRODUCT FEATURES:- Accurate motion and light level detection - Wireless notifications and low battery alerts (when included to a Z-Wave gateway controller)- Custom automation scenarios based on both light and motion triggers (advanced configuration required)- Adjustable sensitivity levels for motion detection to fit your needs- Ultra small and simple design- Z-Wave Plus with improved 500 chip for faster and safer wireless communication- Flexible and quick installation SPECIFICATIONS:Model Number: ZSE09Z-Wave Signal Frequency: 908.42 MHzPower: 1 CR123A battery (included)Power Consumption: 0.15WOperating Temperature: 32104 FMotion detection: Up to 20 feetRange: Up to 100 feet line of sightInstallation and Use: Indoor onlyDimensions: 1.9 x 1.8 Weight:oz</lang></description><productName>Zooz Z-Wave Motion and Light Mini Sensor</productName><brandName>Zooz</brandName><productCode>ZSE09</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 for lifeline communication of motion / no motion and light level status to Z-Wave controller. Supported command classes:NOTIFICATION_REPORT_V4SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT_V2SENSOR_MULTILEVEL_REPORT_V7BATTERY_REPORTDEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 for control command communication to associated Z-Wave devices in the network. Use parameters 2, 3, 5, and 8 to configure this groups settings. Supported command classes:BASIC_SET</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 3 for notifications to Z-Wave devices associated in this group. Supported command classes:NOTIFICATION_REPORT_V4</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 4 for notifications to Z-Wave devices associated in this group. Supported command classes:SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT_V2</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Motion Sensitivity</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose the right motion sensitivity for your environment and lifestyle. Adjust detection just right by choosing a value from 8 to 255, where 8 stands for high sensitivity level (detection of the smallest movement) and 255 stands for very low sensitivity level.</lang></description><value from="8" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Motion detection sensitivity</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED Notifications</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Use this parameter to turn LED notifications on or off for motion detection.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Trigger ON Duration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set the duration you want the associated device to stay ON for after being triggered by the sensor before it automatically turns OFF. The number entered as the value corresponds to the number of seconds. So if 30 is entered by default, the associated device will stay ON for 30 seconds after the Mini Sensor reports status change (BASIC_SET command) and triggers the device, it will then turn off automatically. Its an easy and quick way to set up a motion-based lighting event. If you change this setting to 300, the associated Z-Wave light fixture will stay ON for 5 minutes after motion has been detected by the Mini Sensor. The value set for this parameter needs to be greater than value set in parameter 6.</lang></description><value from="5" to="600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Number of seconds the associated device to stay ON for after being triggered by the sensor before it automatically turns OFF</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Trigger Action</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">You can choose if your Mini Sensor turns an associated device on or off when sending the BASIC SET command. Use value 0 to turn the associated device OFF and value 255 to turn it ON. Adjust brightness level for a Z-Wave dimmer (Multilevel switch) by putting in any value between 1 and 99. </lang></description><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Associated device will turn ON when triggered by the sensor</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Brightness level (percentage) the associated device will turn ON to when triggered by the sensor</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="255" type="constant"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Motion Detection</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Use this parameter to enable and disable motion detection on your Mini Sensor.</lang></description><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Motion detection enabled </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="2" default="100" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Light Trigger Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set your light sensor as a secondary trigger for associated devices. If light level in a room falls beyond the set point and motion is detected, the Mini Sensor will send BASIC_SET command to associated devices to turn ON. The number entered as the value corresponds to the number of LUX. So if 100 is entered by default, the associated device will turn ON if light level last reported by the sensor is under 100 LUX and if motion has been detected by your Mini Sensor. Values: 01000 (LUX). 100 (LUX)default setting.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Light level change (in LUX) to set off light trigger</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="8" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Motion Trigger Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Adjust the time when motion is reported again after initial trigger. The number entered as the value corresponds to the number of seconds. So if 8 is entered by default, the Mini Sensor will report motion for 8 seconds after it first detects movement. The value set for this parameter can NOT be greater than value set in parameter 2.NOTE: Small interval will increase activity and decrease battery life.</lang></description><value from="1" to="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Number of seconds for motion trigger interval</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="2" default="180" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Light Polling Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Decide how often you want the Mini Sensor to report light level to the controller and associated devices. The number entered as the value corresponds to the number of seconds. So if 180 is entered by default, the Mini Sensor will report light level values every 3 minutes. The value set for this parameter can NOT be greater than the wake-up interval.NOTE: Small interval will increase activity and decrease battery life. </lang></description><value from="60" to="360000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Light polling interval in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Light Trigger</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Use this parameter to enable and disable the light sensor as secondary trigger. If this feature is enabled, the Mini Sensor will activate associated devices based on motion AND light level set in parameter 5.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Light trigger disabled</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Light trigger enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="2" default="100" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Light Report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose light level change to be reported by the Mini Sensor to the controller. The number entered as the value corresponds to the number of LUX. So if 100 is entered by default, the sensor will report any change of 100 LUX or more. </lang></description><value from="0" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Light level change (in LUX) to be reported by the sensor to the controller</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16085198"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
