<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="015D"/><productType value="0112"/><productId value="241C"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16085194</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">PRODUCT FEATURES:- Manual or remote on/off control and dimming from your mobile device or computer (when included to a Z-Wave gateway controller)- Z-Wave Plus with improved 500 chip for faster and safer wireless communication- Works with most high-quality DIMMABLE LED, CFL, and incandescent bulbs- Based on universal command classes - supported by most Z-Wave controllers- May be associated and grouped with other Z-Wave devices for advanced home automation- LED indicator to help locate the switch in dark space- Simple elegant design with screwless snap-on wall plate included- Built-in Z-Wave signal repeater for a stronger and more reliable networkSPECIFICATIONS:Model Number: ZEN22Z-Wave Signal Frequency: 908.42 MHzPower: 120 VAC, 60 HzMaximum Loads: 500W Single-gang, 400W Double-gang, 300W Triple-gang Incandescent, 150W CFL or LEDRange: Up to 100 feet line of sightOperating Temperature: 32-104 F (0-40 C)Installation and Use: Indoor only</lang></description><productName>Zooz Z-Wave Dimmer Light Switch</productName><brandName>Zooz</brandName><productCode>ZEN22</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Depending on your Z-Wave gateway's home automation software capabilities, you may be able to associate your Z-Wave switch in groups with other Z-Wave devices to schedule scenes and create events. This dimmer switch supports Group 1 with up to five devices for lifeline communication. This device will send SWTICH MULTILEVEL REPORT to Group 1 when operated manually.Please refer to your controller's user guide for advanced programming instructions as they are a little different for every software.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16085194"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
