<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="021F"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0086"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16095211</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Dome Home Automation DMMZ1 Mouser is a powerful rodent electric trap with Z-Wave technology built-in. It kills mice, rats and other rodents quickly, cleanly and humanely with a powerful jolt of electricity. Simply set bait, turn on and place in desired location. When connected to Z-Wave Certified Hub, once the trap is full, it sends out a notification to your smarthome system. You can easily dispose of Mousers contents without ever having to touch them. Use the top handle and tip to dispose of caught rodents. Specially designed removable and washable bait tray will allow you to easily replace the bait and set it back up. It operates on 4 AA batteries (not included) and is optimised to last over 50 uses. Mouser features extra-long Z-Wave wireless range (up to 150 ft) andDome DMMZ1 Mouser comes with a 1-year limited warranty. Measurements in inches: 8.75 x 4.5 x 5. Dome Home Automation Z-Wave devices give your family peace of mind and security you can count on. With Dome, youre always connected and always covered.Humanely kills mice, rats and other rodents with a powerful electric shock and sends an alert to your smarthome system when the trap needs to be emptiedEasy to use: set bait, turn on and place in desired location Touch free: hold handle and tip to dispose of contents, then set it againUp to 150-foot Z-Wave range. Operating Temperature: 32F - 112F. Powered by 4 AA batteries (not included) enabling it to be triggered over 50 timesZ-Wave Plus Certified. Works as a stand alone electronic mouse trapbut requires a Z-Wave Certified Hub for notification functionalityTested to work with SmartThings, Vera, Staples Connect, HomeSeer, Nexia, Piper, URC, Harmony. Not supported by Wink, DSC, ADT Pulse, 2Gig, Napco, Interlogix, Honeywell (Dome is not associated with listed brands)</lang></description><productName>Dome Mouser</productName><brandName>Dome</brandName><productCode>DMMZ1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 is the Lifeline group, which can hold five members, typically including the main Z-Wave controller.The Door/Window Sensor sends this group a Notification Report and a Binary Sensor Report when it is tripped, reset, armed, and disarmed.It also sends this group a Battery Report in reponse to Battery Get commands.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Mouser sends a Basic Set command to Association Group 2 (or the Control Group) to directly trigger devices (like a light, chime, etc.) when it is tripped. After the trap is reset, a BASIC_SET(00) command is sent to reset the device (e.g. turn off the light.) The value of the Basic Set command (e.g. brightness of the lamp) is configured using configuration parameter 1.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 3 supports up to 5 members and the Mouser sends it a NOTIFICATION_REPORT when tripped, reset, armed, and disarmed.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 4 supports up to 5 members and the Mouser sends it a SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT when tripped, reset, armed, and disarmed.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">BASIC_SET Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the value sent by the BASIC_SET command to Association Group 2 (for more information, see Assocation Groups.)</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn Off Device</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dim Level</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn On Device</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="2" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Set Firing Mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets firing mode of the Mouser.Two firing modes are available: in the first (Continuous Fire,) electricity is passed continuously for four minutes, and in the second (Burst Fire,) electricity is passed continuously only for the first minute andit is pulsedat approximately 400 beats per minute for the remainder of the time.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Continuous Fire</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Burst Fire</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="2" default="100" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines how long the Mouser will fire continuously before it starts to burst-fire (see parameter 2.)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines how long the Mouser will fire continuously before it starts to burst-fire (see parameter 2.)</lang></description><value from="100" to="360"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable LED Alarm</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter enables or disables the indicator LED alarm when the trap is tripped.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED Alarm Disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED Alarm Enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED Alarm Duration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the amount of time the LED Indicator blinks after the trap is tripped.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED Blinks Until Trap is Reset</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Hours</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16095211"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
