<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="021F"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="1087"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16095213</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Dome Home Automation DMOF1 On/Off Plug is designed to give you control over small appliances from your smart device wherever you are. Conserve energy and save money always knowing how much power is used by every monitored appliance. Plug in your lamp and have it turn on/off on demand or according to preset schedule (Z-Wave Certified Hub required). Also great for humidifiers, dehumidifiers, air conditioners, space heaters, fans and holiday lights. It never blocks the other side of your duplex receptacle with the ergonomic design. Extra-long Z-Wave wireless range (up to 150 ft) allows you to place it where its needed without worrying if the signal is reaching your Z-Wave Hub. It also acts as a Z-Wave range extender. Dome DMOF1 On/Off Plug comes with a 1-year limited warranty. Measurements in inches: 1.625 x 1.625 x 2. Dome Home Automation system gives your family peace of mind and security you can count on. With Dome, youre always connected and always covered. Used to turn On/Off lamps and small appliances for up to 13 Amps (1,560 Watts). Monitors energy consumption of attached device and shuts down in case of overload with build-in protection circuit Ergonomic design allows it to only occupy single side of electrical duplex leaving the second outlet fully accessible. It doubles as Z-Wave signal extenderUp to 150-foot range. Operating Temperature: 32F - 112FZ-Wave Plus Certified. Requires a Z-Wave Certified Hub to operateTested to work with SmartThings, Vera, Staples Connect, HomeSeer, Nexia, Piper, URC, Harmony. Not supported by Wink, DSC, ADT Pulse, 2Gig, Napco, Interlogix, Honeywell (Dome is not associated with listed brands)</lang></description><productName>Dome On/Off Plug-In Switch</productName><brandName>Dome</brandName><productCode>DMOF1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 is the Lifeline group, which can hold five devices. The On/Off Plug-In Switch sends this group a Notification Report and Binary Switch Report whenever it is turned on or off. It also sends a Meter Report incrementally based on time (see Param 2,) or when arelative change in power usage is detected (see Param 6.) Finally, the On/Off Plug-In Switch sends this group a Device Reset Locally notification to remove itself from the Z-Wave network.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The On/Off Plug-In Switch sends a BASIC_SET(FF) command to Association Group 2 to directly trigger devices (like a siren, chime, etc.) when the current passes above the level set in Parameter 3. When the current drops below the level again, a BASIC_SET(00) command is sent to reset the device (e.g. turn off the siren.) This Group can hold five devices.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The On/Off Plug-In Switch sends Notification Reports to Group 3, and it can hold five devices.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable METER_REPORT</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter enables/disables the METER_REPORT function, which sends periodic reports to Group1 members with information on line voltage, current load, and power &amp; energy consumption. Also see Param 2 &amp; 6.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable Meter Functionality</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enable Meter Functionality</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="150" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable BUTTON</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If this parameter is enabled, the user can turn the device on or off using the BUTTON.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable Button</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enable Button</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="300" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">METER_REPORT Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the amount of time between each successive METER_REPORT signal sent to Group 1 (also see Param 1 &amp; 6.)</lang></description><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="13" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Set &amp;amp;amp;amp;quot;Overload&amp;amp;amp;amp;quot; Current Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Sets the maximum current the plug will pass before it cuts off power and sends a NOTIFICATION_EVENT_POWER_MANAGEMENT_OVER_LOAD_DETECTED signal to Group 1 and a BASIC_SET(FF) to Group 2.The LED will then blink red once per second until the current returns to normal.To clear the NOTIFICATION and start monitoring again, the BUTTON must be pushed once (only after the current is back to normal.)NOTE: this value must be higher than Param 4</lang></description><value from="1" to="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Amps</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Set Alert Current Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Sets the current level at which the On/Off Plug-In Switch will flash its LED yellow, until the current returns to below this level.It will NOT cut off current to the device; this functions as a visible warning to the user.NOTE: this value must be lower than Param 3</lang></description><value from="1" to="15"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Amps</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable Indicator LED</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter enables or disables the indicator LED.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable LED</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enable LED</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="5" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Current change METER_REPORT level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">In addition to sending a METER_REPORT to Group 1 in the time interval set by Param 2, the On/Off Plug-In Switch also sends a METER_REPORT when it detects a relative change in current flow.This parameter sets this minimum current change amount, in percent, at which point the On/Off Plug-In Switch will send a METER_REPORT to Group 1.Also see Param 1 &amp; 2.</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in percent change in amps</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Remember On/Off Status</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets whether or not the On/Off Plug-In Switch will remember if it was turned on or off when it was last plugged in.If enabled, whenever the device is rebooted (plugged in and out of the main outlet,) it will resume its state from before the reboot.If disabled, it will turn on everytime the device is rebooted.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Do not Remember On/Off Status</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Remember On/Off Status</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable Timer Function</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If this parameter is enabled, whenever the On/Off Plug-In Switch is turned on, it will automatically turn off after a set amount of time (set in Param 9.)</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable Timer Functionality</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enable Timer Functionality</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="2" default="150" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Set Timer Time Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Sets the time interval before the On/Off Plug-In Switch automatically shuts off.See Param 8.</lang></description><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Minutes</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16095213"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
