<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="021F"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0085"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16095212</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Dome Home Automation DMWS1 Leak Sensor is purpose built to withstand a wet environment it may find itself in. It is suitable for areas where leaks are likely to occur: sinks, toilets, washing machines and water heaters. The Leak Sensors flat design allows it to be easily slid under common household appliances with low clearance from the floor. Additional flexibility is provided with a Remote Sensor extending 4 feet for placing it in hard to reach areas and sump pump pits. Once the leak is detected, the Leak Sensor will alert you by beeping locally and it will send an instant notification to your smarthome system. With a Z-Wave Certified Hub, this sensor can be set up to trigger sirens, lights and custom automation scenes or even turn off the water when used with Dome Water Main Shut Off (DMWV1). Extra-long Z-Wave wireless range (up to 150 ft) allows you to place it where its needed without worrying if the signal is reaching your Z-Wave Hub. There is a 3-year battery life, so you can always be confident that your sensor has power. Dome DMWS1 Leak Sensor comes with a 1-year limited warranty. Measurements in inches: 2.625x 2.625x 1.125. Dome Home Automation Z-Wave devices give your family peace of mind and security you can count on. With Dome, youre always connected and always covered. Water resistant design with ultra low profile to fit under appliances. Includes a 4 feet long Remote Probe for hard to reach areas and sump pump pitsLocal alarm sound with LED visual indicator when leaks are detected. Can be integrated with sirens, lights and compatible water main shut off valves (like Dome DMWV1)Up to 150-foot range and 3-year battery life (CR14250 Battery Included)Z-Wave Plus Certified. Requires a Z-Wave Certified Hub to operateTested to work with SmartThings, Vera, Staples Connect, HomeSeer, Nexia, Piper, URC, Harmony. Not supported by Wink, DSC, ADT Pulse, 2Gig, Napco, Interlogix, Honeywell (Dome is not associated with listed brands)</lang></description><productName>Dome Z-Wave Plus Leak Sensor</productName><brandName>Dome</brandName><productCode>DMWS1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 is the Lifeline group, which can hold five members, typically including the main Z-Wave controller.The Leak Sensor sends this group a Notification Report and a Binary Sensor Report when water is detected or removed.It also sends this group a Battery Report in reponse to Battery Get commands and a Locally Reset Notification upon local reset.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Leak Sensor sends a Basic Set command to Association Group 2 (or the Control Group) to directly trigger devices (like a light, chime, etc.) in response to a detected leak. Then, after the leak is no longer detected, a BASIC_SET(0x00) command is sent to reset the device (e.g. turn off the light.) The value of the Basic Set command (e.g. brightness of the lamp) is configured using configuration parameter 7.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 3 supports up to 5 members and the Leak Sensor sends it a NOTIFICATION_REPORT when water is detected or removed.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 3 supports up to 5 members and the Leak Sensor sends it a NOTIFICATION_REPORT when water is detected or removed.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="120" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Total Alarm Duration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the total amount of time the Leak Sensor will beep and light its LED in the event of a leak (see Figure 5.) </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Leak Sensor beeps until water is removed</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Minutes</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Mute Time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the amount of time the Leak Sensor remains quiet between each Reminder Alarm (see Fig 5.)</lang></description><value from="1" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Minutes</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="60" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Initial Alarm</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the amount of time the Leak Sensor beeps before it is muted (see Fig 5.)</lang></description><value from="10" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="5" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Reminder Alarm</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the length of each beep after the Initial Alarm (see Fig 5.)</lang></description><value from="5" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable Audible Alarm</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter enables or disables the audible alarm (beeping) functionality of the Leak Sensor.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable Audible Alarm</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enable Audible Alarm</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable Water Detection</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter enables or disables the Leak Sensor - if disabled, the device will not respond in any way to detected leaks.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Water Detection Disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Water Detection Enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the value sent by the BASIC_SET command to Association Group 2 (for more information, see Assocation Groups.)</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn Off Device</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dim Level</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn On Device</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16095212"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
