<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0090"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0238"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16105255</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Kwikset, the leader in residential security, introduces the SmartCode 910 Touchpad Electronic Deadbolt with Z-Wave.Backlit keypad with One touch locking30 user codesBHMA grade 2 certifiedFull 128-bit encryption securityDrill and pick resistant backup keywaySmartKey: Re-key the lock in seconds</lang></description><productName>SmartCode 910</productName><brandName>Kwikset</brandName><productCode>910</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus LifelineSupports the following types of unsolicited messages:Battery Report - sends periodic battery reports containing the battery percentage.Door Lock Operation Report - upon power up, this message will be sent to allow the controller to sync up with the current lock status.Notification Report - many notification types will be sent for status and alarms.The following notification types are supported:Access Control (V2), Home Security (V2), and Power Management (V2).Device Reset Locally Notification - this message will be sent to notify the smart home controller that the lock is resetting back to factory defaults and will be leaving the network.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">This group will provide all Notification reports as described for the Lifeline.This group allows other controllers, other than the lifeline, to receive these types of unsolicited messages as well.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 1</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 1. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 10</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 10. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="11" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 11</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 11. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="12" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 12</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 12. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="13" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 13</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 13. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="14" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 14</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 14. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="15" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 15</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 15. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="16" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 16</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 16. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="17" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 17</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 17. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="18" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 18</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 18. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="19" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 19</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 19. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 2</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 2. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="20" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 20</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 20. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="21" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 21</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 21. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="22" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 22</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 22. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="23" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 23</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 23. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="24" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 24</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 24. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="25" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 25</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 25. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="26" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 26</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 26. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="27" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 27</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 27. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="28" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 28</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 28. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="29" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 29</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 29. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 3</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 3. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="30" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 30</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 30. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 4</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 4. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="40" size="1" default="1" type="constant"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Reset to Default</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter allows the smart home controller to force a factory reset of the lock.After receiving this request, the lock will send a Device Reset Locally message back to the lifeline controller.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Force Factory Reset</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 5</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 5. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 6</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 6. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 7</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 7. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 8</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 8. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">User Code Type for User Code 9</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter is used to get or set the type of user for their corresponding user code. By default, all user codes are set to the Owner type unless otherwise specified. The parameter type is associated with the user code location 9. Caution must be used when setting these values. Guests and Workers will require schedules attached to them in order for those types to be assigned.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Owner</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Guest</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Worker</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16105255"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
