<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0090"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="4006"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16105261</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Kwikset, the leader in residential security, introduces the SmartCode 914 Touchpad Electronic Deadbolt with Z-Wave.10 digit backlit keypad with one touch lockingDramatically reduced, all-metal interior30 user codes plus master codeBHMA grade 2 certified20 minute fire rating - UL certifiedFull 128-bit encryption securitySmartKey: Re-key the lock in seconds</lang></description><productName>SmartCode 914</productName><brandName>Kwikset</brandName><productCode>914</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus LifelineSupports the following types of unsolicited messages:Battery Report - sends periodic battery reports containing the battery percentage.Door Lock Operation Report - upon power up, this message will be sent to allow the controller to sync up with the current lock status.Notification Report - many notification types will be sent for status and alarms.The following notification types are supported:Access Control (V2), Home Security (V2), and Power Management (V2).Device Reset Locally Notification - this message will be sent to notify the smart home controller that the lock is resetting back to factory defaults and will be leaving the network.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">This group will provide all Notification reports as described for the Lifeline.This group allows other controllers, other than the lifeline, to receive these types of unsolicited messages as well.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16105261"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
