<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="008C"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0024"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16105271</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">VeraPlus: Advanced Home Controller for Everything in Today's Smart Home UniverseOne-touch control of your entire systemView all your cameras and control all your devices from one easy appWorks with 4 popular wireless device protocols for maximum compatibility with most brands (Z-Wave, ZigBee, Bluetooth and Wi-Fi)See and control your system from any smartphone or tablet from anywhere in the world (where there's Internet)Save money on energy, automatically!Expand your system to control over 220 devices Wireless communications makes installation a breeze in any home or small businessEasy, intuitive setup with simple Q&amp;A format; adding devices later is easy too with preconfigured settings for most devicesNo monthly fees required!Cutting edge features like geo fencing let the system know when you're coming home, automatically, and when you leave, too!Controls all the leading brands of locks, thermostats, and other devices so you don't need to compromise when selecting components.More device compatibilityfour radio protocols work with most devicesFaster processor for superior performance (compared with VeraEdge)More memory for better response times and flexibility (compared with VeraEdge)WPS easy push button pairing for Wi-Fi devicesImproved multi-camera managementIntuitive user set up and controlLocal control of devices to avoid any latency or connectivity issues (works locally even when your Internet goes down)Use VeraPlus for home security, convenience and energy savings. Achieve the peace of mind of knowing your family is safe and your home or small business is alrightfrom anywhere in the world!</lang></description><productName>Multiple RF Home Gateway</productName><brandName>Vera Control, Ltd.</brandName><productCode>VeraPlus-US</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16105271"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
