<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0258"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="1083"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16105298</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">This product can be included and operated in any ZWave network with other ZWave certified devices from other manufacturers and/or other applications. All nonbattery operated nodes within the network will act as repeaters regardless of vendor to increase reliability of the network.In the Back casing, there is a button that is used to carry out include, exclude, wake up device or reset factory default settings.When power is first supplied, the LED will flash on and off alternately at one second intervals within 5 seconds if the detector has not been added a ZWave network. Please get familiar with the terms below before starting the operations.</lang></description><productName>Motion Sensor (PIR)</productName><brandName>Coolcam</brandName><productCode>NAS-PD01ZE</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">GROUP 1 is lifeline service that assigned to Sensor (Motion detector) statusOpen/Close. Itenables the sensor to send reports and readings to ZWave Controller or ZWave Gatewaywhenever the sensor is triggered. This Group Support:NOTIFICATION_REPORT_V4SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT_V2SENSOR_MULTILEVEL_REPORT_V7BATTERY_REPORTDEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">GROUP 2 allows for sending control commands to associated devices such as relay module,lighting, etc. This association group is configured through the advanced parameters no. 2, 3, 5and 8. This Group Support:BASIC_SET</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">GROUP 3 allows for Send Notification to associated devices in this group. This GroupSupport: NOTIFICATION_REPORT_V4</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">GROUP 4 allows for Send Sensor Binary Report to associated devices in this group. This GroupSupport:SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT_V2</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Sensitivity Level Setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the sensitivity of PIR detector, it is recommended to test the detectorwith movements from a farthest end of the coverage area at first time of use. If movementscannot be detected sensitively, simply adjust the sensitivity level with this parameter. ThisParameter can be configured with the value of 8 through 255, where 8 means high sensitivity and255 means lowest sensitivity.</lang></description><value from="8" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">unsigned</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Led Blink Enable</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the Led on/off enable. If this parameter is set to 1, the led blink will beenabled, the led will blink once when motion sensor detect a movement. Otherwise, the led willbe turned off always.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">unsigned</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">On/Off Duration Setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter can be determined how long the associated devices should stay ON status. Forinstance, this parameter is set to 30(second), the PIR detector will send a BASIC_SET Command toan associated device with value basic set level if PIR detector is triggered and the associateddevice will be turned on 30(second) before it is turned off. This Parameter value must be largethan Parameter 6#. If user set this parameter to default by Configure CC, the parameter #6 will beset to default value.</lang></description><value from="5" to="600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">second. unsigned</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="255" type="constant"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Command will be sent where contains a value when PIR detector is triggered, thereceiver will take it for consideration; for instance, if a lamp module is received the Basic SetCommand of which value is decisive as to how bright of dim level of lamp module shall be. ThisParameter is used to some associated devices.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0, 1 ~ 99 or 255 0OFF, Alarm cancelling or turning a device off 1 ~ 99 or 255ON (Binary Switch Device) Dim Level (Multilevel Switch Device)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enabled/Disabled PIR Function</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter can be enabled or disabled the PIR detector detecting function.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> Disable PIR Detector Function. unsigned</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> Enable PIR Detector Function. unsigned</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="2" default="100" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Lux Level Set</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter can be set a lux level value which determines when the light sensor is activated. Ifthe ambient illumination level falls below this value and a person moves across or within thedetected area , PIR detector will send a ZWave ON command(i.e. BASIC_SET (value = parameter3) to an associated device and activate it.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lux .unsigned</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="8" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Retrigger Interval Setting.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This Parameter can be used to adjust the interval of being retriggered after the PIR detector hasbeen triggered. This Parameter value must be less than Parameter 2#. If user set this parameterto default by Configure CC, the parameter #2 will be set to default value.</lang></description><value from="1" to="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">second .unsigned</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="2" default="180" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Light Sensor Polling Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This Parameter can be set the light sensor measure ambient illumination level interval time.NOTE: This Value Must Be less than Wakeup Interval Time.</lang></description><value from="60" to="36000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">second .unsigned</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Lux Level Enable</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If this parameter is set to 1, and when Lux level less than the value define by parameter #5, PIRdetector will send a BASIC_SET command frame(i.e. BASIC_SET (value = parameter 3) to anassociated device and activate it. If Lux Level greater than the value define by parameter #5, PIRdetector will not send a BASIC_SET command frame.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">unsigned</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="2" default="100" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Lux Level Report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines by how much Lux Level must change, in lux, to be reported to the maincontroller.</lang></description><value from="0" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lux. unsigned</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16105298"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
