<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="019D"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="54"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-16110002</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Tubular motor mob.iq EZRS M35 10/14 by Mobilus Motor Company is a modern radio controllable drive, designed to drive rolling shields. This device has a number of innovative solutions, including:SENSO technology:- programming of endpoints automatically or using the remote control,- operation regardless of the used hangers type,- bidirectional obstacles detection which eliminates failures due to obstacles (each failure will be reported to controller as an alarm)- saving your time due to lack of supervision of your shutters - obstacle detection system, insensitive to minor disruption during work.But the most important feature of our motor is the usage of Z-Wave technology as the communication standard. It provides inter alia:- easy procedure of connection the device to the network,- bidirectional communication between the motor operator and control device - therefore the user has the opportunity to receive a variety of information about the motor operator (location, work errors, obstacles encountered in the blinds way of work),- automatic creation of network of devices, so there is no need for additional radio signal repeaters,- compatibility with third party control devices - Z-Wave is a mature standard for radio communication, chosen by over two hundred manufacturers of devices intended to create anintelligent home control systems.Technical parameters:- fi roller tube diameter of 35 mm,- torque: 10 Nm,- revolutions per minute: 14 rpm,- supply voltage 230 V.</lang></description><productName>Tubular Motor EZRS M35 10/14</productName><brandName>MOB.IQ</brandName><productCode>Tubular Motor EZRS M25 10/14</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0086" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="https://mobilus.pl/en/produkty-mob-iq/silowniki-mobiq/silowniki-mobiq-m35/mobiq-m35-ezrs/"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
