<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0315"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16125344</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Z-Wave Toolbox is a self-contained tool that enables the user to easily troubleshoot Z-Wave networks. Whether the problem is a range issue, interference, or device placement, the Z-Wave Toolbox will make troubleshooting a breezeThe toolbox is a web-based, flexible tool that will work withany operating system, even smart phones and tablets. The toolbox contains 3 major applications, The Z-Wave Packet Analyzer, the Spectrum Analyzer, and the Network Health Tester.The Z-Wave Packet Analyzer allows the user to see Z-Wave traffic. It helps troubleshoot connections, identify abnormal device operation, and pinpoint weak spots. The Spectrum Analyzer allows users to scan frequencies close to Z-Wave frequencies for any interference. Network Health Tester. This powerful tool can determine link stability, quality of service, latencies, and can help the user totroubleshoot, optimize, and deploy Z-Wave networks with confidence. Technical details:Self-contained hardware that does not need computer to operateConnectivity - Ethernet, WiFi (AP and Client mode)Low power; it can run on batteries (battery pack sold separately)Power Adapter (12V/1A, 100-240VAC)FCC and CE compliant</lang></description><productName>Z-Wave ToolBox</productName><brandName>Z Wave Products Inc.</brandName><productCode>ZWP-TBX</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.zwaveproducts.com/shop/brands/zwaveproducts/zwp-tbx-z-wave-toolbox"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
