<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0154"/><productType value="0100"/><productId value="0400"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-16125341</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Weather is a cup anemometer for Z-Wave installations. It continually measures the wind speed and can, for example, trigger closing of the awnings and blinds if it is too windy. It also measures the amount of rotation, enabling calculation of the wind yield per day or per year. In addition, Z-Weather includes sensors for humidity, temperature, air pressure and dew point, essentially providing the core sensors of a weather station. Z-Weather is powered by a solar cell and stores energy on an internal capacitor, enabling continuous operation, even with few sun for a couple of days. It does not use any batteries and is completely maintenance free. Using the built-in solar cell it also measures the ambient light and the solar yield. This information can be used to turn on the outdoor light at dusk time and turn the light off in the morning. Z-Weather&amp;lsquo;s wind yield and solar yield metering can be used as a calculation base for planning a wind generator or a solar panel on the roof of a house.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;During normal operation, Z-Weather is limiting continuous measurement to wind speed and solar radiation, other sensors are operating only on demand. This conservative energy management ensures continuous operation with the limited energy harvested from the solar cell powering Z-Weather. The Z-Wave radio frequency transmitter is turned off most of the time and is turned on if there is too much wind, at twilight time and on a continuous base, depending on the energy budget. The wake up interval is between five minutes at noon in summer and five hours in the second half of the night in winter. Z-Weather also wakes up on pushing the button.</lang><lang xml:lang="de">&lt;p&gt;Die Popp Z-Weather Station wurde für den Outdoor-Gebrauch entwickelt und misst alle relevanten Wetterdaten.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Die Z-Weather Station misst kontinuierlich die Windstärke und kann so, beispielsweise, die Markisen und Jalousien schließen wenn es zu windig ist. Außerdem misst sie die Rotation, und erlaubt so eine Berechnung der Windausbeute pro Tag oder Jahr. Außerdem besitzt die Z-Weather Station Sensoren, um Luftfeuchtigkeit, Temperatur, Luftdruck und Taupunkt zu messen, wodurch sie alle wichtigen Bereiche einer Wetterstation abdeckt. Andere Z-Wave Geräte können direkt bei Sonnenaufgang und Sonnenuntergang angesteuert werden.&lt;br /&gt;Das Gerät wird durch eine Kombination aus extern angebrachter Solarzelle und interner Pufferbatterie mit Energie fersorgt und benötigt daher keine weitere externe Stromversorgung oder Batterien. Das interne Energiemanagement stellt sicher, daß immer genügend Energie für den Windalarm zur Verfügung steht und wird daher eventuell das Abfrageinterval für Temperatur, Feuchte ext. automatisch reduzieren.&lt;/p&gt;</lang></description><productName>Z-Weather</productName><brandName>Popp</brandName><productCode>POPE005206</productCode><inclusionNote><lang xml:lang="en">Push the button 3 times within 1.5 seconds. If the LED is not blinking after releasing the button, Z-Weather has not enough energy and must be charged for several hours in bright sunlight.</lang><lang xml:lang="de">Dreimal den Taster drücken innerhalb von 1.5 Sekunden. Wenn die LED nicht leuchtet, dann ist nicht genügend Energie vorhanden.</lang></inclusionNote><wakeupNote><lang xml:lang="en">Push the button 3 times within 1.5 seconds. The LED blinks once indicating that Z-Weather is alive.</lang><lang xml:lang="de">Drei Mal den Taster drücken innerhalb von 1.5 Sekunden. Wenn die LED nicht leuchtet, dann ist nicht genügend Energie vorhanden.</lang></wakeupNote><exclusionNote><lang xml:lang="en">Push the button 3 times within 1.5 seconds.</lang><lang xml:lang="de">Dreimal den Taster drücken innerhalb von 1.5 Sekunden. Wenn die LED nicht leuchtet, dann ist nicht genügend Energie vorhanden.</lang></exclusionNote></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lifeline.&amp;nbsp;</lang><lang xml:lang="de">Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Too windy If the threshold value for wind (Default value: 6m/s ) is exceeded, the basic set is sent to all group members.&amp;nbsp;</lang><lang xml:lang="de">Windstärke von mehr als 6 m/s (22 Km/h)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">It is getting bright.Sends BASIC SET command in the morning when brightness reached trigger level (Default value: 37%) </lang><lang xml:lang="de">Zum Ende der Morgendämmerung, wenn es hell wird</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">It is getting dark.Sends BASIC SET command in the evening when brightness reached trigger level (Default value: 37%)</lang><lang xml:lang="de">Zum Ende der Abenddämmerung, wenn es dunkel wird</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="6" type="constant"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold for too much wind</lang><lang xml:lang="de">Schwellwert für zu viel Wind</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Crossing this value&amp;nbsp;on the rising edge, Z-Weather sends a basic set to the associated groups, serves the lifeline and sends a wake up notification.</lang><lang xml:lang="de">Bei Überschreiten dieses Grenzwertes wird ein Kommando an alle Geräte der Assoziationgruppe 2 gesendet.</lang></description><value from="0" to="30"><description><lang xml:lang="en">m/s</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="37" type="constant"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold for twilight</lang><lang xml:lang="de">Schwellwert für Dämmerung</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the trigger level for twilight to control devices inassociation group 3 und 4</lang><lang xml:lang="de">Bei Überschreiten dieses Wertes wird ein Kommando in die Geräte der Assoziationsgruppe 3 gesendet. Gleichermaßen wird beim Unterschreiten dieses Wertes wird ein Kommando in die Geräte der Assoziationsgruppe 4 gesendet.</lang></description><value from="0" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">%</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-16125341"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
