<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="013C"/><productType value="0005"/><productId value="0031"/><libType value="Enhanced 232 Slave"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17045556</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">PAD02 is an E27(EU)/ E26(US) Edison screw based lamp socket, which provides electrical connection to the E14(EU)/ E12(US) Edison screw based lamps and support it in the lighting fixture. The use of socket allows lamps to be safely and conveniently replaced. You can On/Off the light by pressing the button briefly, or a long pressing to control the brightness of dimmable lightbulb. This dimmer is a transceiver which is a security enabled device which based on Z-Wave Plus technology. Z-Wave PlusTM enabled devices displaying the Z-Wave PlusTM logo can also be used with it regardless of the manufacturer, and can also be used in other manufacturers Z- WaveTM enabled networks. Remote dim level control of the connected light is possible with other manufacturers wireless Controller. Since PAD02 supports Security Command Class, it can learn with a Secured enabled controller to fully utilize the device. Its functionality and supported command classes is identical when included as a secure and non-secure device. Adding to Z- WaveTMNetwork In the front casing, there is an on/off button with LED indicator below which is used to switch on and off, dim level, or carries out add, remove, reset or association. When first power is applied, its LED flashes on and off alternately and repeatedly at 0.5 second intervals. It implies that it has not been assigned a node ID and start auto inclusion. Auto InclusionThe function of auto inclusion will be executed as long as the dimmer does not have Node ID and just connect the dimmer to main power. Note: Auto inclusion timeout is 2 minute during which the node information of explorer frame will be emitted once every several seconds. Unlike inclusion function as shown in the table below, the execution of auto inclusion is free from pressing the On/Off button on the dimmer. </lang></description><productName>Z-Wave Smart Dimmer Socket</productName><brandName>Philio</brandName><productCode>PAD02</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LifelineThe dimmer can be set to send reports to associated Z-Wave devices. It supports one association group with one node support for Grouping 1. For group 1, the dimmer will report ALARM_REPORTDEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION and MULTILEVEL_SWITCH_REPORT. </lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">When the On/Off status changes or the dim level is achieved manually, it will send BASIC_SET command to group 2 nodes to make them unanimous.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Dimmer Level Report mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever dimmer on/off state changes, it will send MULTILEVEL_SWITCH_REPORT to the nodes of group1. The default setting is Enable the function.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 : Disable</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 : Enable</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED indication mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">1. Show dimmer StateWhen dimmer is on, LED is on. When dimmer is off, LED is off. The default setting is Show dimmer State. 2. Show Night modeWhen dimmer is on, LED is off. When dimmer is off, LED is on. 3. One flash mode : When dimmer on/off state changes, LED will light on one second and then off.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 : Show dimmer state</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2 : Show night mode</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3 : One flash mode</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Restore dimmer state</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever the AC power return from lost, PAD02 will restore the switch state which could be Dimmer offLast dimmer stateDimmer on. The default setting is Last dimmer state.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 : Dimmer off</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 : Last dimmer state</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2 : Dimmer on</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17045556"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
