<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0271"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="1A73"/><libType value="03"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="30"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17045541</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The moveable sensor-switched outdoor floodlight with fully swivelling LED panel in a classy opal look. The XLED home 2 sensor-switched floodlight comes in a sophisticated design. It is not just an eye-catcher, but also a truly talented mover. Thanks to the fully swiveling LED panel, every corner of the entrance area can be illuminated flexibly and as required. The highly efficient LED technology coupled with the opal cover provides maximum lighting comfort. As an individual floodlight or interconnected with the slave version, the innovative new generation of the XLED home success series is available in white, black, graphite and silver.Smart home included.The optional Smart Friends Box and the free Smart Friends app make it easy to set the XLED home 2 Z-Wave via smart phone or tablet. The floodlight can also be switched ON or OFF via app. Other Steinel products can also be interconnected. If you wish, this also works via remote control when you are out. That completes your own light management system.Along with STEINEL products, Smart Friends solutions from PAULMANN, SCHELLENBERG and ABUS can also integrated. Smart homes from a brand-name provider.</lang></description><productName>XLED home 2 Z-Wave</productName><brandName>Steinel GmbH</brandName><productCode>50111677101 </productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus LifelineLifeline messages- Device Reset Locally- Notifications:0x09 ( System )Hardware failure with manufacturerproprietary code ( 0x03 )0x09 ( System )Software failure with manufacturerproprietary code ( 0x04 )0x07 ( Home security )Motion Begin event ( 0x08 )0x07 ( Home security )Motion End event ( 0x00, 0x08 )- Binary Switch Reportlamp state- Multilevel Sensor Reportvalue of internal ambient lightsensorMotion Begin and Motion End events are sent along withframes to group 3. If multichannel association is created theevents are sent from motion sensor endpoint.Switch Report is sent immediately upon a change of statusalong with frames to group 2. If multichannel association iscreated the events are sent from lamp endpoint.Multilevel Sensor Report is sent a maximum of once per1 minute (if the value has changed by least by 3%) anda minimum of once per 15 minutes (if the value has notchanged). If the ambient light value is old (cannot measurebecause of permanent light), the value is not transmitted vialifeline. Multilevel Sensor Report can be also added to someother events to send in bulk. If multichannel association iscreated the events are sent from light sensor endpoint.All notifications to lifeline are sent as sensor states regardlessof sensor settings and states as SLAVE_MODE, LOCAL_DISABLED and MOTION_ENABLE.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">On/Off Control-Basic SetGroup 2 is used for directly controlling Z-Wave devices viaBASIC SET commands through the evaluation of movementand light as with internal use ( so that all of these deviceswork together ). This is intended for use especially withthird-party devices that do not implement reactions for motionevents. BASIC_SET and similar Z-Wave commands arenot retransmitted intentionally to slaves and must be sentto slave devices via the controlling device simultaneously.Only for use in master-slave system, multidevice control isnot possible.Group 2 is evaluated and frames are transmitted there also inSLAVE_MODE, regardless of LOCAL_DISABLED state andwhen MOTION_ENABLE is off ( not using internal motion sensorjust reacts for remote motion events then ).If multichannel association is created the events are sendfrom motion sensor endpoint.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Motion begin/end - Notifications: 0x07 (Home security)Motion Begin event (0x08)0x07 (Home security)Motion End event (0x00, 0x08)Group 3 sends MOTION_BEGIN and MOTION_END frames.MOTION_BEGIN frame = Notification 0x07 ( Homesecurity )Motion detection without location ( 0x08 )MOTION_END frame = Notification 0x07 ( Home security ) After first motion detection MOTION_BEGIN is sent. If continualmovement is detected MOTION_BEGIN is sent every1 minute repeatedly. When motion ends, MOTION_END issent 5 seconds after the last motion detection.Notification to group 3 is sent only when NIGHT_MODE =ON and MOTION_ENABLE = ON, regardless ofLOCAL_DISABLE state.All devices in a group should have the same TIME settings inorder that they switch off at the same time.If multichannel association is created the events are sendfrom motion sensor endpoint.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Ambient light- Multilevel Sensor Reportvalue of internal ambient light sensorAmbient Light via group 4 is intended to substitute locallymeasured LUX values in target devicesso that the networkcan have one source of ambient light value. The frame rate isa value being sent a maximum of once per 2.5 minutes, anda minimum of once per 15 minutes.When device already uses remote Ambient light value, thenthis value is also retransmitted to group 4.All devices in such a group should have the same LIGHT( threshold ) settings in order that night mode is detected atthe same time.If multichannel association is created the events are sendfrom light sensor endpoint.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="180" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">TIME</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Duration of light after motion detection.</lang></description><value from="5" to="900"><description><lang xml:lang="en">seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="2" default="10" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">OFF_BEHAVIOUR</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Behaviour after BASIC OFF ( and similar commands ).If a transition ( even with zero change ) with a non-default duration isto be processed, the transition cannot be interrupted by any motionevent in any case.for values 1-209 - Lamp is switched off and remains so until after a specified timeout once a new motion event (local or remote) is received.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lamp is switched off and remains so until any new motion event (local or remote) is received.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 second (1) to 100 seconds (100) in 1-second resolution</lang></description></value><value from="101" to="200"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 minute (101) to 100 minutes (200) 1-minute resolution</lang></description></value><value from="201" to="209"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 hour (201) to 9 hours (209) in 1-hour resolution</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lamp is switched off for TIME (cfg 1). It does not wait for a motion event and works normally via current motion evaluation</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="11" size="2" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">ON_BEHAVIOUR</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Behaviour after BASIC ON (and similar commands).If a transition (even with zero change) with a non-default duration is to be processed, the transition cannot be interrupted by any motion event in any case.for values 1-209 - Lamp is switched on and remains so until after a specified timeout once a new motion event (local or remote) is received.It then works normally via current motion evaluation.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lamp is switched on and remains so until any new motion event (local or remote) is received. It then works normally via current motion evaluation. Noticeduring the day, this mode cannot be ended remotely due to motion events not being transmittedonly via local motion sensor if enabled.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 second (1) to 100 seconds (100) in 1-second resolution</lang></description></value><value from="101" to="200"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 minute (101) to 100 minutes (200) 1-minute resolution</lang></description></value><value from="201" to="209"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 hour (201) to 9 hours (209) in 1-hour resolution</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lamp is switched on for TIME (cfg 1). It does not wait for a motion event and works normally via current motion evaluation.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="12" size="2" default="204" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">ON_TIME_OVER</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Time limit to stop waiting for motion after timeout of ON_BEHAVIOURor OFF_ON_BEHAVIOUR ( 0-209 ) to prevent staying ON forever whenis no motion.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">o additional waiting for motion.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 second (1) to 100 seconds (100) in 1-second resolution</lang></description></value><value from="101" to="200"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 minute (101) to 100 minutes (200) 1-minute resolution</lang></description></value><value from="201" to="209"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 hour (201) to 9 hours (209) in 1-hour resolution</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Never stop waiting before motion.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="13" size="2" default="204" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">ON_OFF_BEHAVIOR</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Behaviour after after a rapid sequence of BASIC ON and BASIC OFF commands.The intention is to use a much longer timeout value than the time after a single ON command which should then be followed by a short timeout value.The behaviour is almost the same as for parameter 10 (OFF_LOCAL_DISABLE) for values 1-209 - Lamp is switched off and remains so until after a specified timeout once a new motion event (local or remote) is received.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lamp is switched off and remains so until any new motion event (local or remote) is received.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 second (1) to 100 seconds (100) in 1-second resolution</lang></description></value><value from="101" to="200"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 minute (101) to 100 minutes (200) 1-minute resolution</lang></description></value><value from="201" to="209"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 hour (201) to 9 hours (209) in 1-hour resolution</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">device ignores ON - OFF sequence and uses OFF behavior</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="14" size="2" default="204" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">OFF_ON_BEHAVIOUR</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Behaviour after after a rapid sequence of BASIC OFF and BASIC ONcommands.The intention is to use a much longer timeout value than the time aftera single OFF command which should then be followed by a shorttimeout value.The behaviour is amost the same as for parameter 11for values 1-209 - Lamp is switched on and remains so until after a specified timeout once a new motion event (local or remote) is received.It then works normally via current motion evaluation.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lamp is switched on and remains so until any new motion event (local or remote) is received. It then works normally via current motion evaluation. Noticeduring the day, this mode cannot be ended remotely due to motion events not being transmittedonly via local motion sensor if enabled.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 second (1) to 100 seconds (100) in 1-second resolution.</lang></description></value><value from="101" to="200"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 minute (101) to 100 minutes (200) 1-minute resolution</lang></description></value><value from="201" to="209"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 hour (201) to 9 hours (209) in 1-hour resolution</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">device ignores OFF - ON sequence and uses ON behaviour</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="15" size="1" default="255" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">SEQUENCY_TIME</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Time in [ 100 miliseconds ] of maximum delay between BASIC ONand BASIC OFF ( and vice versa ) to consider this as a sequence. It istypically 1 second, but can be exceptionally longer due to retransmissionsand overloadin this case, a longer interval can be allowed ( upto 5 seconds ).</lang></description><value from="10" to="50"><description><lang xml:lang="en">tenth of second</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="16" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">MOTION_DISABLE</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Motion disable timeout after BASIC SET to motion endpoint when theinternal motion sensor is not used for evaluating the behaviour of thelamp and groups 2 and 3. Events are, however, still transmitted to theLifeline, and the lamp can be controlled via remote motion sensors.for values 1-209 - Internal motion sensor is disabled for specified timeout after BASIC SET 0x00 to Motion endpoint.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">BASIC SET to Motion endpoint ignored, Motion sensor still enabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 second (1) to 100 seconds (100) in 1-second resolution</lang></description></value><value from="101" to="200"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 minute (101) to 100 minutes (200) 1-minute resolution</lang></description></value><value from="201" to="209"><description><lang xml:lang="en">timeout: 1 hour (201) to 9 hours (209) in 1-hour resolution</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">BASIC SET to Motion endpoint ignored, Motion sensor still disabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="2000" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LIGHT</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Light threshold [ lx ]Value can be controlled via potentiometerpotentiometer value isused as the default value and any potentiometer movement rewritesthe current setting.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">run Learn ambient light sequence (the level is set automatically)</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="1999"><description><lang xml:lang="en">lux</lang></description></value><value from="2000" to="2000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2000 - is used as daylight ( always night mode)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="100" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">SENSITIVITY</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Motion Sensor (radar) Sensitivity [%]Value can be controlled via potentiometerpotentiometer value isused as the default value and any potentiometer movement rewritesthe current setting</lang></description><value from="2" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">%</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">BRIGHTNES MEAS INTERVAL</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Brightness measuring interval [ minutes ]Interval for ambient light measuring when lamp is on ( lamp switchesoff shortly and measures ). 0=function is off</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function is off</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="120"><description><lang xml:lang="en">minutes</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">GLOBAL_LIGHT</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Use External Ambient Light ValueWhen GLOBAL_LIGHT mode is ONdevice overrides its own lightsensor values and uses Light report values from any Z-Wave lightsensor insteadthis has to be configured appropriately to send lightautomatically.If the last remote light level value is older than 30 minutes, the internallight value is used again until the next external value is received.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ON function</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">OFF function</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="2" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">SLAVE_MODE</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Can disable sensor controllStupid mode (bit 2 = 1): - has higher priority then slave mode. - lamp is permanently on (usefull for simple power wall switch controlling).Slave mode ( bit 0 = 1 ):- only if included in Z-Wave network- usefull for controlling via third-party sensor- lamp is directly controlled via Z-Wave, internal sensors are not used for controlling it.Central unit checking ( bit 1 = 1 ):( usefull especialy for controlling via gateway ) When Slave bit is 0:- lamp signalises fail of lifeline connection ( if this bit is zero fail of lifeline connection is not signalised ) When slave bit is 1:- lamp checks presence of Z-Wave device in lifeline group ( gateway ). If it is not present for 2 minutes ( testing repeatedly every 30 seconds ) device switches to normal mode in the same way as after the end of local disabled mode ( ON_BEHAVIOUR )- The device checks every 1 minute for recovery of Lifeline connection.- if no lifeline specified - it works in normal modeBe careful with this option, lamp stops using its own motion sensor in Slave and Stupid mode.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Normal mode</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Slave mode without gateway checking</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Normal mode with lifeline error signalisation</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Slave mode with gateway checking</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Stupid mode - lamp permanetly on</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17045541"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
