<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="026B"/><productType value="0004"/><productId value="0004"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17025446</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">This product consists of a premium quality Photoelectric Smoke Alarm designed to North American standards, combined with a plug-in Z-Wave wireless communication module.The Smoke Alarm will also function as a standalone device and is certified by Underwriters Laboratories and satisfies all UL217 requirements. Patented, high-performance optical chamber with integral micro-mesh fixed insect screen further reduces the possibility of false alarms.A large test button allows on-device test of smoke chamber, electronics and battery. The device also offers a built-in self-test and an electronic smoke chamber test making the use of test aerosol unnecessary. A low battery warning will last for 30 days, but full function of the Alarm will continue during this time.The Z-Wave module allows the device to report smoke (EiA650RFZ) or to report smoke, as well as low battery alarms wirelessly to a central Z-Wave Controller.</lang></description><productName>Z-Wave Photoelectric Smoke Alarm</productName><brandName>Ei Electronics</brandName><productCode>EiA650RFZ</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Alarm Reports. All devices in this group will receive Alarm notifications (Smoke , Battery Low, Tamper)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Switching Command. All devices in this group will receive a BASIC SET command on Smoke Alarms. Configuration parameter 3 and 4 will define when ON and when OFF is sent.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17025446"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
