<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="018E"/><productType value="0004"/><productId value="001D"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17035457</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">CL Meter is an energy metering device designed to measure, monitor, and report the energy consumption of an entire household or apartment building directly from the electric box or breaker panel, for users to look for energy-saving opportunities or provide tenant-specific billing. Installed directly in the homes main circuit box, with the clamps attached to it, the CLMT-1ZW will monitor the total amount of electricity the entire home uses with accuracy and speed. With the CL Meter, users can easily track their power usage, allowing them to make the most out of reducing energy consumption and achieving greater energy efficiency.</lang></description><productName>Clamp Meter</productName><brandName>Climax Technology</brandName><productCode>CLMT-1ZW</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 for LifeLine: (maximum node:1)Device Reset Locally CC, V2 Meter CC, V2For group 1, the Clamp Meter will report:(1) The sum of instant Power Consumption (Watt) read fromCT1 and CT2(2) The sum of accumulated Power Consumption (KWh) readfrom CT1 and CT2</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 for meter CT1 (maximum node: 1)Meter CC, V2For group 2, the Switch will report: (1) Instant Power Consumption (Watt) read from CT1 (2) Accumulated Power Consumption (KWh) read from CT1</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 3 for meter CT2: (maximum node: 1)Meter CC, V2For group 3, the Switch will report(1) The sum of instant Power Consumption (Watt) read from CT2(2) The sum of accumulated Power Consumption (KWh) read from CT2</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17035457"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
