<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="008C"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0025"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17045531</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">VeraSecure is an easy-to-install comprehensive home controller/alarm hub. Its like an alarm security panel in a box. Just add sensors, cameras and lockschoosing from dozens of brandsand VeraSecure does the rest. VeraSecure does more than securityyou can adjust thermostats, control lights, garage doors, and more. Operate everything from one easy app on your smartphone, tablet or computer.Get The Security &amp; Peace Of MindOf Never Arriving Home To A Dark HouseoAutomatically schedule your lights to turn on before you enter your home with a VeraSecure System.Of Being Sure When Your Kids Come HomeoReceive notifications automatically with your motion sensor &amp; security camera connected to your VeraSecure System.Of Knowing Your Home Is SafeoCameras, sensors and siren ensure your home is being monitored from anywhere on your mobile device.Of Watching What Your Pet Is Up TooWith your VeraSecure System and security camera you can always ensure your pet is safe.Of Knowing You Are Saving MoneyoBy never wasting energy in your home with control of lighting, heating and cooling.Get Maximum Compatibility &amp; PerformanceComprehensive wireless connectivity with Z-Wave, ZigBee, Bluetooth LE, VeraLink (433/345 Mhz), 802.11a/b/g/n/ac Wi-Fi3G cellular connection keeps home protected even when Internet goes out Built-in backup battery protects home during power outages (4-8 hours)Built-in Siren for local alarm notification2-Way audio for optional VeraProtect 24/7 alarm monitoring service</lang></description><productName>Advanced Smart Home Security Controller</productName><brandName>Vera Control, Ltd.</brandName><productCode>VeraSecure - US</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17045531"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
