<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0196"/><productType value="00B7"/><productId value="0097"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17065668</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">PersonalCompliment your home dcor with a beautiful 5 touch-screen LCD, which you can personalize with pictures and themes.Install and run Android apps right on the switch, making it easy to use your Internet telephone, streaming music, recipe and smart home apps.SmartLearns from your usage, automatically turning on the lights when you need themsaving you time, energy and money.Easily connect to and control up to 4 additional Brightswitches or Z-Wave/Z-Wave Plus devices from a single Brightswitch.FriendlySet up new switches quickly and easily with just 3 steps, and then Brightswitches find and add each other automatically.Control switches or change background pictures from anywhere on the Internet with the Brightswitch secure Web-based portal.SafeMonitor your home with the built-in security system. Record or stream video and send a photo MMS to your phone.Set the switch to turn lights on/off whenever you wantmaking it easy to look like you are home, even when you are notGreat for vacations or everyday security.</lang></description><productName>Brightswitch</productName><brandName>Brightswitch</brandName><productCode>201</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline.Frames sent: Device Reset Locally Notification, Switch Multilevel Report (when dim level is changed locally)</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17065668"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
