<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0293"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="001A"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17055586</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Your smart home deserves better than an ordinary light switch.Hogar touch panels are one-of-a-kind collection of switches that will transform walls from boring to an absolutely breath-taking. Fits in existing electrical boxes and does not require new wires. Innovative assembly and snap-in system make it fast and simple to install.Hogar touch panels are the modern creation of switch range that sets the tone in every room. The series makes a convincing impression with its clear structure and its choice of customized color variants. The colored glass frames come in Black, White, Moroccan Blue, Nature Green, Wooden Brown, Elegant Grey, while the metal frames are colored in Black, White, Grey and Rose Gold.Some highlights of the smart features-A touch can do more - Programmable touch buttons to act as a Toggle or Mono stable mode. Mono stable mode can give additional advantage of running scenes when used with Z-wave Home controller. -Uniform dual back light LED with 2-way feedback-Optional custom label or logo design for each button-2 minutes installation with no additional wiring-Heat, Humidity and Shock proof design, No worries in wet or hot areas-A perfect match for LED loads with protective inrush current</lang></description><productName>Touch Panel Switch</productName><brandName>Hogar Controls</brandName><productCode>HG-TS10</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Profile: Control key01Commands: Basic SetGroup name: HGT-01</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Profile: Control key01Commands: Switch Binay SetGroup name: HGT-01</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Profile: Control key02Commands: BasicGroup name: HGT-02</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="5" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Profile: Control key02Commands: Switch Binay SetGroup name: HGT-02</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="6" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Profile: Control key03Commands: BasicGroup name: HGT-03</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="7" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Profile: Control key03Commands: Switch Binay SetGroup name: HGT-03</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="8" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Profile: Control key04Commands: BasicGroup name: HGT-04</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="9" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Profile: Control key04Commands: Switch Binay SetGroup name: HGT-04</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17055586"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
