<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0131"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0015"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17055604</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Using Micromodule Motor Controller user can control connected rollershuttersandblinds,finelyadjusttheirpositionwithhis Z-Wave controller, Z-Wave remote or simple push of a button.MicromoduleMotorControllerisZ-WavePlusenableddevice whichmakesitcompatiblewithanyZ-Waveenablednetwork, regardless of the manufacturer. Slim design makes it easy to fit in majority of wall boxes. New smart-relay calibration technology reduces inrush current caused by the load and enables module to work perfectly with all kinds of roller shutters and blinds. Micromodule is able to detect position of the Shutter by using thepatternedpowermeasuringmethod,soitcanberemote controlled not only fully up or down, but also can be adjusted to ex. 30% or 50%. When manually operated by the push button, Micromodule Motor Controllercanalsomemorizethepositionandsendthenew shutter position to its controller (ex. IP-Gateway).</lang></description><productName>Micro Module motor controller</productName><brandName>Zipato</brandName><productCode>ph-pan08.eu</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LifelineThere is only one group called Group1, there is only one node for Group1 which support MULTILEVEL_SWITCH_REPORT, METER_REPORT_COMMAND_V3, ALARM_REPORT.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="720" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Watt Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Ifthesettingisconfiguredfor1hour(setvalue=720),the Micromodulewillreportitsinstantpowerconsumptionevery 1hourtothenodeofcorrespondingGroup.Themaximum intervaltoreportitsinstantpowerconsumptionis45hours (5s*32767/3600=45hr). Default value is 1 hour.</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">5*720s=3600s=1 hour</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="6" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">KWH Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Ifthesettingisconfiguredfor1hour(setvalue=6),the MicromodulewillreportitsAccumulatedPowerConsumption (KW/h)every1hourtothenodeofcorrespondingGroup.The maximum interval to report its Accumulated Power Consumption (KW/h) is 227.55 days (10min*32767/1440=227.55 days). Default value=1 hour.</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">6*10min= 1 hour</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="2" default="500" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of current for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the wattage of load exceeds the preset thresholdvalue,Ifthesettingvalueis500,whentheload currentoverthisvalue,Micromodulewillsendcurrentmeter reportcommandtothenodeofcorrespondingGroup.Default value=500.</lang></description><value from="10" to="500"><description><lang xml:lang="en">500*0.01=5 A</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="2" default="10000" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of KWH for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the KWh of load over the preset threshold value,Ifthesettingvalueis10000,whentheAccumulated PowerConsumptionofRelay1orRelay2overthisvalue, Micromodule will send KWh Meter Report command to the node ofcorrespondingGroup,minimumvalueis1KWhanddefault value is 10000 kWh.</lang></description><value from="1" to="10000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">10000*1KWh=10000KWh</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">External switch type</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">1.ONE PUSH BUTTONWhen the configuration setting is One Push Button, only S1 input will be valid. The control moving commands can be accepted in this switch type while the shutter is moving. In this switch type, theinclusion/exclusion/reset/associationfunctioncanalsobe fulfilled by pressing S1 just like the operation of include button. WhenS1isshortpressed,theshutterwillmoveuptoward TOP(0xFF). If during this movement S1 is short pressed again, the shutter will stop moving. A third short pressing of S1 will move the shutter down toward BOTTOM(0x00). If during this movement S1 is short pressed again, the shutter will stop moving. And so on Inverting direction and stopping.2.TWO PUSH BUTTON: (THE DEFAULT SETTING IS TWO PUSH BUTTON (2))IfthissettingisconfiguredasTwoPushButton,S1andS2 input will be valid, but will not accept pressing S1 and S2 at the sametime.Inthisswitchtype,theinclusion/exclusion/reset/association function can also be fulfilled by pressing S1 or S2 just like the operation of include button. When S1 is pressed and held more than 1.5 seconds, the shutter will move up toward TOP(0xFF), and the shutter will stop moving when S1 is released. When S2 is pressed and held for more than 1.5 seconds, the shutter will move down toward BOTTOM(0x00), and the shutter will stop moving when S2 is released.WhenS1isshortpressed,theshutterwillmoveuptoward TOP(0xFF). If during this movement S1 i short pressed again S1 again, the shutter just keep moving up toward TOP(0xFF). The easy way to stop this moving is short pressing S2. When S2 is short pressed, the shutter will move down toward BOTTON(0x00). If during this movement S2 is short pressed again S2 again, the shutter just keep moving down toward BOTTON(0x00). The easy way to stop this moving is short pressing S1. When in Two Push Button switch type, S1 or S2 are pressed and not released, and PAN08 receive any control moving command from Z-Wave RF (Ex. BASIC_SET, BINARY_SWITCH_SET, MULTILEVEL_SWITCH_SET, MULTILEVEL_SWITCH_START_LEVEL_CHANGE or MULTILEVEL_SWITCH_STOP_LEVEL_CHANGEorSCENE_ACTIVATION_SET),PAN08wontdoanychangeinpositionbut report alarm to Group1 (Alarm_Type=1, Alarm_level =0xFF), this indicate that the S1 or S2 not been release. </lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1: One Push button</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2:Two Push button</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="2" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Level report mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Mode 1 : In 5 seconds period after controlled by a moving command, it will report the destination level when received request command. Out of the 5 seconds period, it will report the actual level of the shutter when received request command.Mode 2 : Whenever the shutter moves past a 10 percent level, it will auto report the level to Group 1 node.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1:Report destination level in 5s</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2:Report 10 percent level while running</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17055604"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
