<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0131"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0012"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17065647</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">ThisproductcanbeoperatedinanyZ-Wavenetworkwithother Z-Wave certified devices from other manufacturers. All non-battery operated nodes within the network will act as repeaters regardlessofvendortoincreasereliabilityofthenetwork. Micromodule Switch Double is a transceiver which is a Z-Wave Plus enableddeviceandisfullycompatiblewithanyZ-Waveenabled network. Mini size design allow the module to be easily hidden into the wall box which is good for the house decoration. There are many kinds of application for using the module to switch AC power ON and OFF, one of which is the light control. The new smart relay calibration technology can reduce the inrush current caused by the load and let the module work perfectly with many kinds of light like incandescent, fluorescent and LED light. This Micromodule is able to detect Instant power wattage and overload wattage (current 7.5A) of connected light or appliances. When detecting overload state, theswitchwillbedisabledanditsON/OFFbuttonwillbelocked during which LED will flash repeatedly. Unplugging and reconnecting the Module will reset its overload condition to normal status.</lang></description><productName>Micro Module Switch Double w.meter</productName><brandName>Zipato</brandName><productCode>ph-pan04.eu</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LifelineMicromodulecanbesettosendreportsinordertocontrol associatedZ-Wavedevices.Itsupports3associationgroups whicheverygrouphasonenodesupport.Group1~Group3 support SWITCH_BINARY_REPORT, METER_REPORT_COMMAND_V3 For group 1, Micromodule will report (1) ON/OFF status of Relay1 and Relay2 (2) Instant Power Consumption (Watt) of Relay1 and Relay2 (3) Accumulated Power Consumption (KWh) of Relay1 and Relay2 to Z-Wave Controller. </lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">For group 2, Micromodule will report (1) ON/OFF status of Relay1 (2) Instant Power Consumption (Watt) of Relay1 (3) Accumulated Power Consumption (KWh) of Relay1 to Z-Wave Controller. </lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">For group 3,Micromodule will report (1) ON/OFF status of Relay2 (2) Instant Power Consumption (Watt) of Relay2 (3) Accumulated Power Consumption (KWh) of Relay2 to Z-Wave Controller. </lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="720" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Watt Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If the setting is configured for 1hour (set value =720), Micromodule willreportitsinstantpowerconsumptionevery1hourtothe node of correspond Group. The maximum interval to report its instant power consumption is 45 hours (5s*32767/3600=45hr).</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">5*720s=3600s=1 hour</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Existence of Endpoint3</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multi-Channel Command is a good way to control relay1 and relay2 of Switch individually. The endpoint3 of Micromodule is related to both relay1 and relay2. In some condition it becomes redundant in Multi-Channel Command Class. When the Existence of Endpoint3 is set as 2, the endpoint3 will be disabled. The default value is 1. Endpoint1 and Endpoint2 are fixed, only Endpoint3 is dynamic.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1: Endpoint exist</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2: No Endpoint3</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="6" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">KWH Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If the setting is configured for 1hour (set value =6), Micromodule will report its Accumulated Power Consumption (KW/h) every 1 hour to the node of correspond Group. The maximum interval to report its Accumulated Power Consumption (KW/h) is 227.55 days (10min*32767/1440=227.55 days).</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">6*10min= 1 hour</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Slected End Point</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">IfMicromoduleisnotusingMulti_Channelcommandclassto access the relay of Switch, you may configure the select value to react the Basic Command Class, Binary Switch Command Class or Meter Command Class V3.1.SELECTED RELAY1:Only relay1 can be controlled and report.2.SELECTED RELAY2:Only relay2 can be controlled and report.3.SELECTEDRELAY1ANDRELAY2:DEFAULT SELECT IS 3Both relay1 and relay2 can be controlled and report.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1: Relay1</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2: Relay2</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3: Relay1 &amp;amp;amp; Relay2</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Edge or Pulse mode or Edge-Toggle mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Manual switch S1 and S2 can set to Edge mode or Pulse mode or Edge-Toggle mode, default value is Edge mode.1.EDGE MODE :This mode is suitable for the bi stable wall switch that has indicator point on the Micromodule, and the same position correspond to same state of relay1 and relay2. if the Switchs relay changes the state because of receiving Z-Wave RF command, it may need two switchings (switch on to off or switch off to on) to let relay back to the corresponding state.2.PULSE MODE :This mode is suitable for the toggle type wall switch to swap the state of Relay1 or Relay2.3. EDGE-TOGGLE MODE :This mode is suitable for the normal bi-stable switch, every state change of the wall switch will also swap the state of Relay1 or Relay2.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1: Edge mode</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2: Pulse mode</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3: Edge-Toggle mode</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="2" default="750" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of Current for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the wattage of load over the preset threshold value, If the setting value is 750, when the load wattage of Relay1 or Relay2 over this value, Micromodule will send Watt Meter Report command to the node of correspond Group, the Range of the setting value is from 10 to 750, and the default value is 750.</lang></description><value from="10" to="750"><description><lang xml:lang="en">750*0.01A = 7.5A</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="2" default="10000" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of KWH for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the KWh of load exceeds preset threshold value, If the setting value is 1000, when the Accumulated Power Consumption of Relay1 or Relay2 exceeds this value, Micromodule will send KWh Meter Report command to the node of corresponding Group, the Range of the setting value is from 10 to 1000, and the default value is 750.</lang></description><value from="1" to="10000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">10000*1KWh = 10000KWh</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Restore switch state mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever the AC power return from lost, Micromodule will restore the switch state which could be SWITCH OFF, LAST SWITCH STATE, SWITCH ON. The default setting is LAST SWITCH STATE.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0: Switch off</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1: Last switch state</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2: Switch on</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto off timer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever Micromodule switches to on, the auto off timer begin to count down. After the timer decrease to zero, it will switch off automatically. However if Auto off timer is set as 0, the auto off function will be disabled. The default setting is 0.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0: Disable auto off function</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1-0x7FFF: 1s - 32767s</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">RF Switch off command mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever a switch off command, BASIC_SET , BINARY_SWITCH_SET, SWITCH_ALL_OFF, is received, it could be interpreted as 4 kinds of commands.1.SWITCH OFF : It switches to OFF state. The default setting is Switch Off.2.IGNORE : The switch off command will be ignored.3.SWITCH TOGGLE : It switches to the inverse of current state.4.SWITCH ON : It switches to ON state.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0: Switch off</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1: Ignore</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2: Switch toogle</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3:Switch on</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17065647"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
