<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0300"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0010"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17055601</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Our connected dimmable lighting has basic function of On, Off and Dim, or in the lighting world, we just call it OFD. Using your app and controller/gateway, you can turn your lights on, off and dim them down to 5% brightness from anywhere in the world, using your smartphone. At 2700K and 800 lumens, it is a true 60W equivalent.With all of our lighting, and the app that supports it, you can group lights together, set different lighting scenes for different groups and set schdules to autotmatically turns lights, and groups, on and off. Not only does this give you tremendous lighting flexibility, but its great for security purposes. Automatically turning your lights on and off when youre away, gives the impression you are actually home and this will help deter unwanted entry.Our connected lighting has the additional option for what we call Saved State. Saved State allows you to save an actual light setting in the bulb itself. This means that when you lose power, the lights will not come back on to the standard, blaring 2700K at full bright. The Saved State will allow the lights to come back on to the nice setting youve previously saved.LEEDARSON stays on the cutting edge of technology and innovation. Thats because they have a responsibility to their customers. Thats because at LEEDARSON, We build your success in IoT.</lang></description><productName>A19 LED BULB DIMMABLE</productName><brandName>LEEDARSON</brandName><productCode>6VA-A806ST-Q1R</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="255" size="4" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">reset</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reset to factory configuration and removed theZ-Wave network.Reset Configuration parameter to default value.</lang></description><value from="-2004318072" to="-2004318072"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reset to factory configuration and removed the Z-Wave network.</lang></description></value><value from="-2013265920" to="-2013265920"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reset Configuration parameter to default value.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17055601"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
