<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="029F"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17075679</certNumber><rfFrequency>South Korea</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">AMADAS Smart Lock is a truly user-centric connected smart lever lock offering all-in-one solution including left/right handed lever, keypads, unique App, wire-free and a solar panel in a solid stainless steel casing. AMADAS Smart Lock offers D.I.Y. installation. There is no need to call a professional installer. Users can install it by themselves without any professional technique. Also, it works for 100% of the time even when the batteries run out. AMADAS can be powered by shining a smart phone flash light on the built-in solar panel for 20 seconds. AMADAS Smart Lock connects to user's smartphone. For better security, users can check door lock condition, access log, etc., via its unique app whenever or wherever they are. With its high compatibility, AMADAS Smart Lock can be installed on the most comprehensive standard doors regardless of a thickness, material and in/outdoor. Made for both tech-savvy and non tech-savvy users, they can easily enter their homes via Smartphone or the button (Touch/Push) configuration on AMADAS' lever, whichever way is most convenient.</lang></description><productName>AMADAS Smart Lock</productName><brandName>AMADAS</brandName><productCode>ADSL-1001</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Supported Command Classes (14):- Z-Wave plus info (V2) - Manufacturer specific (V2) - Security (V1) - Device reset Locally (V1) - Battery (V1) - Power level (V1) - Version(V2) - Door Lock (V2) - User Code (V1) - Association (V2) - Association Group Info (V1) - Notification (V4) - Configuration (V1) - Firmware update meta data (V2)</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">set door open notification On or Off</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">if configuration value is 0x01 then set door open notification onand configuration value is 0xFE then set door open notification off</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">set door open notification on</lang></description></value><value from="254" to="254"><description><lang xml:lang="en">set door open notification off</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17075679"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
