<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="017F"/><productType value="0101"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17075686</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Wink Motion Sensor is a Z-Wave Plus battery-powered device that senses motion in your home, helping you monitor activity around your home to keep your family safe. When motion is detected, your sensor will blink with a blue LED indicator and your Wink Hub or other Z-Wave Plus certified hub can send an alert to your smartphone, set off an alarm or chime, or trigger an automation such as turning on your lights. This sensor has flexible mounting options, convenient for multi surface installation on wall, ceiling, shelf or tabletop. The sensor body design with magnetic cradle and angled facet offers easy line-of-sight perspective of the area you wish to monitor, with an extra-wide 110 coverage area, and uses a spherical magnet to hold the sensor body in place, so that it can point in any direction. The Wink Motion Sensor offers an extra-long z-wave wireless range of up to 150 feet, and requires a Wink Hub or other Z-Wave Plus certified hub for operation. The Motion Sensor comes with a CR123A 3.0V battery and has a three-year battery life, and will send an alert to your smartphone when the device has low battery. Z-Wave Plus CertifiedRequires a Z-Wave Plus Certified Hub to operateWorks with all Z-Wave Plus compatible networksFlexible Mounting Options110 Extra-Wide Coverage AreaUp to 150 feet rangeThree-Year Battery Life (CR123A Battery included)Low Battery IndicationMeasurements in millimeters: 45 x 45 x 56.2 mm (combined depth of mount and sensor)</lang></description><productName>Wink Motion Sensor</productName><brandName>Wink</brandName><productCode>Wink Motion Sensor</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 is the Lifeline group, which can hold five devices.The Motion Detector sends this group a Notification Report and Binary Sensor Report whenever motion is detected and when it stops.It also sends a Multilevel Sensor Report incrementally based on time (see Param 7,) or when a relative change in light level is detected (see Param 9.)Finally, the Motion Detector sends this group Battery Reports and a Device Reset Locally notification to remove itself from the Z-Wave network.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Motion Detector sends a BASIC_SET command to Association Group 2 to directly trigger devices (like a siren, chime, etc.) when motion is detected and when it stops.Optionally, the Motion Detector can be set to only send this when ambient light levels fall below a predetermined level (see Configuration Parameters 5 and 8.)See Configuration Parameters 2, 3, 5, and 8 for more details regarding Association Group 2.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 3 supports up to 5 members and the Motion Detector sends it a NOTIFICATION_REPORT when motion is detected and when it stops.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 4 supports up to 5 members and the Motion Detector sends it a SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT when motion is detected and when it stops.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Sensitivity Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the sensitivity of the Motion Detector. It is a unitless parameter ranging in values from 8 up to 255, with 8 being the highest sensitivity level and 255 being the lowest.After physical installation, make sure the farthest part of the coverage area is still visible to theMotion Detector by adjusting this parameter.</lang></description><value from="8" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Sensitivity Level</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable LED INDICATOR</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If this parameter is enabled, the LED INDICATOR will flash everytime there motion is detected.If this is disabled, the LED INDICATOR will not flash to indicate motion events.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED Disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED Enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Motion Cleared Time Delay</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameters sets the amount of time after a motion event before the Motion Detector reports no activity to the main controller (see Notification and Binary Sensor command classes on page 14-15 for more information.)This also sets the amount of time before a BASIC_SET(00) command is sent to Association Group 2 to turn off any activated devices.This value must be higher than the value of Parameter 6, and if this parameter is reset to default settings, Parameter 6 will also be reset.See Group 2 on page 14 for more information.</lang></description><value from="5" to="600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">In Seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the value sent by the BASIC_SET command to Association Group 2 (for more information, see Group 2 on page 14.)</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn Off</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dim Level</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">On</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable Motion Detection</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This setting enables or disables motion detection.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Motion Detection Disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Motion Detection Enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="2" default="100" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 Ambient Light Threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If Parameter 8 is enabled, this setting sets the light level below which the Motion Detector will send BASIC_SET commands to Association Group 2 when motion is detected.For more information, seeGroup 2 on page 14.</lang></description><value from="5" to="1000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Lux</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="8" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Retrigger Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">After each motion event, the Motion Detector is disabled for the amount of time set by this parameter before it can send out another Motion Detected Notification Report/Binary Sensor Report.This value must be lower than the value of Parameter 2, and if this parameter is reset to default settings, Parameter 2 will also be reset.</lang></description><value from="1" to="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="2" default="180" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Light Sensing Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the amount of time between each successive ambient light level reading that is sent.This value must be less than the Wakeup Interval Time (which is 43,200 seconds or 12 hours by default.)</lang></description><value from="60" to="3600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable Group 2 Ambient Light Threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If this parameter is enabled, the Motion Detector will only send Basic Set commands to Associon Group 2 if the ambient light level is below the value set in Parameter 05.For more information, see Group 2 on page 14.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 Ambient Light Threshold Disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 Ambient Light Threshold Enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="100" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Ambient Light Sensitivity Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This Parameter sets the minimum change in ambient light level (in lux) the Motion Detector must detect before a Multilevel Sensor Report is sent to the main controller.</lang></description><value from="0" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in Lux</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17075686"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
