<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="017F"/><productType value="0100"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17075685</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Wink Door/Window Sensor is a Z-Wave Plus battery-powered device that detects when a door, window, or cabinet is opened and closed in your home, helping you monitor activity around your home to keep your family safe. Works with exterior and interior doors, garage doors, patio doors, windows, cabinets, drawers, and other openings. When your sensor detects activity, your Wink Hub or other Z-Wave Plus certified hub can send an alert to your smartphone, set off an alarm or chime, or trigger an automation such as turning on your lights. The Wink Door/Window Sensor offers an extra-long z-wave wireless range of up to 150 feet, and requires a Wink Hub or other Z-Wave Plus certified hub for operation. The Wink Door/Window sensor comes with a CR14250 battery and has a three-year battery life, and will send an alert to your smartphone via the hub when the device has low battery. Z-Wave Plus CertifiedRequires a Z-Wave Plus Certified Hub to operateWorks with all Z-Wave Plus compatible networksUp to 150 feet rangeThree-Year Battery Life (CR14250 Battery included)Low Battery IndicationMeasurements in millimeters: 19 x 66.3 x 20.2 mm (sensor) and 10 x 39.55 x 10.5 mm (magnet)</lang></description><productName>Wink Door/Window Sensor</productName><brandName>Wink</brandName><productCode>Wink D/W Sensor</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 is the Lifeline group, which can hold five members, typically including the main Z-Wave controller. The Door/Window Sensor sends this group a Notification Report and a Binary Sensor Report when it is opened or closed. It also sends this group a Battery Report in response to Battery Get commands.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Door/Window Sensor sends a Basic Set command to association Group 2 (or the Control Group) to directly trigger devices (like a light, chime, etc.) in response to events. Then, after a preset delay, a BASIC_SET(0x00) command is sent to reset the device (e.g. turn off the light.) The value of the Basic Set command (e.g. brightness of the lamp,) and the delay time before the BASIC_SET(0x00) is sent is configured using configuration parameters 1 and 2 respectively.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 3 supports up to 5 members and the Door/Window Sensor sends it a NOTIFICATION_REPORT when the door either opens or closes.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 4 supports up to 5 members and the Door/Window Sensor sends it a SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT when the door either opens or closes.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">BASIC_SET Off Delay</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the delay time from when the Door/Window Sensor sends the BASIC_SET command to Association Group 2 and when the BASIC_SET(0) is sent. It accepts a value up to 65535, in seconds.</lang></description><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="99" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">BASIC_SET Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the value sent by the BASIC_SET command to Association Group 2 (for more information, see Association Groups.)</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Off/Cancel Alarm/Etc.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dim Level (for Multilevel Switch)</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">On (for Binary Switch)</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17075685"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
