<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0300"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0012"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17075683</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Our RGBW bulb has three functional categories: Good, Better and Best. Good is your basic On, Off and Dim. Using your app and controller/gateway, you can turn your lights on, off and dim them down to 5% brightness from anywhere in the world, using your smartphone. At 2700K and 800 lumens, it is a true 60W equivalent. At Better, this is where the innovative technology takes over. You get your basic On, Off and Dim, but now you have the ability to tune the white color from a warm 1800K to a cool 6500K. The ability to tune the white is what we call Tunable White, or TW. The last functional category is Best. With Best, not only do you get On, Off, Dim, and Tunable White, but now we add the colors of Red, Green and Blue. This lighting is what we call RGBW. With LeedarsonsRGBW bulbs, you will get full, saturated colors that are true Reds, true Greens and true Blues. Having this capability allows combinations of 16 Million colors. With all of our lighting, and the app that supports it, you can group lights together, set different lighting scenes for different groups and set schdules to autotmatically turns lights, and groups, on and off. Automatically turning your lights on and off when youre away, gives the impression you are actually home and this will help deter unwanted entry.</lang></description><productName>A60 LED BULB RGBW</productName><brandName>LEEDARSON</brandName><productCode>6VA-A806ST-Q1G</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">get the temperature of NTC.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">It was used to get the temperature of NTC.</lang></description><value from="0" to="-1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">It was used to get the temperature of NTC.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="255" size="4" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">reset</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reset to factory configuration and removed the Z-Wave network.Reset Configuration parameter to default value.</lang></description><value from="-2004318072" to="-2004318072"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reset to factory configuration and removed the Z-Wave network.</lang></description></value><value from="-2013265920" to="-2013265920"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reset Configuration parameter to default value.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17075683"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
