<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0085"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="0011"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17075693</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">FAKRO ZWS12 chain motor thanks to their small dimensions and suitable force output are ideal for roof window operating, being fully compatible with the Z-Wave Plus system. The motors can be applied in both centre pivot and top hung and pivot roof windows as well as windows of non-standard dimensions. The chain has 2 output speed and reach 24cm. The ZWS12 motor is equipped with encoder and two limit switches:limit switch at maximum chain travel position,overload limit in both directions (used mainly when closing the window).This product can be operated in any Z-Wave network with other Z-Wave certified devices from other manufacturers.ZWS12 also can be controlledmanuallyby button and closed by rain sensor and timer.There are four association groups in actuator ZWS12:Life Linegroup for position reporting actuator after each a stoppage and alarm reportingBasic Repeatgroup used to transfer the received basic commands to the devices included in this group.Multilevel Repeatgroup used to transfer the received multilevel commands to the devices included in this group. Basic Raingroup used to transfer the received commands from actuator &amp; rain detector to the devices included in this group. Z-Wave Plus Secure Enabled ProductThis device is a security enabled Z-Wave Plus product that is able to use encrypted Z-Wave Plus messages to communicate to other security enabled Z-Wave Plus products.Technical Parameters: Chain reach: 240 mmOutput power : 9 WRated current: 0.72 AStandby current: 0.03 AChain pushing force: 200 NClosing force: 200 NCurrent limit: YESPower voltage: 15V DCPower cable: 2 x 0.75 mm2 (0,4 m)</lang></description><productName>Chain actuator - window opener</productName><brandName>FAKRO</brandName><productCode>ZWS12</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Life Linegroup for position reporting actuator after each a stoppage and alarm reporting (overcurrent, damage encoders).This group can be a maximum 1 device.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Repeatgroup used to transfer the received basic commands to the devices included in this group. This group can be amaximum 5 devices.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multilevel Repeatgroup used to transfer the received multilevel commands to the devices included in this group. Thisgroup can be a maximum 5 devices.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Raingroup used to transfer the received commands from actuator &amp; rain detector to the devices included in thisgroup. This group can be a maximum 5 devices.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="12" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Callibrate</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter on/off callibration function</lang></description><value from="1" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1- calibrated,2discalibrated</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="13" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Last saved position</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter set servomotor in previous position after using Basic Mode operation</lang></description><value from="1" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1FF go to Max, 2FF go to previous position</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="15" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Close after time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter closeservomotor after set time. The time is counting in minutes</lang></description><value from="0" to="120"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0-120 minutes</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="2" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Motor speed I</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter change motor speed</lang></description><value from="1" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1- the lowest speed, 4 - the higest speed, 2- default</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="2" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Motor speed II (rain sensor)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter change motor speed when rain sensor turned on servomotor</lang></description><value from="1" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1- the lowest speed, 4 - the higest speed, 2- default</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17075693"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
