<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0285"/><productType value="0201"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17085728</certNumber><rfFrequency>Israel</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The CTS-iCPE is a Gateway Controller. It is based on a managed layer-2 switch with full Z-Wave controller functionality added. As such it is unique at launch.The CTS-iCPE is positioned as an open, secure and high quality product. It is meant to be used as a professional and operationally secure gateway for carrier class IoT services.This CTS-iCPE is ideally positioned to support open multi-service networks and providers. Typical services address eHealth/Homecare, Real estate, Individual metering, Sustainability/Eco systems, Security as well as Home automation and Smart home solutions.The CTS-iCPE operates with any and all Z-Wave sensors and actuators available. However,this will not be enough for creating a winning value proposition. The true value will be delivered to the market based on so-called open service platforms. Service Mediators using such open platforms have started to enter the market with scalable delivery of innovative applications and operational services to the end-users.A summary of the necessary layers towards full market solutions: Gateway: Professional and secure CTS-iCPE Secure Z-Wave sensors and actuators Open multi-service solution platforms Independent Communication operators Easy integration for delivery from service specific operational market players (i.e. Security companies; eHealth solutions, Utility Cos etc.)All basic functions for proper use of the CTS-iCPE are handled in the basic User Manual. More in-depth instructions for service platform owners and service mediators can be obtained at:cts_fae@ctsystem.com</lang></description><productName>iCPE</productName><brandName>CTS</brandName><productCode>iCPE</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17085728"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
