<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0266"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0320"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17085748</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Door sensor is an intelligent security equipment that can transmit the Z-Wave network which has particular frequency. In the Z-Wave network communications, door sensor can be connected to any Z-Wave main controller (ex, SiterOne tablet). The door sensor can send messages to the Z-Wave main controller, and realize association with other devices through the Z-Wave main controller. Different countries or areas, the radio frequency is different. In the communication with the Z-Wave main controller, the door sensor can send messages to the Z-Wave main controller, but it cannot receive messages from the Z-Wave main controller. When alarm is triggered, the door sensor sends messages to the Z-Wave main controller, the Z-Wave main controller will displays the current status of door sensor, so the door sensor can associate with other devices. Door sensor is battery powered, is small and can be installed on the window or door easily. When the door or window is open, the door sensor is triggered and linkage alarm realized. </lang></description><productName>Siterwell Door Sensor</productName><brandName>Siterwell Technology</brandName><productCode>STW-W3320WU</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">is lifeline service that assigned to Sensor (Door/Window detector) statusOpen/Close. It enables the sensor to send reports and readings to Z-Wave Controller or Z-Wave Gateway whenever the sensor is triggered. This Group Support:NOTIFICATION_REPORT BATTERY_REPORT SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT DEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">allows for sending control commands to associated devices such as relay module, lighting, etc. This association group is configured through the advanced parameters no. 1 and 2. This Group Support:BASIC_SET.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">allows for Send Notification to associated devices in this group. This Group Support:NOTIFICATION_REPORT</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">allows for Send Notification to associated devices in this group. This Group Support:SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">On/Off Duration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter that can be used to adjust the amount of delay before the OFF command is transmitted. This parameter can be configured with the value of 0 through 65535, where 0 means send OFF command immediately and 65535 means 65535 seconds of delay.</lang></description><value from="0" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">inseconds,each1s</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Command will be sent where contains a value when the door/window is opened or closed, the receiver will take it for consideration; for instance, if a lamp module is received the Basic Set Command of which value is decisive as to how bright of dim level of lamp module shall be.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">OFF, Alarm cancelling or turning a device off</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ON (Binary Switch Device) Dim Level (Multilevel Switch Device)</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ON (Binary Switch Device) Dim Level (Multilevel Switch Device)</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17085748"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
