<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0266"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0350"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17085749</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">This product can be included and operated in any ZWave network with other ZWave certified devices from other manufacturers and/or other applications. All nonbattery operated nodes within the network will act as repeaters regardless of vendor to increase reliability of the network.In the front casing, there is button that is used to carry out include, exclude or reset factory default settings on PCB Board.When power is first supplied, the LED will flash on and off with yellow alternately every 1 second intervals within 5 seconds if the detector has not been added a ZWave network, otherwise the LED will flash on and off 5 times with cyan alternately every 300 millisecond. Please get familiar with the terms below before starting the operations.This Plug has function that remembers the relay states, the plug will turn on after power up next time if the plug is turn on before the power cutoff.</lang></description><productName>Siterwell Power plug Sensor</productName><brandName>Siterwell Technology</brandName><productCode>STW-W3350WU</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">GROUP 1 is lifeline service that assigned to plug statusON/OFF. It enables the Plug to send reports and readings to ZWave Controller or ZWave Gateway. This Group Support:NOTIFICATION_REPORT_V4 METER_REPORT_V4 SWITCH_BINARY_REPORT DEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">GROUP 2 allows for sending control commands to associated devices such as Siren, relay module, lighting, etc. If current load is over the max current defined in parameter #3, the Plug will send a BASIC_SET (0xFF) to associated devices. When current load is normal, plug will send a BASIC_SET (0x00) to associated devices. This Group Support:BASIC_SET</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">GROUP 3 allows for Send Notification to associated devices in this group. This Group Support: NOTIFICATION_REPORT_V4</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Meter Report Enable</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines Disable/Enable meter report measure data to controller.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable Report</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enable Report</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable Button On/Off</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the button on/off function is enabled or not on the top of the wall plug. This parameter can be configured 0 and 1. If this parameter is set to 1, users can turn on and off the wall plug by pressing the button on the top of the wall plug. If this parameter is set to 0, the wall plug cannot be turned on and off by pressing the button.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="300" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Set Report Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines interval time (in seconds) that Meter report data to main controller.</lang></description><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">s</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="13" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Set the upper current threshold.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines maximum current the plug can provide to load that be connected to plug. If the current consumed by load is greater than maximum current, the plug will cut off power, and send NOTIFICATION_EVENT_POWER_MANAGEMENT_OVER_LOAD_DETECTED to associated devices in lifeline. Red Led will blink every seconds until current is normal (less than Parameter #3). You must remove the loader and turn on the Plug (press the button once) to enable current monitor and clear NOTIFICATION ALARM.This parameter value must be great than #4. If user set this parameter to default by Configure CC, the parameter #4 will be set to default value.</lang></description><value from="1" to="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Ampere</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="12" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Set Alarm upper current threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines maximum current, if the current plug provide to load is great than this parameter, the plug will light yellow LED, but plug cannot cutoff power.This parameter value must be less than parameter #3. If user set this parameter to default by Configure CC, the parameter #3 will be set to default value.</lang></description><value from="1" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Ampere</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED Enable/Disable</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the LED indication Function ON/OFF. This parameter can be configured with 0 or 1, where 0 means disable LED indication Function and will always be turnoff, and 1 means enable LED Function.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="5" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Meter Reporting Setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines by how much current changed must change to be reported to the ZWave Controller or ZWave Gateway, in percents. If the rate of current change ratio is greater than this parameter, the plug will report the results, voltage, current, power and energy, that plug measure to ZWave Controller or ZWave Gateway.</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">%</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Remember Relay Status</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defined the relay status if remember or not. If remembered, the plug will restore the relay status last power off when the plug supply power next time.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dont Remember, the relay will keep OFF when Plug Supply Power</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">emember the Relay Status.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Time switch Configure</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the timer function Enable/Disable. This parameter can be configured with 0 or 1, where 0 means disable time switch function and 1 enable. The time period will be defined in parameter #9.If this parameter is Set to 1, and when turn the plug relay on, the timer in plug start run with time period defined in parameter #9 and the plug will turn the relay off.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Time switch Disable</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Time switch Enable</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="2" default="150" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Time switch Configure</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the time period that plug time switch off. This parameter can be configured 1 ~ 65535(in minutes). If Parameter #9 is set to 1, and relay is turnon, the relay will be turnoff after delay this parameter.</lang></description><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">minutes</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17085749"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
