<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="004F"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0015"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17095779</certNumber><rfFrequency>Brazil</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The in-wall Roller Shutter Controller is designed to switch rise/lower roller shutter connected to its terminals using radio waves, controllers and a push button directly connected to this Roller Controller. This in-wall Roller Shutter Controller is a transceiver which is a Z-Wave Plus TM enabled device and is fully compatible with any Z-Wave TMenabled network. Slim design let the Controller can easily hide itself into the wall box and that will be good for the house decoration.The new smart relay calibration technology can reduce the inrush current caused by the load and let the module work perfectly with many kind of Roller Shutter. This in-wall Roller Shutter Controller is able to detect position of the Shutter by using the patterned power measuring method, so it can be remote controlled not only fully up or down, but also can be adjusted to ex. 30% or 50%. And when manual controlled by push button, the controller also can memorize the position and send the new shutter position to its controller (ex. IP-Gateway).Adding to Z-Wave TMNetworkIn the front casing, there is an include button with LED indicator below which is used to carry out inclusion, exclusion, reset or association. When first power is applied, its LED flashes on and off alternately and repeatedly at 0.5 second intervals. It implies that it has not been assigned a node ID and start auto inclusion. Auto InclusionThe function of auto inclusion will be executed as long as the FXS-M08 does not have Node ID and just connect the FXS-M08 to main power.Note: Auto inclusion timeout is 2 minute during which the node information of explorer frame will be emitted once every several seconds. Unlike inclusionfunction as shown in the table below, the execution of auto inclusion is free from pressing the Include button on the FXS-M08. </lang></description><productName>Micro-Smart Module for AC Motors</productName><brandName>FLEX AUTOMATION</brandName><productCode>FXS-M08</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="720" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Watt Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If the setting is configured for 1hour (set value =720), the FXS-M08 will report its instant power consumption every 1 hour to the node of Group 1. The maximum interval to report its instant power consumption is 45 hours (5s*32767/3600=45hr). Default value is 1 hour. </lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">5*720s=3600s=1 hour</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="6" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">KWH Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If the setting is configured for 1hour (set value =6), the FXS-M08 will report its Accumulated Power Consumption (KWh) every 1 hour to the node of correspond Group. The maximum interval to report its Accumulated Power Consumption (KWh) is 227.55 days (10min*32767/1440=227.55 days). Default value=1 hour. </lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">6*10min= 1 hour </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="2" default="500" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of current for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the current of load over the preset threshold value, if the setting value is 500, when the load current of Relay1 over this value, FXS-M08 will send current meter report to warn the Group1 node, the Range of the setting value is from 10 to 500, and the default value is 500.</lang></description><value from="10" to="500"><description><lang xml:lang="en">500*0.01A=5A</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="2" default="10000" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of KWH for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the KWh of load over the preset threshold value, If the setting value is 10000, when the Accumulated Power Consumption of Relay1 or Relay2 over this value, FXS-M08 will send KWh Meter Report command to the node of correspond Group, minimum value is 1KWh and default value is 10000 kWh.</lang></description><value from="1" to="10000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">10000 * 1KWh = 10000 KWh</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="2" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">External switch type</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">1. One Push ButtonWhen the configuration setting is One Push Button, only S1 input will be valid. The control moving commands can be accepted in this switch type while the shutter is moving. In this switch type, the inclusion/exclusion/reset/association function can also be fulfilled by pressing S1 just like the operation of include button.When S1 is short pressed, the shutter will move up toward TOP(0x63). While in this moving S1 is short pressed again, the shutter will stop moving. A third short pressing of S1 will move the shutter down toward BOTTOM(0x00). While in this moving S1 is short pressed again, the shutter will stop moving. And so on Inverting direction and stopping. 2. Two Push Button (The default setting is Two Push Button (2)) If this setting is configured as Two Push Button, S1 and S2 input will be valid, but will not accept pressing S1and S2 at the same time. In this switch type, the inclusion/exclusion/reset/association function can also be fulfilled by pressing S1 or S2 just like the operation of include button. When S1 is pressed and hold more than 1.5 seconds, the shutter will move up toward TOP(0x63), and the shutter will stop moving when S1 is released. When S2 is pressed and hold more than 1.5 seconds, the shutter will move down toward BOTTOM(0x00), and the shutter will stop moving when S2 is released. When S1 is short pressed, the shutter will move up toward TOP(0x63). While in this moving short pressed S1 again, the shutter just keep moving up toward TOP(0x63). The easy way to stop this moving is short pressing S2. When S2 is short pressed, the shutter will move down toward BOTTON(0x00). While in this moving short pressed S2 again, the shutter just keep moving down toward BOTTON(0x00). The easy way to stop this moving is short pressing S1.When in Two Push Button switch type, S1 or S2 are pressed and not released, and FXS-M08 receive any control moving command from Z-Wave RF (Ex. BASIC_SETBINARY_SWITCH_SETMULTILEVEL_SWITCH_SETMULTILEVEL_SWITCH_START_LEVEL_CHANGE or MULTILEVEL_SWITCH_STOP_LEVEL_CHANGE or SCENE_ACTIVATION_SET), FXS-M08 wont do any change in position but report alarm to Group1 (Alarm_Type=1, Alarm_level =0xFF), this indicate that the S1 or S2 not been release. ATT. : For avoid misunderstanding that RF command dose not work, it is recommended to check the status of S1 and S2. </lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1: One Push button</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2:Two Push button</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="2" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Level report mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Mode 1 : In 5 seconds period after controlled by a moving command, it will report the destination level when received request command. Out of the 5 seconds period, it will report the actual level of the shutter when received request command. Mode 2 : Whenever the shutter move pass a 10 percent level, it will auto report the level to Group 1 node.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1:Report destination level in 5s</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2:Report 10 percent level while running</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17095779"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
