<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0266"/><productType value="0007"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17095782</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Heat alarm is an alarm device that can give off warning under the condition that the environmental temperature between 54-70the abnormal temperature may caused by an actual fire, in order to alert the dwelling of the dangerous situation and notice them to evacuate right away. At the same time in this alarm state if the alarms have been matched Smart home or other Z-Wave system, they will send a warning message to the main controller in this network group. The heat alarm can be included and operated in any Z-Wave network with other Z-Wave certified devices from other manufacturers under the same radio frequency. It is the point that only under same radio frequency the heat alarm can be included and operated. All non-battery operated alarms within the network will act as repeaters, as to increase reliability of the network. In the Z-Wave network communication, the heat alarm can communicate with other devices associated. Through the Z-Wave network controller, you can get the status of the alarm, such as battery level.</lang></description><productName>Heat Alarm</productName><brandName>siterwell</brandName><productCode>GS412B</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Linkage group 2 is assigned to the devices status - sending BASIC SET control frame to the associated devices having detected the heat alarm.This heat alarm will send a BASIC SET(0xFF) message to associated group, when pressing test button to check the function; and this heat alarm will also send a BASIC SET(0x00) message to associated group, when quiting the test button. This heat alarm will send a BASIC SET(0xFF) message to associated group, when the heat alarm is overheat alarm; and this heat alarm will also send a BASIC SET(0x00) message to associated group, when theoverheat alarm is cleared.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Linkage group 3 reports the detection's status to the associated device. heat alarm.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17095782"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
