<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0085"/><productType value="0005"/><productId value="0011"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17105794</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">FAKRO AMZ Z-Wave Electric awning blind is an appropriate combination of effective protection from heat and comfort of use. Due to the fact that the awning blind absorbs solar radiation before it reaches the glazing and emits the heat to the outside of the room, it constitutes much better protectction from tiresome heat in the sunny days than internal accessories. At the same time, it allows the ingress of natural light and ensures visual contact with the environment. FAKROAMZ Z-Wave electrically is controlled by remote control or by wall switch in wireless system Z-Wave. In an emergency, the awning blind can be controlled by service button located on the awning blind. The awning blind is powered by 15VDC. Motor nominal current is 1.4A. The AMZ Z-Wave awning blind has three extremes: - Maximum extension (encoder maximum position)- Completely rolled up (encoder minimum position)- Current limiting protecting awning blind against damage and user against accidental injury resulting from the contact with moving elements of awning blind.There are three association groups in awning blindFAKRO AMZ Z-Wave:- Life Linegroup for position reporting awning blind after each a stoppage and alarm reporting (overcurrent, damage encoders). This group can be a maximum 1 device.- Basic Repeatgroup used to transfer the received basic commands to the devices included in this group. This group can be a maximum 5 devices. - Multilevel Repeatgroup used to transfer the received multilevel commands to the devices included in this group. This group can be a maximum 5 devices.Technical Parameters: Power voltage: 15V DCRated current: 1,4 ACurrent limit: YESSpeed: 13 r.p.mTemperature of usage: (-10oC) do (65oC)Supplying cable: 2 x 0,75 mm2</lang></description><productName>AMZ Z-Wave</productName><brandName>FAKRO</brandName><productCode>AMZ</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Life Linegroup for position reporting awning blind after each a stoppage and alarm reporting (overcurrent, damage encoders)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Repeatgroup used to transfer the received basic commands to the devices included in this group.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multilevel Repeatgroup used to transfer the received multilevel commands to the devices included in this group.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="12" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Remote Calibration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to the remotly calibration of AMZ Z-Wave via gateway or remote control with a display, e.g. FAKRO ZRS24Value 1calibratedValue 2discalibratedto enter the calibration mode must first time discalibrate and then calibrate</lang></description><value from="1" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1calibrated;2 - discalibratedto enter the calibration mode must first time discalibrate and then calibrate</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="13" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Go to position</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">1FF go to maximum position2FF go to previous position</lang></description><value from="1" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1go to maximum position; 2go to previous position</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17105794"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
