<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0301"/><productType value="0048"/><productId value="010F"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17115826</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Wireless Energy Meter (WEM) is a smart device that performs quasi real-time measurements of the electricity consumption of the home by continuously monitoring the power line.WEM will be installed into the main distribution board, with the amperometric clamp closed around the live wire of a 1-phase system. This allows WEM to measure the line voltage and current, and thus compute the total power and energy consumption of the home.After a simple configuration phase, WEM starts reporting the measurement it takes to a central controller device, such as a home gateway, by means of the Z-Wave wireless technology. Z-Wave is a widespread and interoperable wireless home control technology based on the ITU-T 9959 open standard.WEM has an intuitive user interface, with a LED informing the user about its current state, and a push button to let the user issue the necessary commands. WEM can measure and report the following physical dimensions: Total Accumulated Active Energy (Wh), Instantaneous Active Power (W), RMS Voltage (V), RMS Current (A).WEM allows to fine-tune the way the measurements are performed and reported by means of several parameters, which can be set by most controllers on the market.</lang></description><productName>Wireless Energy Meter</productName><brandName>Seco srl</brandName><productCode>SYS-72027-ENL/01</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus LifelineWEM uses the Lifeline association group to send the following commands:Time Parameters Get,Configuration Report,Meter Report,Meter Table Current Data Report,Meter Table Historical Data Report,Device Reset Locally Notification.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="10" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Avg_Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Avg_Period determines the time window used to compute an average over the line readings. Each unit of Avg_Period is worth 5 seconds. If Avg_Period = 0 no average is computed and the last sample is returned. Note that the maximum average window coincides with the minimum value of Max_Rep_Interval. Also note that a delay of up to the average window can be introduced in returning the measurements (each measurement is returned only when ready).</lang></description><value from="0" to="6"><description><lang xml:lang="en">seconds x 5</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Meas_Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Meas_Period is the unit period for computing a measurement. WEM checks for changes in the line measures every Meas_Period. If there are meaningful changes, a report is sent to the controller. Therefore Meas_Period also represents represents the minimum reporting interval, i.e. 1/Meas_Period is the maximum reporting frequency. </lang></description><value from="30" to="120"><description><lang xml:lang="en">seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="6" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Max_Rep_Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Max_Rep_Interval is the maximum time that can elapse without sending a report. If no meaningful events occur, WEM sends one full measurement every Max_Rep_Interval seconds.</lang></description><value from="3" to="60"><description><lang xml:lang="en">seconds x 10</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="4" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Res_Active_Power</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Res_Active_Power is the minimum quantity (resolution) that triggers a report for active power. It can be used to tune the sensitivity of WEM to changes in this physical dimension.</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Watt</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="2" default="10" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Res_RMS_Voltage</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Res_RMS_Voltage is the minimum quantity (resolution) that triggers a report for active power. It can be used to tune the sensitivity of WEM to changes in this physical dimension.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Volt x 0.1</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="2" default="10" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Res_RMS_Current</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Res_RMS_Current is the minimum quantity (resolution) that triggers a report for active power. It can be used to tune the sensitivity of WEM to changes in this physical dimension.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Ampere x 0.01</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="255" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Clamp_reversed</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Clamp_Reversed is a read-only parameter that the controller can query to learn about the current placement of the clamp. During the measurement phase, WEM checks whether the clamp has been placed correctly or reversed (with regard to phase rotation). In the latter case, WEM notifies the user with a different blink pattern and stores this information into the Clamp_Reversed parameter. The clamp is placed correctly if Clamp_Reversed = 0 and is reversed if Clamp_Reversed = 1. If Clamp_Reversed = 0xFF a fault occurred and it was not possible to detect the clamp position.</lang></description><value from="0" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">only 0,1, 255 (0xFF) are valid</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable_CRC16</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enable_CRC16 provides for an extra layer of redundancy in order to protect low bit rate transmissions against radio channel errors. This applies to the reports and frames sent spontaneous by WEM. Requests from the controller are always answered as asked. WEM will send CRC16 encapsulated frames to the associated node if this has proved to support it and Enable_CRC16 is set to 1. Otherwise, reports will be sent with no extra CRC16 encapsulation.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17115826"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
