<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0331"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="1D04"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17105818</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">4 in 1multi sensor,Function includes Motion detected, Door/window detected, Tampering detected, Ambient light intensity /temperature measured.</lang></description><productName>4 in 1 multi sensor </productName><brandName>WINKA SYSIT</brandName><productCode>WK-0002</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lifeline group, Support Command List as below:COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATION, NOTIFICATION_REPORTCOMMAND_CLASS_SENSOR_MULTILEVEL, SENSOR_MULTILEVEL_REPORTCOMMAND_CLASS_SENSOR_BINARY, SENSOR_BINARY_REPORTCOMMAND_CLASS_BATTERY, BATTERY_REPORTCOMMAND_CLASS_DEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY, DEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">control group, the preset event is occured, sensor will send BASIC_SET command to the devices that associated in this group. Support Command List as Below:COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC, BASIC_SET</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">This group is for motion event report to devices that associated in this group. Support Command List as Below:COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATION,NOTIFICATION_REPORT (Home Security)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">This group is for Door/Window Open and close event report to devices that associated in this group. Support Command List as Below:COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATION, NOTIFICATION_REPORT (Access Control)</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="4" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">1)Sensitivity setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is to set the detection sensitivity of the motion sensor. The smaller the value is and the higher the detection sensitivity is, the farther the detection range of the sensor is.</lang></description><value from="0" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 is Max Sensitivity, 99 is Min Sensitivity</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="2" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Delay time of clear the motion event</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The time set by this parameter refers to: The duration from the time when the sensor detects the motion event to the time when the sensor completes the removal of the motion event alarm. If during this period, the sensor detects the occurrence of another motion event, the timer will start counting again.When the sensor removes the motion event alarm, the sensor will also send BASIC_SET(0x00) command to all devices in Connection Group 2.</lang></description><value from="0" to="4095"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Motion event clear time delay</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="11" size="2" default="50" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Setting of light intensity value report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the conditions of the sensor detecting the environment brightness value and reporting it to the host. If the absolute value of the difference between the currently measured environment brightness value and that measured last time is greater than the value set by this parameter, the sensor will report the currently measured environment brightness value to the host, or otherwise the value will not be reported. In theory, the smaller the value is, the shorter the batterys life is.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">lux, the Differential value for Luminance Report.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="12" size="2" default="50" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Setting of light intensity threshold in the night</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The values set by this parameter should make it clear whether the current time is night or daytime. If the currently measured environment brightness is greater than the set value of this parameter, it means that it is daytime currently; otherwise it is in the evening.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">If the Light Intensity Value is less than this value, it will be considered to night.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="13" size="1" default="5" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Setting of temperature value report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the conditions of reporting the environmental temperature value currently measured by the temperature sensor to the host. If the absolute value of the difference between the currently measured environmental temperature value and that reported last time is greater than the value represented by the setting of this parameter, the sensor will report the currently measured environmental temperature value to the host, or otherwise the value will not be reported. In theory, the smaller the value is, the shorter the batterys life is.Each value represents 0.1 Celsius degree. For example, if the default value is set as '5', then the temperature represented is 5 * 0.1 = 0.5 Celsius degree; It means that when the difference between the current temperature and the temperature reported last time is greater than 0.5 Celsius degree, the current temperature value will be reported to the host.</lang></description><value from="0" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Differential value for Temperature Report. (0.1 Celsius)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="14" size="1" default="3" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Interval of the sensors measured setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the measurement interval of the optical sensor. The greater the set value of this parameter is, the longer the battery life is and the less frequently the brightness is reported to the host when Parameter 10 is met; The smaller the set value of the parameter is, the shorter the battery life will be accordingly and the more the brightness data reported to the host with Parameter 10 being met is. Unit: min</lang></description><value from="1" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">minute. the time interval for Sensor measurment</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="15" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Setting of the trigger source for controlled the associated devices</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets to control connected devices in Group 2 by selecting a certain trigger event supported by the device.0 None of the following events will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices.1 When detecting a motion event (Motion), it will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices2 When detecting the doors or windows being opened (Open), it will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices3 When detecting the device being dismantled (Tamper), it will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices4 When the brightness is lower than the threshold set in 16, it will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices5 When the brightness is lower than the threshold set in 17, it will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices6 When the temperature is lower than the threshold set in 18, it will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices7 When the temperature is lower than the threshold set in 19, it will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices 8 When Conditions 1 ~ 3 are met, it will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices 9 When Conditions 4 ~ 5 are met, it will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices10 When Conditions 6 ~ 7 are met, it will trigger BASIC_SET command to control the connected devices</lang></description><value from="0" to="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Trigger source number for BASIC_SET Command</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="16" size="2" default="50" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Low light intensity threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">When the environment brightness value is lower than the value set by this parameter, if the trigger source set by Parameter 15 is low brightness threshold alarm, the sensor will trigger BASIC_SET to control all connected devices in Connection Group 2.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lux. Low threshold value for light intensity</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="17" size="2" default="2000" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">High light intensity threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">When the environment brightness value is higher than the value set by this parameter, if the trigger source set by Parameter 15 is high brightness threshold alarm, the sensor will trigger BASIC_SET to control all connected devices in Connection Group 2.</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lux. High threshold value for light intensity</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="18" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Low temperature threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">When the environment temperature value is lower than the value set by this parameter, if the trigger source set by Parameter 15 is low temperature threshold alarm, the sensor will trigger BASIC_SET to control all connected devices in Connection Group 2.</lang></description><value from="-40" to="30"><description><lang xml:lang="en">celsius, Low temperature threshold Value</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="19" size="1" default="25" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">High temperature threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">When the environment temperature value is lower than the value set by this parameter, if the trigger source set by Parameter 15 is low temperature threshold alarm, the sensor will trigger BASIC_SET to control all connected devices in Connection Group 2.</lang></description><value from="0" to="80"><description><lang xml:lang="en">celsius. High temperature threshold value</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="2" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">PIR Window Time Setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">PIR sensor detects the duration of the motion events. Within the scope of the time, if events meeting Parameter 3 occur, the sensor will confirm that it has detected the occurrence of the motion events.In theory, the greater this value is, the higher the sensitivity of the sensor is. Thus, it is not recommended for users to modify the setting of this parameter.Window time = ([setting] + 1)4s, (value range: 4s, 8s, 12s, 16s)</lang></description><value from="0" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Window time = (Value + 1)x 4s; </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="20" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Binary Sensor Report Enable</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">When this parameter is set as 1, then the reporting Binary Sensor Report function of the sensor will be open. When the door magnet, motion detection, or tamper event is triggered, in addition to reporting the Notification Report to the host, it will also report the Binary Sensor Report for the purpose of downward compatibility of the sensor.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 - Disable, 1 - Enable</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">PIR Pulse Counter Settings</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Within the window time set by Parameter 2, when the number of pulses detected by the sensor reaches the value set by this parameter, the sensor will determine the occurrence of motion events. In theory, the higher the value is, the lower the sensitivity of the sensor is. It is not recommended for the user to modify the setting of this parameter.Number of pulses = [setting] + 1. So the value range of the parameter is as follows: 1, 2, 3, 4. </lang></description><value from="0" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Pulse Counter = Value + 1</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="15" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">PIR Blind Time Setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">BlindAfter the sensor detects a motion event, it will stop detecting the duration of the motion event. During this period, the sensor will not issue any command even if there is a motion event occurring in front of the PIR sensor. In theory, the higher the value is, the lower the power consumption of the sensor is. The time set by this parameter must be shorter than the time set by Parameter 9.Silence period = ([setting] + 1) x 0.5s.Thus, the value range of this parameter is as follows: 0.5s ~ 8s, with an interval of 0.5s.</lang></description><value from="0" to="15"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Blind Time = (Value + 1)x 0.5s</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">PIR Detected Disable</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The detection function of the motion sensor set by this parameter is disabled or not.'1'-motion detected function is enabled; '0'-motion detected function is disabled.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 - Disable, 1 - Enable</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED indicator Disable</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is to set whether the sensor will open LED and other indication functions when detecting a motion event. '1'-LED indication is open. When the sensor detects a motion event, the LED will flash once; '0'-LED indication is closed. When the sensor detects a motion event, the LED will not flash. Setting of this parameter will not affect the LED indication of the sensor in other conditions.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 - Disable, 1 - Enable</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Associated Control with Light Sensor Setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets whether to send the BASIC_SET command to the connected device based on the current brightness when there is a connected device in Connection Group 2.Parameters of BASIC_SET are determined by Parameter 8.'0'-Whether to send BASIC_SET command has nothing to do with the current environment brightness. As long as the sensor detects the occurrence of the motion event, the sensor will send BASIC_SET command to all devices of Connection Group 2 to control the motions of the device.'1'-When the current environment brightness is lower than the brightness value set by Parameter 11 and the sensor detects the occurrence of the motion event, the sensor will send the BASIC_SET command to all devices in Connection Group 2; If the current environment brightness is greater than or equal to the brightness value set by the parameter, the sensor will not send BASIC_SET command to all devices in Connection Group 2.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 - Disable, 1 - Enable</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="100" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Setting of BASIC_SET parameter</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the parameter value of BASIC_SET command so as to facilitate the control over different connected devices by the sensor. For example, if the connected device is a light, when the door magnet is detected to be open, this device will issue BASIC_SET command (the corresponding parameter is the set value of the parameter) to control the switch of the light.</lang></description><value from="0" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 - Off, 100 - On(Corresponding to 0xFF), 1 ~ 99 is responding to multilevel value</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="2" default="30" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Setting of BASIC_SET (0x00) time delay</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the delay time of sending BASIC_SET = 0x00 (closing the connected device) command by the sensor to the connected device, the unit of which is: Seconds. The execution effect of this parameter is affected by Parameter 15.If Parameter 15 is set as '1' or an event related to '1', the setting of this parameter will be invalid. The time controlling the connected device is only associated with the time set by Parameter 10. When the sensor triggers Motion Clear, it will send BASIC_SET=0x00 automatically.If Parameter 15 is set as '2' or '3' or an event related to '2' or '3', then when a Door/Window Close event or a Tamper Clear event occurs, the sensor will send BASIC_SET=0x00 to close the connected device after delaying for an interval set by this parameter.If Parameter 15 is set as 4 ~ 7, 9, 10, when the event meeting the conditions triggers the sensor, it will issue BASIC_SET= (value of Parameter 8) to control the connected device and then send BASIC_SET=0x00 to close the connected device after delaying for an interval set by this parameter. If the delay time has not come but the measured result of the sensor has returned to normal, then it will trigger BASIC_SET = 0x00 to close the connected device automatically.If this parameter is set as '0', it means that the BASIC_SET = 0x00 command is issued immediately when the trigger event is removed.If this parameter is set as '32767', it means that the device does not send BASIC_SET = 0x00 command.</lang></description><value from="0" to="4095"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0- No Delay; Other Value is Delay time (Second)</lang></description></value><value from="32767" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Not Send BASIC_SET = 0x00</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="99" size="2" default="1024" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Light Sensor Calibrated</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Due to the differences in shell light transmittance and the influences of sensor installation position on the receiving of light by light sensor, there will be errors in the measurement of environment brightness values. This parameter provides correction methods used in different application environments so as to get as exact environment light intensity as possible. This method requires a standard illuminometer as the reference and it will add the sensor to Z-Wave network. The correction steps are as follows: aRestore this parameter to default value by the host.bPut the standard illuminometer and the sensor in the same position and ensure that the light exposed to them is largely equal. Record the reading on the standard illuminometer, namely Vs. The value measured by this sensor, namely Vm, will be sent to the host via Z-Wave network. Record Vm. The calibration coefficient of this sensor is: k = Vm / Vs.cMultiply k, the coefficient having obtained, by 1024, and then get an integer by rounding it.dSet the value obtained in step c in Parameter 13 via the host. Then the calibration is finished.Example: The reading of the illuminometer Vs = 2600, and the data measured by the sensor at the same time Vm = 300; Then, k = Vm / Vs = 300 / 2600 = 0.1153, multiply the result by 1024k = 0.1153 * 1024 = 118.07, Round it, k = 118And then the calibration will be finished after the value 118 is set in Parameter 99 by host.</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Light intensity value correct coefficient</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17105818"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
