<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0060"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0006"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17105825</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">This presence detector using PIR (passive infrared receiver) detects the presence of a person in a room. The units compatible with S2 security, send information to a controller or any other associated Z-Wave device.Up to 4 devices can be controlled from this device.The sensor is a battery-powered device, which is in sleeping mode unless an action is detected. After a programmable sleeping time the device wakes up and sends a status information. After this the unit goes back to sleeping mode. Batteries can be changed without unscrewing the device from the door or frame.The unit will give a visual warning on the device and sends a warning to the Z-Wave controller, when batteries need to be replaced.The unit offers a tampering control and sends an alarm message when tampered.</lang></description><productName>MOTION DETECTOR</productName><brandName>Everspring</brandName><productCode>SP817-2</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Association with 1 node.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Association with 4 nodes (i.e. end devices such as smart plugs and other lighting controllers). This allows the detector to transfer commands directly to end devices without the participation of the controller. This has the effect that when the detector triggers, all devices associated with detector will be operated.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="99" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set level</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17105825"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
