<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="032C"/><productType value="5005"/><productId value="0002"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="01"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17115851</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Keyfob Remote Control with 4 keys is a ZWave standard reporting portable controller (RPC). It supports multiple key press actiontrigger central scenes notification and/or controls max 8 devices in group turn on, off, stop. A special "SOS" key designs foremergency notification. Further more, it can act as primary controller to add and control ZWave device as standalone application.The product supports acting as ZWave primary controller to add (inclusion), remove (exclusion) device stand alone, meanwhile itcan associated device to control groups while the device was added, supports triggers control associated device in groups.Also, It supports learn mode for added by other master controller, supports trigger central scene command to master controller, andit can associated control devices by keyfob local operation or master controller association set configuration.</lang></description><productName>Keyfob Remote Control</productName><brandName>Saykey</brandName><productCode>SK-5005-02</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline,is assigned to send unsolicited report lifeline status, including central scene report, notification alarm report,battery report, factory reset locally report etc.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group #2 assigned to send Basic Set Off/Binary Switch Off/Multilevel Start Change Down/Door Lock Secure Command control associated devices corresponding to the off key operation, including key press 1 times.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group #3 assigned to send Basic Set On/Binary Switch On/Multilevel Start Change Up/Door Lock Unsecure Command control associated devices corresponding to the on key operation, including key press 1 times.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group #4 assigned to send Stop Multilevel Change Command control associated devices corresponding to the stop key operation, including key press 1 times.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Protect timeout</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">From last keyfob operation complete protect timeout or received protect command from master controller; keyfobs keyboard was protected nomore keyboard except unprotect sequence is acceptable.</lang></description><value from="30" to="60"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Protect timeout, in second.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17115851"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
