<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="001A"/><productType value="0000"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17105809</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Eatons home automation hub is designed to act as a single solution for home owners, home builders and electrical contractors looking for a smart home system that incorporates home automation &amp; energy management. The home automation hub is designed to provide best in class user experience with Eatons line of compatible home automation products. The hub also allows homeowners and installers to integrate variety of other popular smart home devices such as Nest thermostats, Amazon Echo, Kwikset locks, as well as security systems. By integrating the control of these various devices into a single app, we help simplify home automation experience for the homeowners. The hub is a powerful device that continues to let homeowners access their smart home even when the internet connection to the cloud is down. With ad-hoc Wi-Fi capability, contractors can install the controller and Z-Wave based products in new home construction when there is no internet connectivity. With automatic firmware updates, Eaton ensures the hub is always current. This allows the device to have the latest features and fix any issues without service interruptions and expensive call backs. </lang></description><productName>Eatons Home Automation Hub </productName><brandName>Eaton</brandName><productCode>HOMECT</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17105809"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
