<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0060"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="0003"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17115856</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">This sensor offers information whether a door or window is open or closed.The product consists of a magnetic element and the main unit. One of the parts is mounted on the moving part of the window or of the door. The other part is placed on the frame. The installation can be done with screws or double-sided tape.The SM810 is a battery-powered device, which is in sleeping mode unless an action is detected. After a programmable sleeping time the device wakes up and sends a status information. After this the unit goes back to sleeping mode. Batteries can be changed without unscrewing the device from the door or frame.The unit will give a visual warning on the device and sends a warning to the Z-Wave controller, when batteries need to be replaced. The units send information to a controller or any other associated Z-Wave device. Up to 4 devices can be controlled from this device. The device needs to be included into a Z-Wave network by a remote control or any other Z-Wave controller. For configuration of certain behavior a static controller such as a PC with home automation software or a gateway is required.</lang></description><productName>Door/Window Detector</productName><brandName>Everspring</brandName><productCode>SM810-2</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Association with 1 node.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Association with 4 nodes (i.e. end devices such as smart plugs and other lighting controllers).This allows the detector to transfer commands directly to end devices without the participation of thecontroller. This has the effect that when the detector triggers, all devices associated with detector will beoperated.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17115856"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
