<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0330"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="a10d"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17115883</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Wall controller is a Security Enabled Z-Wave Plus device that can both control other Z-Wave devices and activate scenes in Gateways. The wall controller can be included and operated in any Z-Wave network with other Z-Wave certified devices from other manufacturers and/or other applications. All nonbattery operated nodes within the network will act as repeaters regardless of vendor to increase reliability of the network.</lang></description><productName>Wall Controller</productName><brandName>Sunricher</brandName><productCode>SR-ZV9001T4-DIM-EU</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline;1. Send Command Class Device ResetLocally to associated devices of thisgroup to report factory reset informationwhen factory reset the wall controller.2. Double click a group number of the wallcontroller to send scene activationcommand to associated devices of thisgroup using Command Class CentralScene.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="12"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Press button u00221u0022 to activate group in orderto switch the associated devices with aBasic Set (by pressing the central buttononce) or dim these devices by using thefour lower buttons (or the dim wheelaround the central button).</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="12"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Press button u00222u0022 to activate group in orderto switch the associated devices with aBasic Set (by pressing the central buttononce) or dim these devices by using thefour lower buttons (or the dim wheelaround the central button).</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="12"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Press button u00223u0022 to activate group in orderto switch the associated devices with aBasic Set (by pressing the central buttononce) or dim these devices by using thefour lower buttons (or the dim wheelaround the central button).</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="5" maxNodes="12"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Press button u00224u0022 to activate group in orderto switch the associated devices with aBasic Set (by pressing the central buttononce) or dim these devices by using thefour lower buttons (or the dim wheelaround the central button).</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17115883"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
