<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0241"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17125909</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Having to use several remotes and apps for our smart home gadgets and AV-devices in our homes is cumbersome, inconvenient and overwhelming. We believe the interaction with our daily technology should feel natural, simple and magical. That is why we have created NEEO. To control everything from one place. Instantly.The NEEO Thinking Remote is the most instant interface to control your AV devices and smart home gadgets. No need for multiple remotes or smart phone apps. The solid and long lasting anodized aluminium case protects against damage, resists fingerprints and feels just right thanks to its premium surface finish. It has just the buttons which are absolutely needed, designed for an optimal tactile experience. The amazing 291ppi touch screen display facilitates richest browsing and control. The remote comes with an embedded hand recognition technology for personal profiles, parental controls and more. The NEEO Brain connects to all of the devices in our homes and makes them available on the NEEO Thinking Remote or the NEEO app. Built in support for all smart home languages and protocols allows full control of your smart devices and gadgets out of the box. Via Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, Z-Wave, ZigBee, 6LowPan and incredibly strong IR blasters embedded in one device, NEEO simplifies control for more than 50000 AV and home automation products. The high-end antenna, hardware and case design as well as built in redundancy systems guarantee frictionless communication between the devices, facilitating a smooth user experience. </lang></description><productName>NEEO Brain, EU</productName><brandName>NEEO AG</brandName><productCode>6336-BRAIN-00008</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17125909"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
