<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="027B"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0003"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-17105789</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">There were several key concepts in the development of the Smart Hub. The product relies on the high acceptance of smartphones in our society and the presence of Wi-Fi networks in the homes. The Smart Hub utilizes a patent-pending technology to determine who is home and who is away based upon these two assumptions.The Smart Hub is always aware of the presence of the members of the household and the members of the household are always aware of the status of their home. Other guiding attributes were:A security first approach plus home automationA simplistic installationUser friendly interfaces (mobile app &amp; web portal)A system requiring minimal user interactionTo be device and sensor agnostic so to be compatible with many existing technologiesModern, sleek stylingThe Smart Hub is the next evolution in security and home control as it does not require a keypad for arming and disarming of the security system.It is compatible with the primary wireless technologies for the IoT, such as Z-Wave, Wi-Fi and ZigBee, as well as legacy wireless technologies for security devices by such leading manufacturers as Honeywell, GE, DSC, 2Gig and Elk Products.Also, any IP Wi-Fi cameras supporting Real Time Streaming Protocol (RTSP) are also compatible. With cameras in the home, there is always a concern with privacy, so additional controls were developed into the product to provide peace of mind and allow full control of the streaming of any video based on authority levels by camera, by user, based on who is home.</lang></description><productName>White Rabbit Smart Hub</productName><brandName>White Rabbit Electronics</brandName><productCode>SH-ZW+CBB+UT</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Lifeline association group is only used for reporting Device Reset Locally Notification. If the Smart Hub is reset to default state by pressing the u0022Reset Defaultsu0022 button found in the Z-Wave Toolbox, the Smart hub will send a Device Reset Locally Report to all the nodes contained in the Group 1 association list. If no nodes are configured, it will send the message to Broadcast.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-17105789"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
