<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0085"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0011"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18015975</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">FAKRO ARZ Z-Wave external roller shutters have been adapted for wireless cooperation with the Z-Wave system. The shutter is designed for FAKRO roof windows and its installation is possible at any time after roof window installation. It is also possible to use the shutter for roof windows of other manufactures. Installed on the outside of the window, the roller shutter constitutes an optimum solution against overheating and provides additional protection of the window e.g. against falling tree branches etc. The roller shutter enables complete blackout and good sound reduction. It is also good protection from glazing excessive cooling during the winter. The roller shutter also means increased security. It has built-in overload protection and can be controlled by using standard Z-Wave controller.The AMZ Z-Waveroller shutter has three extremes: - Maximum extension (encoder maximum position)- Completely rolled up (encoder minimum position)- Current limiting protecting awning blind against damage and user against accidental injury resulting from the contact with moving elements of awning blind.There are three association groups in roller shutter ARZ Z-Wave:1.Life Linegroup for position reporting roller shutter after each a stoppage and alarm reporting (overcurrent, damage encoders). This group can be a maximum 1 device.2.Basic Repeatgroup used to transfer the received basic commands to the devices included in this group. This group can be a maximum 5 devices.3.Multilevel Repeatgroup used to transfer the received multilevel commands to the devices included in this group. This group can be a maximum 5 devices.Technical Parameters: Power voltage: 15V DCRated current: 1,4 ACurrent limit: YESSpeed: 23 r.p.mTemperature of usage: (-10 C) do (65C) Supplying cable: 2 x 0,75mm2</lang></description><productName>ARZ Z-Wave</productName><brandName>FAKRO</brandName><productCode>ARZ Z-Wave</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline, group for position reporting roller shutter after each a stoppage and alarm reporting (overcurrent, damage encoders)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Repeatgroup used to transfer the received basic commands to the devices included in this group.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multilevel Repeatgroup used to transfer the received multilevel commands to the devices included in this group.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="12" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Calibrate</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Value describe the calibration status</lang></description><value from="1" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Value 1calibrated, Value 2discalibratedto enter the calibration mode must first time discalibrate and then calibrate.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="13" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">End Position</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Value describe the end position of roller shutter.</lang></description><value from="1" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1FF go to Max, 2FF go to previous position</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18015975"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
