<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0152"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0512"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18025986</certNumber><rfFrequency>South Africa</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Dome Home Automation DMWV1 Water Main Shut-off is designed to fit over existingturn ball-valves for pipes sized up to 1 inch. No professional plumbing contractor is required- it can be installed by a homeowner with just a screwdriver. This device requires a Z-Wave Certified hub for operation. When configured with a Water Leak Sensor, the Water Main Shut-off can automatically cut off the supply to limit the damage. You can also remotely control the valve position using your smarthome system mobile app. Extra-long Z-Wave wireless range (up to 150 ft) allows you to place it where its needed without worrying if the signal is reaching your Z-Wave Hub. Also functions as Z-Wave signal extender. Dome DMWV1 Water Main Shut-off comes with a 1-year limited warranty. Measurements in inches: 2.5 x 3.5 x 6. Dome Home Automation Z-Wave devices give your family peace of mind and security you can count on. With Dome, youre always connected and always covered.Installs over existing valve without need of a plumber using just a screw driver. Works withturn ball-valves on pipes sized up to 1 inchOpen/Close valve control allowing for automatic water shut-off when leaks are detected as well as on demand control using your smarthome mobile app.Up to 150-foot range. Functions as Z-Wave signal extenderZ-Wave Plus Certified. Requires a Z-Wave Certified Hub to operate</lang></description><productName>Water Main Shut-Off</productName><brandName>Dome</brandName><productCode>DMWV1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 is the Lifeline group, which can hold five devices. The Water Main Shut-Off sends this group a Binary Switch Report whenever it is turned on or off. The Water Main Shut-Off also sends this group a Device Reset Locally notification to remove itself from the Z-Wave network.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18025986"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
