<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0189"/><productType value="759e"/><productId value="6aff"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18015973</certNumber><rfFrequency>Australia and New Zealand</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">MEZZOs onboard WiFi allows it to be connected to your network wirelessly and combined with the MEZZO app on a smart phone or smart device, Use the MEZZO app to control your security, turn lights on and off, manage your energy, monitor your house with ease and receive push notifications of events. MEZZO provides Cellular backup should your network go down or is switched off allowing for general arming and disarming of your system and event notification.Add a small Z-Wave receiver to any light switch or power point to turn on, off or dim lights and devices from anywhere, anytime. In fact you can control almost any type of Z-Wave enabled device remotely using the MEZZO app. Interface with numerous Ness wireless security devices such as MEZZO radio PIR, radio reed switches, radio keys, radio smoke detectors.MEZZO can control numerous security devices such as wireless PIR motion sensors, wireless door switches, wireless smoke detectors and many others, all designed to cleverly secure your home.With MEZZOs multi-scenario geo-fencing you can set your house to a desired temperature and lighting level when you approach your home. MEZZO can even disarm the security, open your garage door and unlock your door when you pull into the driveway ... all without touching a button.</lang></description><productName>Mezzo</productName><brandName>Mezzo</brandName><productCode>106-360</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18015973"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
