<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="024F"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="1002"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18026000</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Multifunction Switch is a Z-Wave Plus mains powered Wallbox mountable Wall Controller. It can be configured to control up to Four separate Light Zones or Central Scenes. Each Light Zone can consist of both Dimmers and Switches. The device can be combined with a Back Unit, which provide local Switch or Dimmer functionality.Room and Floor temperature sensors can also be connected to the device, which enables the device to function as a head-less Thermostat. The Thermostat is fully controllable from a Z-Wave Controller, and can control both a Local and Remote heating relay.</lang></description><productName>Multifunction Switch</productName><brandName>SE Devices</brandName><productCode>FMS</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline - Supports MultichannelOnly local Light Zone changes are reported if Multichannel association is not used.Commands issued:- Basic Report: Reports Light Zone state and level changes- Central Scene Notification: Notifies activated Scenes- Sensor Multilevel Report: Power Consumption and Air Temperature (if a sensor is connected)- Meter: Reports energy consumption- Device Reset Locally - Reports device Factory Reset</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls devices in Light Zone 1. Supports Multichannel AssociationCommands Issued:- Basic Set: Controlled by Light Zone 1. Dimmer or Switch mapped Basic command values is configurable</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls devices in Light Zone 2. Supports Multichannel AssociationCommands Issued:- Basic Set: Controlled by Light Zone 1. Dimmer or Switch mapped Basic command values is configurable</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls devices in Light Zone 3. Supports Multichannel AssociationCommands Issued:- Basic Set: Controlled by Light Zone 1. Dimmer or Switch mapped Basic command values is configurable</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="5" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls devices in Light Zone 4. Supports Multichannel AssociationCommands Issued:- Basic Set: Controlled by Light Zone 1. Dimmer or Switch mapped Basic command values is configurable</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="6" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enables control of external Heating Thermostats in the same heating zone.Commands Issued:- Thermostat Setpoint Set: Sent on local Thermostat Set-Point changes- Thermostat Mode Set: Sent on local Thermostat Mode changes</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="7" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enables the Thermostat to control Remote Heating Relays.Commands issued:- Basic Set: Value ON (255) or OFF (0), according to Thermostat Heating State changes.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="10" size="1" default="200" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Dimming Speed</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Defines the u0022fadeu0022 time when setting a dim level from a controller. Fade time is defined as the time it takes to dim from MIN level to MAX level, which means an increase of 10% in light level takes 1/10th of the configured time. The value defines the dim time in 1/100'th of a second, which means a value of 200 means the Dimming Speed is 2.0 seconds from MIN to MAX. Max time is 327.67 seconds (around 5.5 minutes). Values below 300 (0.3 seconds) are ignored and values below 1000 (1 second) are discouraged.</lang></description><value from="30" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dimmer Speed in 1/100th of a Second</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="11" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Dimmer Mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Defines if Dimmer should operate in Leading or Tailing Edge mode. Most Lights work quite OK in the default Leading Edge mode, but this mode also usually cause some noise from the dimmer unit. During installation it is therefore recommended to try TE mode, and use this if the Light operates properly. Tailing Edge mode is known to cause instability in some type of Lights! This configuration does not have an effect on 1-10V Dimmer Back Units!0 = Leading Edge Mode (LE)1 = Tailing Edge Mode (TE)</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dimmer Operation Mode</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="12" size="1" default="90" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Maximum Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Maximum Light level of the dimmer. Typically there is no visible difference when the dimming level reaches a point in the range 75 - 90, and the installer should set this value to the lowest value where no change is visible. The default value of 90 is usually OK. Range 1-99.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Maximum Dimmer Level</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="13" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Minimum Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Minimum Light Level of the dimmer. This should be adjusted so the controlled Light is still ON and stable. Remember that LED type lights may work if dimmed down to a low value, but may not start if the light is turned OFF and ON again. Range 1-99.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Minimum Dimmer Level</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="14" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Button Mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls the operation mode of the buttons. Valid configuration values are:0Single Switch Mode (default)1Dual Switch Mode2Quadruple Switch Mode3Legacy Scenario Mode4Central Scene Controller Mode(See detailed description in manual)</lang></description><value from="0" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set Button Mode</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="15" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Light Zone Control Mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls if the Light Zones should operate in Switch or Dimmer Mode (only used in Button Modes 0, 1 and 2):0All Light Zones in Dimmer Mode (default)1All Light Zones in Switch Mode (default with Relay back unit)To control Light Zones mode individually, add any of the following values to enable switch mode individually (dimmer is default):2Light Zone 1 Switch Mode4Light Zone 2 Switch Mode8Light Zone 3 Switch Mode16Light Zone 4 Switch ModeExample: A value of 10 (8 + 2) enables switch mode in Light Zone 1 and 3.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Common Mode for all Light Zones</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="30"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Switch Mode for individual Light Zones</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="17" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Back Unit Role</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Configures the Role of the Back Unit, which dictates what Local functionality controls it.Valid configuration values are:0 - The Thermostat will control the Back Unit (if the back unit is a dimmer, then this value has no effect as Thermostats requires a relay to function)1 - The Light Control feature (buttons) will control the Back Unit.2 - Disconnected mode means the Back Unit is not controlled by any local UI or features, and can only be controlled via Z-Wave End-Point 5 (or non-channel encapsulated commands).</lang></description><value from="0" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Selected Back Unit Role</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="18" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Back Unit Light Zone</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Selects which Light Zone the Back Unit should be assigned to. Possible values are:1Light Zone 1 (Button and Z-Wave) (default)2Light Zone 2 (Button and Z-Wave)3Light Zone 3 (Button and Z-Wave)4Light Zone 4 (Button and Z-Wave)This can be used to assign the back unit control to any of the Multiswitch buttons (Light Zone 1 - 4). This does not have any effect however when the BU role is set to Thermostat or Disconnected!</lang></description><value from="1" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Selected Back Unit Light Zone</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="240" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Floor Sensor Temperature Offset</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Defines an offset to the Floor Temperature, given as a signed integer at 1/10 of a degree celcius. This provides an offset range of 12.8 to +12.7 degrees celcius (-128 to 127). </lang></description><value from="-128" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Offset in 1/10th of a degree Celcius</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="241" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Room Sensor Temperature Offset</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Defines an offset to the Room Temperature, given as a signed integer at 1/10 of a degree celcius. This provides an offset range of 12.8 to +12.7 degrees celcius (-128 to 127). </lang></description><value from="-128" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Offset in 1/10th of a degree Celcius</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="32" size="2" default="270" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Thermostat Set Point Max</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Maximum Heat Set Point the Thermostat is allowed to be set to. If the Thermostat is used for Floor Heating, please make sure that this value is configured to the same value as (or lower than) the Max Floor Temperature. Given in 1/10 of a degree Celcius, which means a value of 300 means 30 degrees C. Range: 0500 (0-50 degrees).</lang></description><value from="0" to="500"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set Point Max in 1/10th of a degree Celcius</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="34" size="2" default="50" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Thermostat Set Point Min</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Minimum Heat Set Point the Thermostat is allowed to be set to. Given in 1/10 of a degree Celcius, which means a value of 50 means 5 degrees C. Range: 0500 (0-50 degrees).</lang></description><value from="0" to="500"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set Point Min in 1/10th of a degree Celcius</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="36" size="2" default="3600" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Thermostat Control Resend Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Defines the interval between each time the Thermostat will repeat its last control command. This is used in combination with the Relay Safety configuration when controlling external Relays. If the Thermostat should fail, it would then stop sending control commands which in turn means the Relay will turn itself OFF after the safety mode delay has expired. This insures that heating will not be left ON indefinitely in failure situations. Range: 6032767 seconds</lang></description><value from="0" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Resend Interval in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="37" size="2" default="300" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Thermostat Minimum On/Off Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration defines the minimum interval the controlled Thermostat Relays will be ON and OFF. This is a feature intended to avoid turning control relays ON and OFF too frequently, which should insure a better lifetime of controlled relays. The default value is 5 minutes, which is OK for most electrical heating control. If used to control Water based heating, the value MUST be adjusted in accordance with the manufacturers specifications. Range: 6032767 seconds</lang></description><value from="60" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Minimum On/Off interval in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="38" size="2" default="270" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Thermostat Floor Temp Max</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Max floor temperature if a local floor sensor is connected. If the Floor Sensor reads a temperature Higher than the configured value, it will immediately turn the relay (or any associated relays) OFF. The relay will stay off until the temperature sinks below this value, and the Thermostat issues it's next control command. Disabled if zero (0) value, or if no floor sensor is connected. The value is given as 1/10th of a degree Celcius. Range: 0500 (0-50 degrees). NOTE! MAX 27 degrees is recommended for Wooden Floors! NOTE! This function is always active as long as a Floor Sensor is connected, regardless of the sensor configuration described below.</lang></description><value from="0" to="500"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Floor Temp Max in 1/10th of a degree Celcius</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="2" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Safety Activate Delay</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Safety Mode is activated after the configured number of seconds has elapsed. It will start by turning OFF the Back Unit when activated. A 0 value Disables Safety Mode. The MAX limit is 32767 seconds (9 hours, 6 minutes and 7 seconds). The minimum Actication delay is 60 seconds, and values from 1 to 59 will automatically be translated to a 60 second delay.</lang></description><value from="0" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Safety Activate Delay in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="40" size="1" default="3" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Sensor Select</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Defines which temperature Sensor should be used for Heating Control. The default value is Both (3), which should work well in most scenarios (even when only a Floor or Room sensor is present). If both a Room and Floor sensor is used, the Thermostat will always control heating based on the lowest temperature reading of the two, to insure a comfortable floor temperature even if the room is already warm enough. If this is not wanted, the Thermostat should be configured to use the Room sensor Only. NOTE! The Floor Max Temperature feature will ALWAYS be active as long as a floor sensor is available, even if the Thermostat is configured to only use the Room Sensor. 1 - Local Room - Use temperature from Locally connected Room sensor ONLY. Max Floor Temp protection is still active as long as a floor sensor is available. 2 - Local Floor - Use temperature from Locally connected Floor sensor ONLY 3 - Both (auto) - Use temperature from Locally connected Floor AND Room sensor if available (Default).</lang></description><value from="1" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Sensor Select</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="44" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Cold Start Minimum Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Sets the minimum level the Dimmer should go to when the light is switched ON. This is typically used for LED lamps which does not switch ON correctly when the dimming level is at the Minimum. See detailed description below.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Cold Start Minimum Level</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="2" default="600" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Safety OFF Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The number of seconds to stay in OFF mode when Safety is activated. The Back unit turns ON when the timer have elapsed. If value is 0, the Back Unit will not turn back ON. The MAX limit is 32767 seconds (9 hours, 6 minutes and 7 seconds). A 60 second minimum period applies.</lang></description><value from="0" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Safety OFF Period in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="2" default="300" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Safety ON Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The number of seconds to stay in ON mode when Safety is activated. The Back Unit turns back OFF when the timer have elapsed (and continues to turn ON and OFF alternately). If value is 0, the Back Unit WILL NOT turn ON at all. The MAX limit is 32767 seconds (9 hours, 6 minutes and 7 seconds). A 60 second minimum period applies.</lang></description><value from="0" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Safety ON Period in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="64" size="2" default="600" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Report Inteval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Defines the Periodic Report interval for temperature readings. This can be configured to a minimum of 60 seconds and maximum of (32767 seconds. A 0 value disables the Interval based Periodic reporting, and any value below 60 results in a 60 second interval.</lang></description><value from="0" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Report Interval in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="66" size="1" default="10" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Report Threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Defines a temperature change threshold where a temperature report is sent regardless of the Report Interval. This also works if the report interval is disabled. The value is given in 1/10 of a degree celsius, and can be in the range 1-127. A zero value disables the Threshold.</lang></description><value from="0" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Report Threshold in 1/10th of a degree Celcius</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="67" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Thermostat OnOff Interval Override Threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Defines a temperature threshold at which the configured On/Off interval is overridden and the Heating relay state will change regardless. The value is given in 1/10th of a degree, supporting a max threshold of 12.7 degrees celcius. A Zero (0) value disables this feature (the default)</lang></description><value from="0" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Threshold in 1/10th of a degree Celcius</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="80" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Button LED Mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls the operation of the LEDs. Possible values are:0LEDs are always OFF (default)1Momentary ON2Stable ONThe LED operation is described in details in the User Manual, and also depends on the Button Mode configuration.</lang></description><value from="0" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Selected LED Mode</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18026000"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
