<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0047"/><productType value="3001"/><productId value="0B01"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18026007</certNumber><rfFrequency>Australia and New Zealand</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">It is a Z-Wave enabled device (interoperable, two-way RF mesh networking technology) and is fully compatible with any Z-Wave enabled network and its security framework. Every mains powered Z-Wave enabled device acts as a signal repeater and multiple devices result in more possible transmission routes which helps eliminate RF dead-spots.Z-Wave enabled device displaying the Z-Wave logo can also be used with it regardless of the manufacturer, and ours can also be used in other manufacturers Z-Wave enabled networks.Z-WAVE2RTS interface receives Z-Wave signals and translates them into RTS commands for Somfys RTS motor. The Z-Wave2RTS interface supports mulit-channel Command Class for up to 8 devices corresponding to 8 individual or groups of Somfy motorized products. The Z-Wave2RTS requires 12-24Vdc power supply by power adaptor or 5Vdc via micro-USB adaptor.</lang></description><productName>Z-WAVE2RTS INTERFACE-AU 8 CHANNELS</productName><brandName>Somfy</brandName><productCode>1811723</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline (Report ZWave2RTS interface address to ZWAVE Hub (node) after reset.)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Report DCT status to Hub (node) when DCT port is triggered. The DCT status feedback send to Hub automatically. If EndPoint is defined, it will be use MultiChannel Command to report the DCT status</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18026007"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
