<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="001E"/><productType value="0004"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="81"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18015976</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Notify caregivers when a loved one does not get up at their usual time or gets up multiple times during the night. Easily installed in a kitchen, bathroom, bedroom or hallway - just plug it in! The wide angle motion sensor detects motion when placed at floor level in a normal wall outlet or at counter height in a kitchen or bath. Never needs batteries!Receive an email or text when motion is detected or the temperature is dangerously low while you are away.Turn on lights and sirens automatically.Save energy by automatically turning off lights in unoccupied rooms or hallways.Set the color LED night light to inform you that your garage door is open, there is a severe weather alert or any indicator you can imagine!Operates as a Z-Wave range extender utilizing fifth generation Z-Wave technology to enhance the reliability and speed of every device on a Z-Wave network. Version 2.0 firmware adds AES-128 security S2 and SmartStart</lang></description><productName>EZmultiPli</productName><brandName>Express Controls LLC</brandName><productCode>EZMultiPli</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline.This group supports a single NodeID and is normally assigned to the Z-Wave system controller when EZMultiPli is added to the Z-Wave network. All Notification command class reports (motion detection) are sent to the node assigned to this group. Advanced lighting control should be handled by a home control application based on these reports.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">This group is used to directly turn lights on or off when motion is detected. Up to four (4) Z-Wave devices can be associated in this group. EZMultiPli will send a BASIC ON command to all devices that are associated in this group. Note that including the NodeID of EZMultiPli in this group will control the LED which will come on when motion is detected and goes off when no motion has been detected for OnTime minutes.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="20" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">OnTime</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">OnTime sets the number of minutes that the lights stay on when motion has not been detected.A value of 0 is a special mode where the lights are sent a command to turn them on whenever motion is detected. EZMultiPli will NOT turn the lights off in this mode. A motion detection event is sent at most once per minute.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Only send an ON every time motion is detected</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Minutes of No-Motion when an OFF is sent</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="99" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">OnLevel</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">OnLevel is the value sent by the Z-Wave BASIC_SET command to all Association Group 2 nodes when motion is detected. A value of 0 will turn the lights off (not recommended).A value between 1 and 99 will set the dim level to between 1% and 99% (99% is full on).A value of -1 will turn the light on which depends on the device but most will set the dim level to the last dim setting.</lang></description><value from="-1" to="-1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set to previous ON value</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Not Recommended</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dim Level to set the associated device to</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="60" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LiteMin</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">A Luminance report is sent to the Lifeline every LiteMin minutes.Luminance values can be obtained at any time by polling.</lang></description><value from="1" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Minutes between sensor readings</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="60" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">TempMin</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">A Temperature report is sent to the Lifeline every TempMin minutes.Temperature values can be obtained at any time by polling.</lang></description><value from="1" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Minutes between sensor readings</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">TempAdj</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">TempAdj is a twos-complement number that is used to adjust the temperature reading to make it more accurate. The value is in tenths of degree Fahrenheit. The temperature reading can be adjusted by +12.7F to -12.8F. A value of 1 will adjust the temperature reading by +0.1F. A value of -1 will adjust the temperature by -0.1F. A value of 123 will adjust the temperature by +12.3F. </lang></description><value from="-128" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature adjustment in 0.1F</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18015976"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
