<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0364"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18015970</certNumber><rfFrequency>Japan (922-926 MHz)</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">AXIS T8341 PIR Motion Sensor is a wireless sensor which provides motion detection both day and night. With its support for wireless input/output connectivity, the PIR motion sensor can communicate wirelessly with AXIS M5065 PTZ Network camera or other connected Z-Wave Plus controllers, creating a small security solution with less cabling. Thanks to its integrated wireless I/O connectivity, AXIS T8341 enables flexible installation as the sensor can easily be moved and adapted to your needs. </lang></description><productName>PIR Motion Sensor</productName><brandName>Axis Communications </brandName><productCode>T8341-JP</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Association with 1 node.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Association with 4 nodes (i.e. end devices such as smart plugs and other lighting controllers). This allows the detector to transfer commands directly to end devices without the participation of the controller. This has the effect that when the detector triggers, all devices associated with detector will be operated.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="99" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">When Basic Set Command is sent where contains a value, the receiver will take it for consideration; for instance, if a lamp module is received the Basic Set command of which value is decisive as to how bright of dim level of lamp module shall be.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ON (Binary Switch Device)/Dim Level (Multilevel Switch Device)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="6" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Sensitivity Level </lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">In order to provide a best efficiency of the detector, it is recommended to test the detector with movements from a farthest end of the coverage area at first time of use. If movements cannot be detected sensitively, simply adjust the sensitivity level with Configuration Parameter #3. This parameter can be configured with the value of 1 through 10, where 1 means low sensitivity and 10 means highest sensitivity.</lang></description><value from="1" to="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Sensitivity Level </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="2" default="180" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Re-trigger Interval Setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Configuration parameter that can be used to adjust the interval of being re-triggered after the detector has been triggered as Configuration Parameter #4. No response will be made during this interval if a movement is presented. The time interval can be set between 5 secs to 3600 secs.</lang></description><value from="5" to="3600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Re-trigger Interval Setting</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="20" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Lux Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The user can set a detecting percentage of lux level which determines when the light sensor will be activated. If percentage of lux level of ambient illumination falls below this percentage, and a person moves across or within the protected area, the detector will emit Z-Wave ON Command (i.e. Basic Set Command (Value = Basic Set Level)) to controller and activate connected modules and lighting. Percentage can be set between 1% to 100%.</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lux Level</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="2" default="15" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">On-Off Duration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The function of on-off duration setting will be useful if the detector is connected with a module or lighting. The duration determines how long the module/lighting should stay ON. For instance, Lamp Module turns off 100 secs after it has been turned on. This parameter can be configured with the value of 5 through 3600, where 5 means 5 second delay and 3600 means 3600 seconds of delay.</lang></description><value from="5" to="3600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">On-Off Duration</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18015970"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
