<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0315"/><productType value="4447"/><productId value="3033"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="81"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18025995</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">ZLINKs WS-100 is a Z-Wave Plus certified device with S2 security and Smart Start features. You can now add this device securely and with ease using QR code on the product with compatible gateways supporting S2 and Smart Start. Sleek WS-100 communicates with other Z-Wave certified devices and updates your home into a smart home. ZLINK WS-100 replaces a standard in-wall light switch turning it into a Z-Wave controlled network device with manual and remote ON/OFF control. ZLINK WS-100 supports, Instant Feedback of manual status to compatible gateways as well as Central Scene to allow setting multiple scene control throughout the home, with gateways supporting Central Scene. Each Z-Wave device serves as a node to repeat the signal in the network, thus, extending the overall Z-Wave mesh wireless network range.Additional Features: Power 120 VAC, 60Hz, up to 1800 watts Region US: 908.4, 916 MHz Works with incandescent, CFL &amp; LED lights Remotely or manually turns ON or OFF lights Fits standard wall plates (wall plate not included) Works with any certified gateway supporting Z-Wave</lang></description><productName>Z-Wave In-Wall On/Off Switch</productName><brandName>ZLINK</brandName><productCode>WS-100</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1. Z-Wave Plus Lifeline2. Central Scene Notification3. Switch Binary Report4. Device Reset Locally Notification</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="3" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Night Light</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The LED indicator will be OFF when the connected light is ON and vice versa.When value =0 the LED indicator will be OFF when the the connected light is ON, and the LED will be ON when the connected light is OFF. If value =1 the LED indicator will be ON when the connected light is ON, and the LED indicator will be OFF when the connected light is OFF. If value =2 the LED indicator will always be OFF regardless of the load status</lang></description><value from="0" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">When value =0 the LED indicator will be OFF when the the connected light is ON, and the LED will be ON when the connected light is OFF. If value =1 the LED indicator will be ON when the connected light is ON, and the LED indicator will be OFF when the connected light is OFF. If value =2 the LED indicator will always be OFF regardless of the load status</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Orientation of ON/OFF on rocker switch</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The orientation of the ON/OFF on the rocker switch can be inverted using parameter 4. If value =0, the connected light will turn ON by pressing the top side of the rocker switch and turn OFF by pressing the bottom side. If value =1 the connected light will turn OFF by pressing the top side of the rocker switch and turn ON by pressing the bottom side.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">If value =0, the connected light will turn ON by pressing the top side of the rocker switch and turn OFF by pressing the bottom side. If value =1 the connected light will turn OFF by pressing the top side of the rocker switch and turn ON by pressing the bottom side.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18025995"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
