<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="019A"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0003"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18026002</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The iamsmart Window &amp; Door Sensor is an ultra-thin magnetic contact sensor designed to monitor windows and doors for your safety and efficiency. Its so thin that it can be mounted invisibly in a tiny gap between the frame and the door or window. It is as easy to mount as a sticker using the iamsmart Window &amp; Door Sensors adhesive tape. The iamsmart Window &amp; Door Sensor is a Z-Wave plus compliant and can be used with any existing Z-Wave smart home system. Combined with the iamsmart Smartbox and smart Radiator Thermostat, the Window &amp; Door Sensor is also able to make your heating more efficient by detecting open windows and adjusting the temperature accordingly to not waste energy. To make your home more secure the iamsmart Smartbox and the Window &amp; Door Sensor are the perfect team: the internal, very loud siren of the Smartbox scares robbers and is triggered by the iamsmart Window &amp; Door Sensor if a window or door is opened while youre away. Besides its main featuressecurity and efficient heating in combination with the smart Radiator Thermostat, the iamsmart Window &amp; Door Sensor has an impressive battery life of up to 10 years.</lang></description><productName>Der Aufpasser</productName><brandName>iamsmart</brandName><productCode>3000117</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Notification type</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">User can use this configuration parameter to change the notification type compatible with their gateway controller.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Binary Sensor report</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Notification report</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic report</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED indication</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED On during specific event detected (ex. door opened) else if the parameter value is 0, LED will be turned OFF for the specific event detected.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> Specific event indication (ex. door opened) Off</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">On</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18026002"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
