<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="013C"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="000D"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18026005</certNumber><rfFrequency>Russia</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The slim multisensor PST02-1B has PIR, temperature and illumination, 3 sensors function in one,based on Z-Wave technologyIt is the Z-WaveTM plus product, it support the security, OTA... Thosenewest features of the Z-WaveTM technology. Z-WaveTM is a wirelesscommunication protocol designed for home automation, specifically toremotely control applications in residential and light commercialenvironments. The technology uses a low-power RF radio embedded orretrofitted into home electronics devices and systems, such as lighting,home access control, entertainment systems and household appliances.</lang></description><productName>Slim Multisensor </productName><brandName>Philio Technology</brandName><productCode>PST02-1B</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The group 1 is forreceiving the report message, like triggered event,temperature, illumination etc.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The group 2 is for lightcontrol, the device will send the Basic Set commandto this group.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="10" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto Report Battery Time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The interval time for auto report thebattery level.0 means turn off auto report battery.The default value is 12. The tick timecan setting by the configuration No.20.</lang></description><value from="0" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The interval time for auto report the battery level. 0 means turn off auto report battery. The default value is 12. The tick time can setting by the configuration No.20.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="12" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto Report Illumination Time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The interval time for auto report theillumination.0 means turn off auto reportillumination.The default value is 12. The tick timecan setting by the configuration No.20.</lang></description><value from="0" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The interval time for auto report the illumination. 0 means turn off auto report illumination. The default value is 12. The tick time can setting by the configuration No.20.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="13" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto Report Temperature Time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The interval time for auto report thetemperature.0 means turn off auto reporttemperature.The default value is 12. The tick timecan setting by the configuration No.20.</lang></description><value from="0" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The interval time for auto report the temperature. 0 means turn off auto report temperature. The default value is 12. The tick time can setting by the configuration No.20.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="-127" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Setting the BASIC command value toturn on the light. The 0xFF(-1) meansturn on the light. For dimmerequipment 1 to 100 means the lightstrength.0 means turn off the light.Caution: The value is unsigned byte,the range is from 0x00 ~ 0xFF.</lang></description><value from="-128" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Setting the BASIC command value to turn on the light. The 0xFF(-1) means turn on the light. For dimmer equipment 1 to 100 means the light strength. 0 means turn off the light. Caution: The value is unsigned byte, the range is from 0x00 ~ 0xFF.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="20" size="1" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto Report Tick Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The interval time for auto report eachtick. Setting this configuration willeffect configuration No.10, No.11,No.12 and No.13.The unit is 1 minute.Caution1: Setting to 0 means turnoff all auto report function.Caution2: The value is unsignedbyte, the range is from 0x00 ~ 0xFF.</lang></description><value from="-128" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The interval time for auto report each tick. Setting this configuration will effect configuration No.10, No.11, No.12 and No.13. The unit is 1 minute.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="21" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Differential Report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The temperature differential to report.0 means turn off this function.The unit is Fahrenheit.Enable this function the device willdetect every minutes.And when the temperature is over 140degree Fahrenheit, it will continuereport.Enable this functionality will causesome issue please see the detail in theTemperature Report section.</lang></description><value from="0" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The temperature differential to report. 0 means turn off this function. The unit is Fahrenheit. Enable this function the device willdetect every minutes. And when the temperature is over 140 degree Fahrenheit, it will continue report. Enable this functionality will cause some issue please see the detail in the Temperature Report section.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="22" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Illumination Differential Report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The illumination differential to report.0 means turn off this function.The unit is percentage.Enable this function the device willdetect every minutes.Enable this functionality will causesome issue please see the detail in theIllumination Report section.</lang></description><value from="0" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The illumination differential to report. 0 means turn off this function. The unit is percentage. Enable this function the device will detect every minutes. Enable this functionality will cause some issue please see the detail in the Illumination Report section.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="80" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">PIR Sensitivity</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">PIR sensitivity settings.0 means disable the PIR motion.1 means the lowest sensitivity,99 means the highest sensitivity.High sensitivity means can detectedlong distance, but if there is morenoise signal in the environment, it willre-trigger too frequency.</lang></description><value from="0" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">PIR sensitivity settings. 0 means disable the PIR motion. 1 means the lowest sensitivity, 99 means the highest sensitivity. High sensitivity means can detected long distance, but if there is more noise signal in the environment, it will re-trigger too frequency.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="99" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Light Threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Setting the illumination threshold toturn on the light. When the eventtriggered and the environmentillumination lower then the threshold,the device will turn on the light.0 means turn off illumination detectedfunction. And never turn on the light.1 means darkest.99 means brightest.100 means turn off illuminationdetected function. And always turn onthe light.Notice: In none test mode, only thevalue in 1 to 99 will enable theillumination detected function andupdate the illumination value.</lang></description><value from="0" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 means turn off illumination detected function. And never turn on the light. 1 means darkest. 99 means brightest. 100 means turn off illumination</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Operation Mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Operation mode. Using bit to control.Caution: The value is unsigned byte,the range is from 0x00 ~ 0xFF.Bit1: 1 means test mode,0 means normal modeBit3: Setting the temperature scale.0: Fahrenheit, 1:CelsiusBit4: Disable the illumination reportafter event triggered. (1:Disable,0:Enable)Bit5: Disable the temperature reportafter event triggered. (1:Disable,0:Enable)Bit7: Disable the back key releaseinto test mode. (1:Disable,0:Enable)</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 means test mode, 0 means normal mode.</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Bit3: Setting the temperature scale. 0: Fahrenheit, 1:Celsius</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Bit4: Disable the illumination report after event triggered. (1:Disable, 0:Enable)</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Bit5: Disable the temperature report after event triggered. (1:Disable, 0:Enable)</lang></description></value><value from="7" to="7"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Bit7: Disable the back key release into test mode. (1:Disable, 0:Enable)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="4" type="constant"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Mult- Sensor Function Switch</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multisensor function switch. Using bitto control.Caution: The value is unsigned byte,the range is from 0x00 ~ 0xFF.Bit1: Disable PIR integrateIllumination to turn ON the lightingnodes in the association group 2.(1:Disable, 0:Enable)</lang></description><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable PIR integrate Illumination to turn ON the lighting nodes in the association group 2. (1:Disable, 0:Enable)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="4" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Customer Function</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Customer function switch, using bitcontrol.Caution: The value is unsigned byte,the range is from 0x00 ~ 0xFF.Bit1: Enable sending motion OFFreport. (0:Disable, 1:Enable)Note: Depends on the Bit4,0: Report Notification CC,Type: 0x07, Event: 0xFE1: Sensor Binary Report,Type: 0x0C, Value: 0x00Bit2: Enable PIR super sensitivitymode. (0:Disable, 1:Enable)Bit4: Notification Type,0: Using Notification Report.1: Using Sensor Binary ReportBit5: Disable Multi CC in auto report.(1:Disable, 0:Enable)Bit6: Disable to report battery statewhen the device triggered. (1:Disable,0:Enable)</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Bit1: Enable sending motion OFF report. (0:Disable, 1:Enable)</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Bit2: Enable PIR super sensitivity mode. (0:Disable, 1:Enable)</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Bit4: Notification Type, 0: Using Notification Report. 1: Using Sensor Binary Report.</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Bit5: Disable Multi CC in auto report.(1:Disable, 0:Enable)</lang></description></value><value from="6" to="6"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Bit6: Disable to report battery state when the device triggered. (1:Disable, 0:Enable)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="3" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">PIR Re- Detect Interval Time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">In the normal mode, after the PIRmotion detected, setting the re-detecttime. 8 seconds per tick, default tick is3 (24 seconds).Setting the suitable value to preventreceived the trigger signal toofrequently. Also can save the batteryenergy.Notice: If this value bigger than theconfiguration setting NO. 9. There is aperiod after the light turned off andthe PIR not start detecting.</lang></description><value from="1" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">In the normal mode, after the PIR motion detected, setting the re-detect time. 8 seconds per tick, default tick is 3 (24 seconds).</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="4" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Turn Off Light Time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">After turn on the lighting, setting thedelay time to turn off the lightingwhen the PIR motion is not detected.8 seconds per tick, default tick is 4 (32seconds).0 means never send turn off lightcommand.</lang></description><value from="0" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">After turn on the lighting, setting the delay time to turn off the lighting when the PIR motion is not detected. 8 seconds per tick, default tick is 4 (32 seconds). 0 means never send turn off light command</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18026005"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
