<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0348"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18036034</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Central Home Unit is the main entity to observe and control any other Z-Wave certified device available on the market. The integrated User-Interface allows the user to fully monitor, configure and control devices. The user can get the actual values of any device actively or passively to not overload the network usage over the air. Additionally, the user can set values for devices which acts as actors in the network. The User-Interface also allows the user to create specific rules, e.g. to turn off a device if a consumption is reached or to shut down the curtains at a given point of time. Devices can be grouped together to act collectively on specific events, e.g. if a fire alarm was detected. The user can monitor the whole Z-Wave network and control it. In detail, the user can add, remove or replace devices to or from the network. He can configure connections and reset the whole network. Every node can be updated independently if needed. Every device can also be configured on its own. With this ability devices of the same type can act differently. To have a better monitoring overview each device can be associated with a human readable name and a location description. The User-Interface only allows to control and monitor the capabilities the device offers. The Central Home Unit can also be configured as slave device in a Z-Wave network to support any other Controller device.</lang></description><productName>Central Home Unit</productName><brandName>baseCON</brandName><productCode>CHU00001-w</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Support one association group with one node.Support grouping identifier: 1 (lifeline)Description: This node will receive the Device Reset Locally command.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18036034"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
