<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0371"/><productType value="0102"/><productId value="0003"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18036041</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">TheNanoMote Quadis a wireless, portable and rechargeable scene switch. It can control a Z-Wave device, such as smart plug, smart dimmer with a Z-Wave gateway. You can also activate a scene like sleep scene, movie scene and entertainment scene with it. </lang></description><productName>NanoMote Quad</productName><brandName>Aeotec</brandName><productCode>ZWA003-A</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">NanoMote Quad will send the central scene notification command and battery report command to the associated nodes if any button is triggered.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">NanoMote Quad will send Basic Set command to the associated nodes if button 1 is pressed.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">NanoMote Quad will sendswitch multilevel set, the multilevel start level change and multilevel stop level change command to the associated nodes if button 1 is pressed, hold and released, respectively.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Scene Controller will send Basic Set command to the associated nodes if button 2 is pressed.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="5" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">NanoMote Quad will sendswitch multilevel set, the multilevel start level change and multilevel stop level change command to the associated nodes if button 2 is pressed, hold and released, respectively.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="6" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">NanoMote Quad will send Basic Set command to the associated nodes if button 3 is pressed.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="7" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">NanoMote Quad will sendswitch multilevel set, the multilevel start level change and multilevel stop level change command to the associated nodes if button 3 is pressed, hold and released, respectively.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="8" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">NanoMote Quad will send Basic Set command to the associated nodes if button 4 is pressed.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="9" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">NanoMote Quad will sendswitch multilevel set, the multilevel start level change and multilevel stop level change command to the associated nodes if button 4 is pressed, hold and released, respectively.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="32" size="1" default="20" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Level of low battery</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Define a battery level as the low battery.</lang></description><value from="10" to="50"><description><lang xml:lang="en">when the value is 10% to 50%,it will send a low battery command.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="41" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable send central scene notification.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">set of sending central scene notification or not</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">when value is 0, it can not be send scene notification;when the value is 1,it can be send central scene notification. </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="42" size="1" default="255" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Setting the duration value of the command switch multilevel.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Setting the duration value of the command switch multilevel.</lang></description><value from="-128" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">the higher the value,the long the duration value of the command switch multilevel</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="43" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/disable the buzzer alarm when battery is running low.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">set the buzzer alarm or not when battery is low</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">when the value is 0,the product will not allow the buzzer alarm when battery is running low;when the value is 1,the product will allow the buzzer alarm when battery is running low </lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18036041"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
