<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="024F"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="1003"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18046079</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The SE Devices Wheel Controller Z-Wave is a modular Wall-Box mountable control wheel, which is controllable over a Z-Wave Home Automation Network. The device can be added to and remote controlled via a Z-Wave Home Automation network. This product can be operated in any Z-Wave network with other Z-Wave certified devices from other manufacturers. All non-battery operated nodes within the network will act as repeaters regardless of vendor to increase reliability of the network.The Wheel Controller unit itself can be combined with a Back Unit hidden inside a wall-box to provide local control possibilities. It can also operate in a Stand-Alone mode, powered via a Cascade connector to another unit (Multifunction Switch or Wheel Controller).There are a variety of Back Units available for the Wheel, which can provide Local control functionality such as Relay Control and Dimming.The Wheel is backed by 4 push buttons, located at the Upper, Lower, Left and Right sides of the wheel. By pushing on these points of the wheel, the various functions of the wheel can be accessed and controlled.The Wheel can be rotated in a clockwise and counter clockwise direction to control the Light Level, adjust temperature settings for the Thermostat and issue Central Scene commands. The current operation is shown in the display at all times. When used as a Thermostat, the display will show information on thermostat operation when the device is Idle.</lang></description><productName>Wheel Controller</productName><brandName>SE Devices</brandName><productCode>FWC</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline - Supports MultichannelOnly local Light Zone changes are reported if Multichannel association is not used.Commands issued:- Basic Report: Reports Light Zone state and level changes- Central Scene Notification: Notifies activated Scenes- Thermostat Set-point report: When the Thermostat set-point is changed locally- Thermostat Mode Report: When the Thermostat mode is changed locally- Sensor Multilevel Report: Power Consumption and Air Temperature (if a sensor is connected)- Meter: Reports energy consumption- Device Reset Locally - Reports device Factory Reset</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls devices in Light Zone 1. Supports Multichannel Association.Commands Issued:- Basic Set: Controlled by Light Zone 1. Dimmer or Switch mapped Basic command values is configurable</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls devices in Light Zone 2. Supports Multichannel Association.Commands Issued:- Basic Set: Controlled by Light Zone 2. Dimmer or Switch mapped Basic command values is configurable</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls devices in Light Zone 3. Supports Multichannel Association.Commands Issued:- Basic Set: Controlled by Light Zone 3. Dimmer or Switch mapped Basic command values is configurable</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="5" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controls devices in Light Zone 4. Supports Multichannel AssociationCommands Issued:- Basic Set: Controlled by Light Zone 4. Dimmer or Switch mapped Basic command values is configurable</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="6" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enables control of external Heating Thermostats in the same heating zone.Commands Issued:- Thermostat Setpoint Set: Sent on local Thermostat Set-Point changes- Thermostat Mode Set: Sent on local Thermostat Mode changes</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="7" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enables the Thermostat to control Remote Heating Relays.Commands issued:- Basic Set: Value ON (255) or OFF (0), according to Thermostat Heating State changes.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18046079"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
