<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0085"/><productType value="0005"/><productId value="0012"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18036066</certNumber><rfFrequency>Australia and New Zealand</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">FAKRO AMZ Solar awning blind is a perfect combination of comfort of use and effective protection from heat. Due to the fact that the awning blind absorbs solar radiation before it reaches the glazing and emits the heat to the outside of the room, it constitutes much better protectction from tiresome heat in the sunny days than internal accessories. At the same time, it allows the ingress of natural light and ensures visual contact with the environment. FAKRO AMZ Solar is equipped with the algorithm which allows to operate the awning blind depending on the insolation level. It is also equipped with the Z-Wave remote control. In an emergency, the awning blind can be controlled by a service button located on the awning blind. The solar awning blind is powered by 12VDC battery pack built-in in the blinds cases powered by the solar panel. The AMZ Solar awning blind has three protections: - Maximum extension (encoder maximum position)- Completely rolled up (encoder minimum position)- Current limiting protecting the awning blind against damage and user against accidental injury resulting from the contact with moving elements of the awning blind.There are four association groups in FAKRO AMZ Solar awning blind:1. Life Linegroup for reporting a position of the awning blind after each stoppage and alarm reporting (overcurrent, damage encoders). A maximum 1 device can be in this group.2. Basic Repeatgroup used to transfer received basic commands to devices included in this group. A maximum 5 devices can be in this group. 3. Multilevel Repeatgroup used to transfer received multilevel commands to devices included in this group. A maximum 5 devices can be in this group. 4. Basic Controlgroup used to transfer received commands from the AMZ Solar (A, S mode) to devices included in this group. A maximum 5 devices can be in this group.Technical Parameters: Power voltage: 12V DCRated current: 1,4 ACurrent limit: YESSpeed: 23 r.p.mTemperature of usage: (-10 deg C) do (65 deg C) Supplying cable: 2 x 0,75 mm2</lang></description><productName>AMZ Solar</productName><brandName>FAKRO</brandName><productCode>AMZ Solar AU</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline - group for position reporting awning blind after each a stoppage and alarm reporting (overcurrent, damage encoders)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Repeatgroup used to transfer the received basic commands to the devices included in this group.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multilevel Repeatgroup used to transfer the received multilevel commands to the devices included in this group.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Controlgroup used to transfer the received commands from AMZ Solar (A, S mode) to the devices included in this group.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Mode Control</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The awning blind mode operate:0manual - control with the use of the remote control1semiautomatic - automatic closing and with the use of the remote control2automatic -automatic opening and closing and with the use of the remotecontrol</lang></description><value from="0" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 - manual, 1semiautomatic, 2automatic </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="12" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Calibrate</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Value 1calibratedValue 2discalibratedto enter the calibration mode must first time discalibrate and then calibrate.</lang></description><value from="1" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1-calibrate, 2-discalibrate</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="13" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">The End position</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">1FF go to maximum position2FF go to previous position </lang></description><value from="1" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1FF is maximum position, 2FF is previous position </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Season select</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Seasonof using awning blind1summer2winter</lang></description><value from="1" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1summer, 2winter</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="3" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Timer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The time after which the awning blindwill be open or close (depend on the season)</lang></description><value from="1" to="30"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 to 30 minutes</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="60" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Sensitivity</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Level of sun sensitivity at which the awning blind will open or close.</lang></description><value from="3" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3 to 100 procent</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18036066"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
