<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="024F"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="1013"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18046093</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Standalone 1-Pole Relay is exclusively Z-Wave controllable, and designed to handle loads up to 3000W and be concealed inside Wall Boxes. The Relay can be used to switch both Heat Sources and Light fixtures. The product also contains a fail-safe mechanism which will switch the relay ON and OFF at fixed intervals, in case communication from a controlling device is lost.The Relay measures the immediate and accumulated power consumption of an attached load, which is reported at fixed intervals.</lang></description><productName>Standalone Relay 1-Pole</productName><brandName>SE Devices</brandName><productCode>AR1P</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Lifeline group where all Root Device events are reported. All unsolicited Reports for the supported command classes will be issued to this group. Supports both normal and Multichannel Association.Commands Issued: - Sensor Multilevel Report - Reports Power Consumption and Temperatures - Meter - Reports power consumption to the Controller every 15 minutes. - Device Reset LocallyReports factory resets to the Controller</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Associated devices will be controlled according to local state changes. Supports Multichannel Association in addition to standard association. Command Issued: Basic Set</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="19" type="constant"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Hardware Combination Identifier</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">READ-ONLY: Byte which uniquely describes the combination of form factor and functionality for the current SE Devices unit. Always return 19 for this device.</lang></description><value from="19" to="19"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Hardware Combination Identifier</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="16" size="1" default="6" type="constant"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Functionaltiy Identifier</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">READ-ONLY: Provides an Identifier for the local device functionality, which is the same across all devices in the SEdevices product range.Always return 6 for 1-Pole Relays</lang></description><value from="6" to="6"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Functionaltiy Identifier</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="2" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Safety Activate Delay</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Safety Mode is activated after the configured number of seconds has elapsed. It will start by turning OFF the Back Unit when activated. A 0 value Disables Safety Mode. The MAX limit is 32767 seconds (9 hours, 6 minutes and 7 seconds)</lang></description><value from="0" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Safety Activation Delay</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="2" default="600" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Safety OFF Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The number of seconds to stay in OFF mode when Safety is activated. The Back unit turns ON when the timer have elapsed. If value is 0, the Back Unit will not turn back ON. The MAX limit is 32767 seconds (9 hours, 6 minutes and 7 seconds)</lang></description><value from="0" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Safety OFF Period</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="2" default="300" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Safety ON Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The number of seconds to stay in ON mode when Safety is activated. The Back Unit turns back OFF when the timer have elapsed (and continues to turn ON and OFF alternately). If value is 0, the Back Unit WILL NOT turn ON at all. The MAX limit is 32767 seconds (9 hours, 6 minutes and 7 seconds)</lang></description><value from="0" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Safety ON Period</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18046093"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
