<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="014A"/><productType value="0004"/><productId value="0002"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18056109</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Includes Brown &amp; White coversSleek design virtually disappearsEasy-to-open case requires no special toolsCase tamper protectionIdeal for double-hung windowUp to 3 year battery life on 1 CR123A lithium batteryUses rare earth magnet for up to 5/8th inch gap detectionIncludes white and brown cases</lang></description><productName>EU Z-WAVE DOOR WINDOW SENSOR</productName><brandName>Ecolink Intelligent Technology</brandName><productCode>H114101</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">This sensor has two Association groups of 5 nodes each. Group one is a lifeline group who will receive unsolicited messages relating to door/window open/close notifications, case tampering notifications, low-battery notifications, and sensor binary reports. </lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 is intended for devices that are to be controlled i.e. turned on or off (on only by default) with a Basic Set. On inclusion the controller should put its node ID in group 1 but not group 2.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Sending Basic Sets to Association group 2</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter 1 configures the sensor to send or not send Basic Set commands of 0x00 to nodes in Association group2 turning the devices off when the sensor is in a restored state i.e. the door is closed. By default the sensor does NOT send Basic Set commands of 0x00.</lang></description><value from="-1" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0x00 off, 0xFF on</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Sending sensor binary report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter 2 configures the sensor to either to send or not to send Sensor Binary Report commands to Association Group 1 when the sensor is faulted andrestored. If the controller is fully compatible with the Notification Command Class thereby making the Sensor Binary Reports redundant, the controller candisable the Sensor Binary Report Commands completely.</lang></description><value from="-1" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0x00 off, 0xFF on</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18056109"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
