<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0060"/><productType value="0012"/><productId value="0001"/><libType value="Enhanced 232 Slave"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18056122</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The EH403 is an outdoor security floodlight equipped with Z-Wave wireless communication capability. It features a PIR detector to detect motion through movement of heat sources and a lux sensor for determining brightness of its surroundings.When not connected to a Z-Wave network, EH403 is fully operational as a standalone security floodlight. During hours of darkness its PIR detector turns on the 20W floodlight when it detects movement in the protected area. Its built-in timer will then turn off the floodlight after a preset time has elapsed. During daylight hours, its lux sensor saves energy by deactivating the motion sensor and the floodlight. The lux level and the timer can be set through knobs on the device itself.When added into a Z-Wave network, EH403 communicates directly with other end devices such as smart plugs, or to report directly to a Z-Wave controller (usually a gateway). It alerts the controller when motion is detected and through Z-Wave commands, the controller can remotely turn on/off the floodlight at any time and be able to configure its lux level and timer setting.This product supports the S2 security protocol that uses encrypted Z-Wave Plus messages to communicate to other security-enabled Z-Wave Plus products. A security-enabled Z-Wave Plus Controller must be used in order to fully utilize the security features of this product.</lang></description><productName>Z-Wave Floodlight with Motion Detector</productName><brandName>Everspring</brandName><productCode>EH403-3</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Command Class: -Device Reset Locally Notification-Notification Report-Binary Report-Sensor Multilevel ReportGroup Name: Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Command Class:-Basic SetGroup Name: PIR Control</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="15" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">PIR Trigger Off period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Period to send Trigger Off command after PIR is triggered. Before this period expires, the PIR will not be able to detect any subsequent motion.</lang></description><value from="8" to="720"><description><lang xml:lang="en">PIR Trigger Off period can be set 8~720 secs.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="50" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Lux sensor threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lux level to activate the PIR. When the lux level falls below this threshold and the PIR gets triggered, the unit emits a Basic Set Command (Valus=0Xff) and turns on its floodlight. This overwrites the Lux level set by the Lux knob.</lang></description><value from="30" to="200"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lux sensor threshold can be set 30~200</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="2" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Lux auto report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Period to report Lux value.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1440"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lux auto report can be set 0~1440 minutes.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18056122"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
