<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0095"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0000"/><protoVersion value="05"/><protoSubVersion value="02"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-10050003</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">110V - 240V Circuit Breaker.QEES RETO Shell Switch Plus is a highly aesthetic Z-Wave-controlled 13A switch (EU frequency) designed to control a lamp or any other load type. QEES RETO Shell Switch Plus is a wirelessly controlled switch for retrofit installation that can also be operated locally by pushing the top cover. QEES Switch Power 13A design becomes more practical allowing the control to be done with several body parts (ex. foot, elbow, hip). QEES RETO Shell Switch Pluss software can be upgraded over the air, allowing the device to receive additional features or bug fixes through firmware updates and software apps. This is a unique feature of all QEES products and it facilitates a future-proof, contemporary and flexible infrastructure solution for the building. QEES RETO Shell Switch Plus is compatible with all Z-Wave certified devices from other manufacturers. It also acts as a repeater inside your Z-Wave network increasing the range for your remote control. As with all QEES products, QEES RETO Shell Switch Plus has a self-calibrating built-in power meter and can switch off devices that otherwise would consume power when not needed. </lang></description><productName>QEES Power EU</productName><brandName>QEES ApS</brandName><productCode/></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0086" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.qees.eu/products/plus-retrofit-series/turtle-shells/turtle-shell-relay-eu"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
