<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0258"/><productType value="0200"/><productId value="1025"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="81"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18076181</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">In the Z-Wave network communications, water sensor can work with any Z-Wave main controller. In the Z-Wave network communications, water sensor can send messages to the Z-Wave main controller, and realize association with other devices through the Z-Wave network. In the communication with the Z-Wave main controller, thewater sensor cansendmessages to the Z-Wave main controller, but it can notreceivemessages from the Z-Wave main controller. When the water sensor is triggered, the LED light keeps on and the buzzer will make sound. The water sensor sends messages to the Z-Wave main controller at the same time, the Z-Wave main controller will display the current status of water sensor. Water sensor is battery powered, is small and can be installed easily.</lang></description><productName>Water Leakage Detector</productName><brandName>Coolcam</brandName><productCode>NAS-WS02ZU</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 is lifeline group; all nodes which associated in this group will receive the messages sent bydevice through lifeline. Command Class:COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATIONCOMMAND_CLASS_SENSOR_BINARYCOMMAND_CLASS_BATTERYCOMMAND_CLASS_DEVICE_RESET_LOCALLYEvent:NOTIFICATION_REPORTSENSOR_BINARY_REPORTBATTERY_REPORTDEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 is controlling group, all nodes associated in this group will be controlled through BASIC_SETcommand by the device when device detects a water leakage event. Command Class:COMMAND_CLASS_BASICEvent:BASIC_SET</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18076181"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
