<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0369"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="81"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18066170</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">An open and flexible ecosystemConnectair uses the Z-Wave Plus technology, the most widely used wireless communication system in the world of connected devices. Whether it's heating appliances, lighting, door locks or any other electronic product, if the devices are compatible with Z-Wave or Z-Wave Plus, Connectair can integrate and operate them.An application to manage everythingTo manage your connected devices, use Connectair's simple, free, central and multiplatform interface. This allows you to manage directly from the Controller, your computer, your tablet or your smartphone the various features and connected devices in your ecosystem. The application is accessible from any place and at any time.Connectair is compatible with Windows, Chrome OS, iOS, MacOS and Android operating systems.Scenarios to simplify your lifeProgram a series of comfort and supervision scenarios to simplify your life. You want your lights to come on when you get home? Connectair allows you to do it in just a few clicks. Use your connected devices, such as lighting, appliances, or heating to their full potential.Control your Convectair heating remotelyAdjust the comfort of your home according to your schedule and lifestyle. Connectair allows you to easily and remotely control and make changes to your Convectair units. Adjust your heaters in Comfort, Eco, Frost-protection or Standby mode or adjust the set temperature according to your needs.Convectair compatible unitsConnectair is currently compatible with the Allegro II and Apro (240V only) models. The Allegro II requires the use of the Connectair Module. The Apero requires a pilot wires connection to an Allegro II equipped with a Connectair Module.An evolving ecosystemThanks to its cloud capabilities, Connectair is constantly adapting to stay on the cutting edge. Receive updates on new products, new features, or interface enhancements directly on your devices such as your smartphone.SecureZ-Wave Plus, the protocol used by Connectair, is highly secure to ensure a safe communication between connected devices and the controller. In addition, the Connectair Module is equipped with a manual switch that prevents anyone from remotely shutting down your Convectair heaters.Convectairs warranty 2 years against all manufacturing defectsDue to our commitment to research and development, we reserve the right to change specifications without notice.</lang></description><productName>Controller</productName><brandName>Connectair</brandName><productCode>CW7</productCode></deviceDescription><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18066170"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
