<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0159"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0053"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18066155</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Qubino Flush Shutter DC is ideal for controlling the 1224V DC motors of blinds, rollers, shades, venetian blinds and similar sunscreens. You can control it either remotely through the Z-Wave network or through wall switches. It also measures power consumption and supports the connection of a digital temperature sensor.</lang></description><productName>Flush Shutter DC</productName><brandName>QUBINO</brandName><productCode>ZMNHOD3</productCode></deviceDescription><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="15"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic on/off (triggered at change of the input I1 state and reflecting its state)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic on/off (triggered at change of the input I2 state and reflecting its state)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic on/off (triggered at sensing moving direction of roller: up=FF, down=0) </lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="5" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic on/off (triggered at reaching roller position: bottom=FF, top=0) </lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="6" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic on/off (triggered at reaching roller position: bottom=FF, not bottom=0) </lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="7" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multilevel set (triggered at changes of value of the Flush Shutter DC position)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="8" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multilevel set (triggered at changes of value of slats tilting position)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="9" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multilevel sensor report (triggered at change of temperature sensor</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="10" size="2" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Activate/deactivate functions ALL ON / ALL OFF </lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Flush Shutter DCs module responds to commands ALL ON / ALL OFF that may be sent by the primary or secondary controller within the Z-Wave network. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ALL ON is not active, ALL OFF is not active</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ALL ON is not active ALL OFF active</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ALL ON active ALL OFF is not active</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ALL ON active, ALL OFF active</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="110" size="2" default="32536" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature sensor offset settings</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set value is added to or subtracted from the actually measured value to adjust the temperature report sent by an external sensor (sold separately). This parameter only applies to the degrees temperature unit (the Fahrenheit unit is currently not supported).</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">value from 0.1 degrees Celsius to 10.0 degrees Celsius is added to actual measured temperature. </lang></description></value><value from="1001" to="1100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">value from -0.1 degrees Celsius to -10.0 degrees Celsius is subtracted to actual measured temperature.</lang></description></value><value from="32536" to="32536"><description><lang xml:lang="en">offset is 0.0C</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="120" size="1" default="5" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature sensor reporting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If an external digital temperature sensor (sold separately) is connected to the module, it reports temperature readings based on the threshold defined in this parameter. This parameter only applies to the degrees temperature unit (the Fahrenheit unit is currently not supported).</lang></description><value from="1" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 0,1 degrees Celsius - 12,7 degrees Celsius, step is 0,1 degrees Celsius</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 0,5 degrees Celsius</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="40" size="1" default="10" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power reporting in Watts on power change for Q1 or Q2</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose by how much power consumption needs to increase or decrease to be reported. Values correspond to percentages so if 10 is set (by default), the module will report any power consumption changes of 10% or more compared to the last reading. NOTE: Power consumption needs to increase or decrease by at least 1 Watt to be reported, REGARDLESS of percentage set in this parameter.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> reporting disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 1% - 100% Reporting enabled. Power report is send (push) only when actual power (in Watts) in real time changes for more than set percentage comparing to previous actual power in Watts, step is 1%.</lang></description></value><value from="10" to="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">default value</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="42" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power reporting in Watts by time interval for Q1 or Q2</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The set value refers to the time interval with which the power consumption in Watts is reported (032767 seconds). If 0 is entered (by default), energy consumption reports will not be sent to the controller.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">reporting disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 1 second - 32767 seconds. Reporting enabled, power report is send with </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="71" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Operating modes</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose between the two operating modes. If the venetian mode is selected, an additional widget/endpoint will be displayed on the UI interface, which can be used to control the tilt position of the slats. If the Shutter mode is selected, this additional endpoint is hidden.NOTE1: After the value of this parameter is changed, first exclude module (without setting parameters to their default values), wait at least 30s and then reinclude the module!</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">shutter mode</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">venetian mode (up/down and slate rotation)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="72" size="2" default="150" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Slats tilting full turn time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set the time, required by the slats, to make a full turn (180 degrees). NOTE: If the set time is too long and a full turn was already performed, the device will start to move up or down for the remaining time.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">tilting time disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> = 0,01seconds - 327,67 seconds</lang></description></value><value from="150" to="150"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 1,5 seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="73" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Slats position</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose the position of the slats after up/down movement (activated through the Z-Wave controller or the push-buttons) is completed. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Slats return to previously set position only in case of Z-wave control (not valid for limit switch positions)</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Slats return to previously set position in case of Z-wave control, push-button operation or when the lower limit switch is reached</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="74" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Motor moving up/down time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the time, required by the Shutter DC motor, to completely open or completely close the attached shutters.After the set time passes, the motor stops (relay goes to the off state).NOTE: It is important that the reference position, for setting the moving time, is always when the Shutter is at its lowest position!Set parameter 74 to 0 and move the Shutter (using the up/down push-buttons or the main controller UI) to the lowest desired position. When the Shutter reaches this position, set the parameter 74 to the duration, required by the Shutter, to completely open or completely close the attached shutters. At this point the Shutter can be moved up (open), but can't be moved down, because this position is already set as its lowest position.To change the defined lowest position of the Shutter below the one, which is already defined (manual recalibration), the parameter 74 must be set to 0 and the procedure, which is described above, should be repeated.In case the Shutter operates using limit switches, but the user still wants to control the opening/closing position with time, this is still possible. If a time duration, which is longer than the opening/closing time of the shutters in real time (limited by the limit switches), is set, the Shutter will stop at the limit switches, but the module relay will switch it off after a defined time, not by the limit switch of the Shutter. Take into consideration that in this condition, positioning the shutters with the slider (through the UI) will not display the correct position of the Shutter.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">moving time disabled (working with limitswitches)</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 0,1seconds - 3276,7seconds. After that time motor is stopped (relay goes to off state)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="76" size="1" default="6" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Motor operation detection</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Define the power consumption threshold at the end positions. Based on this value, the device will know, that the shutters reached the limit switches. </lang></description><value from="5" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= (0,5W - 10W), step is 0,1W. </lang></description></value><value from="6" to="6"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 0,6W</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="78" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Forced Shutter DC calibration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">By changing the value of this parameter from 0 to 1, the Shutter enters the calibration mode. For further information about the calibration process, please see section 9.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">default value</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">start calibration process (when calibration process is finished, completing full cycle - up, down and up, set the parameter 78 (Forced Shutter calibration) value back to 0</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="85" size="1" default="8" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power consumption max delay time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Define the maximum time before the power consumption of the motor, after one of the relays is switched ON, is read from the device. If there is no power consumption during the set time (motor not connected, damaged or requires longer time to start, motor at the end position), the relay will switch OFF. This time is defined by entering it manually. </lang></description><value from="3" to="50"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 0,3seconds - 5seconds (100ms resolution)</lang></description></value><value from="8" to="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 800ms</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="86" size="1" default="8" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power consumption at limit switch delay time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the maximum time after which the active output will switch off, due to reaching a limit switch. When power consumption is below the specified power threshold, defined in the parameter no. 76, the set time duration will have to pass in order for the output to turn off.</lang></description><value from="3" to="50"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 0,3seconds - 5seconds (100ms resolution)</lang></description></value><value from="8" to="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">8 = 800ms</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="90" size="1" default="5" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Time delay for next motor movement</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the minimum time duration between successive motor movements (minimum time after which the motor is switched off and on again). </lang></description><value from="1" to="30"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 0,1seconds - 3seconds (100ms resolution)</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">= 500ms</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18066155"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
