<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="009E"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="05"/><protoSubVersion value="02"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="01"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-10040002</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Portable Controller with 4 GroupsThe QEES MyKey is a unique and stylish wireless key fob for personalized control. Since here, at QEES, we know that aesthetics is important to the customer, we managed to combine high-end technology with an exquisite unique design without compromising the functionality. MyKey is an easy to use remote controller with advanced functionality made simple. QEES MyKey can be configured directly into a smart home network with other QEES products or with Z-Wave certified devices from other manufacturers.It will act as a Z-Wave controller in the configuration of the network, meaning that it can build the network, as opposed to slave devices. With the help of four buttons QEES MyKey gives you opportunity to create up to four different home automation setups and control them easy from distance. Once you bought several QEES products you will be able, with the help of MyKey and the application PC Software Update, to upgrade your products firmware over the air gaining access to new features as they will be implemented and released.Z-Wave-controller4 programmable groupsLED action feedback (multi-color RGB)Re-chargeable batteryMicro-USB charge portStrap/key ring featureUpgradeable device softwareWhite or black; other colors on request</lang></description><productName>AI Ring US (QEES)</productName><brandName>QEES ApS</brandName><productCode>0201002 v1.13</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0084" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.qees.eu/products/plus-retrofit-series/remoteseries/product/77/22/Plus-Retrofit-Series/RETO-Remote/qees-mykey-us"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
