<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0315"/><productType value="0202"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="81"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18096237</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">ZL-LD-100 is designed to detect and alert any water leaks in residential or commercial buildings. ZL-LD-100 features an audible buzzer in addition to a wireless alert to your controller providing early notification of water leaks before major damage occurs. - Water sensing cable may be placed anywhere where there is a risk of a leak, horizontal (oor, attic) or vertical (wall, along pipes), providing 3D capability to sense the leak.- Senses as little as couple of drops of water (0.25ml0.5ml)- Provides hundreds of times more coverage vs. traditional single point sensors that only detect leaks in a very localized area.- Quickly senses water leaks (every 400msec with micro USB power supply, every 60 sec. with battery) before expensive damage occurs.- LD-100 reports local temperature once every 60 minutes on battery, when using micro USB power supply it can be set using conguration parameter 3.- Built-in audible buzzer sounds when water is detected.- Includes 4-foot-long sensing cable that senses water on any part of the cable.- Water sensing cable extend-able up to 150 feet with available extensions.- Powered by 3 x AAA batteries (not included) or standard 5V micro USB power supply (not included).</lang></description><productName>Water Leak Detector</productName><brandName>ZLINK</brandName><productCode>ZL-LD-100</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1. BATTERY_REPORT2. NOTIFICATION_REPORT3. SENSOR_MULTILEVEL_REPORT4. DEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION5. Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2: Basic Set, you can associate up to ve Z-Wave devices to Group 2. LD-100 will send a Basic Set to the associated devices, for example, turning on lights or engaging the water auto shut-o valve, when water is detected. </lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="2" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Water detection beep frequency</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter 2 is for the beep interval when on battery power and on USB power during the time water is detected.0= every 10 minutes1= every 5 minutes2= every 30 minutes</lang></description><value from="0" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter 2 is for the beep interval when on battery power and on line power during the time water is detected.0= every 10 minutes 1= every 5 minutes 2= every 30 minutes</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="60" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature reporting interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter 3 defines the temperature interval of reporting to the controller on line power in seconds, the default value is 60.</lang></description><value from="30" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter 3 defines the temperature interval of reporting to the controller on line power in seconds, the default value is 60.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Notification buzzer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The buzzer may be disabled when detecting water on line power or battery, using parameter 4, the default value is set to enabled.</lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The buzzer may be disabled when detecting water on line power or battery, using parameter 4, the default value is set to enabled.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18096237"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
