<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="040D"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18096229</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Delaney Hardwares ZW300 Touchscreen Smartlock offers convenience and security for residential entry doors. Entry is made via touchscreen code, mobile app, or mechanical key. With Delaneys smart home control app, a homeowner can manage who is entering their home from anywhere. ANSI Grade 3 lock with motor-driven deadbolt Keypad accommodates thirty user codes of four to eight digits, and a single-use code, with code-probing prevention and disablement after five attempts (warned with beeps and LED and then 45-seconds downtime) Delaney app utilizes Z-Wave Plus via 128-bit AES encryption, mesh networking technology, and history log. It integrates with other Z-Wave devices such as doorbells with cameras, door and window sensors, outlet controls, heat and smoke sensors, thermostats, and water leak sensors via a security-enabled Z-Wave hub, which conveniently connects through your home WiFi, or plugs into your modem.Configurable auto-locking (from 10-99 seconds)Vacation mode with time-configurable deactivation during which all user codes are disabled such that only the mechanical key.ANSI A156.25 compliance (water, dust, corrosion resistance)Easy installation in standard doors with just a screwdriver (no hard wiring)</lang></description><productName>Smartlock</productName><brandName>Delaney Hardware</brandName><productCode>ZW300</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18096229"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
