<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0364"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18096247</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">AXIS T8341-EUR PIR Motion Sensor is a wireless sensor which provides motion detection both day and night. With its support for wireless input/output connectivity, the PIR motion sensor can communicate wirelessly with AXIS M5065 PTZ Network camera or other connected Z-Wave Plus controllers, creating a small security solution with less cabling. Thanks to its integrated wireless I/O connectivity, AXIS T8341-EUR enables flexible installation as the sensor can easily be moved and adapted to your needs. </lang></description><productName>PIR Motion Sensor</productName><brandName>Axis Communications </brandName><productCode>T8341-EUR</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Association with 1 node.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Association with 4 nodes.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="99" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic set level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">When a Basic Set Command is sent and contains a value, the receiver will process it. For example, a lamp module would receive a Basic Set command which determines the dim level.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic set level can be set 1~99.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="6" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Sensitivity level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">For optimal efficiency, it is recommended to test the detectors response to movements from the farthest end of the coverage area when you use it for the first time. If movements cannot be detected accurately, simply adjust the sensitivity level with the Configuration Parameter #3. This parameter can be configured with a value from 1 to 10, where 1 means low sensitivity and 10 means highest sensitivity.</lang></description><value from="1" to="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Sensitivity level can be set 1~10.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="2" default="180" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Re-trigger interval setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The configuration parameter used to adjust the re-trigger interval after the detector has been triggered as configuration parameter #4. No response will be made during this interval if a movement is detected. The time interval can be set between 5 seconds to 3,600 seconds.</lang></description><value from="5" to="3600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Re-trigger interval can be set 5~3600 seconds.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="20" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Lux level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">You can set a percentage for the lux level which determines when the light sensor will be activated. If the ambient illumination drops below the set percentage, and a person moves across or within the protected area, the detector will emit a Z-Wave ON command (i.e. Basic Set command (Value = Basic Set Level)) to the controller and activate connected modules and lighting. The percentage can be set between 1% to 100%.</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lux level can be set 1~100%.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="2" default="15" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">On-off duration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The on-off duration setting can be useful if the detector is connected to a module or lighting. The duration determines how long the module/lighting should stay ON. For instance, a Lamp Module turns off 100 secs after it has been turned on. The duration can beconfigured to last between 5 to 3600 seconds.</lang></description><value from="5" to="3600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">On-off duration ca be set 5~3600 seconds.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18096247"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
