<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0096"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0001"/><libType value="03"/><protoVersion value="05"/><protoSubVersion value="02"/><appVersion value="02"/><appSubVersion value="37"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="31"/><specificClass value="01"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-11060002</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">NorthQ has developed a small Power Reader that can be easily installed on existing electronic or mechanical meters in order to visualize electricity consumption in private homes. The meter reading solution is based on the Z-Wave wireless standard, which is ideal for controlling automation products within the home.The product consists of 3 parts: a Power Reader, a battery-powered wireless transmitter and a USB receiver. Electricity data is transferred to a chosen PC every 15 minutes, where it can then be visualized in the form of graphs, enabling customers to keep track of their electricity consumption (in kWh and in local currency), and monitor their CO2 emissions, etc. It is also possible to receive real-time measurements in order to investigate how much each individual appliance uses in active or standby mode.Furthermore, it is possible to enter a budget for how much you want to consume in EUR or kWh per year. The NorthQ eGadget on the screen continuously monitors and updates the electricity consumption data to indicate whether you are under or over budget. You are then able to compare your electricity consumption in the current year with that in previous years. It is also possible to compare the consumption in your current home with other types of homes, e.g. apartments, houses, villas, etc. </lang></description><productName>NorthQ Power Reader &amp; Power Manager</productName><brandName>NorthQ APS</brandName><productCode>NQ-92021</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0084" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://northq.com/qpower/"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
