<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0293"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0113"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18106271</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Pebble from Hogar Controls is a wireless touch button that combines elegant design and functionality into a simple, personalized device to control everything in your home. Enabled with a smart touch interface, this suave, compact device can do much more than your run-of-the-mill remote control ever could. Easily attach the Pebble on any glass, wooden or metal surface, or carry around in your pocket to control smart lighting, music, shades, thermostats and much more in your smart home or ofce.It is a compact, battery-powered, Z-wave Plus compatible device that allows you to control various devices through the Z-wave network. As it is based on Z-Wave communication technology, the device can be controlled remotely from anywhere using the internet.When paired with the HC Pro, our smart home controller, the Pebble lets you design, set and activate up to 9 personalized scenes with different gestures like touch, tap, double tap, press, press and hold, swipe left, swipe right, swipe up, swipe down, swipe clockwise, swipe anticlockwise.Set the ambiance for date night, wake up to your own personal mix of actions, or have the house locked and secured before you go to bed. Imagine your home at your ngertips because, with Pebble, it is just a matter of touch-and-go.</lang></description><productName>Hogar Pebble</productName><brandName>Hogar Controls</brandName><productCode>HC-TB-ZW</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Name: LifelineCommands:- Device Reset Locally Notification - Battery Report - Central Scene Notification</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Name: Basic On-OffCommands:- Basic SetWhen Single touch: device send Basic Set ON to 2nd association group.When Double touch: device send Basic Set OFF to 2nd association group.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18106271"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
