<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0293"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="4410"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="81"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18116294</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Hogar 1 Touch Panel Dimmer is perfect for anywhere you would like to switch the light on or off with the added advantage of pressing it for longer and dimming the light from 100 % to 10% or vice versa. The smart touch dimmer is compatible with all types of incandescent bulbs and dimmable LEDs.Featuring a stunning glass face with an advanced capacitive touch sensor, all you need to do is just use a finger for full dimming control and for turning your lights on and off. Tap the back-lit touch button on the panel to switch on or off, and long-press the same button to smoothly dim the lights. This 1 Touch Panel Dimmer ensures that the brightness intensity set is achieved without any loss.The Hogar 1 Touch Panel Dimmer can operate either independently or as a part of the Hogar smart home automation system, and even with any other certified Z-Wave home automation system. It is an extremely easy-to-use panel that installs in a standard BS 2 gang box. Its operating capabilities include a bi-stable mode, a relay mode or touch pulse mode for scene control with a maximum load current of 8 amp. It communicates with the Hogar smart home automation system using the Z-Wave wireless communication protocol.</lang></description><productName>1 Touch Panel Dimmer</productName><brandName>Hogar Controls</brandName><productCode>HTP-1SD</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Name: LifelineCommand:- Device Reset Locally Notification- Switch MultiLevel Report</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18116294"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
