<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0159"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="0054"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18116325</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Smart Plug 16A controls on/off function for the connected device. It also measures power consumption of the connected device according to the principle of fast sampling of voltage and current signals. A built-in microprocessor calculates energy and power from the measured signals.</lang></description><productName>Smart Plug 16A</productName><brandName>QUBINO</brandName><productCode>ZMNHYD1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lifeline - Supports the following command classes: Device Reset Locally: triggered upon request Meter Report: triggered according to Configuration parameters 40 and 42 Notification Report: triggered on overload/overcurrent or according to Configuration parameters 70, 71 and 72 Switch Binary Report: triggered upon request or according to Configuration parameters 11 and 12</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Plug Status - Supports the following command classes: Basic set: triggered at change of relay state</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Plug Threshold - Supports the following command classes: Basic set: triggered at change of active power in combination with Configuration parameters 50, 51 and 52</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="11" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 11 - Turn Smart plug 16A Off Automatically with Timer </lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 11 - Turn Smart plug 16A Off Automatically with Timer If Smart plug 16A is ON, you can schedule it to turn OFF automatically after a period defined in this parameter. The timer is reset to zero each time the device receives an ON command, either remotely (from the gateway (hub) or associated device) or locally from the switch.Values (size is 2 byte dec):default value 00 - Auto OFF Disabled 1 - 32535 = 1 - 32535 seconds. Auto OFF timer enabled for a given number of seconds.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Auto OFF Disabled </lang></description></value><value from="1" to="32535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 - 32535 seconds. Auto OFF timer enabled for a given number of seconds.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="12" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 12 - Turn Smart plug 16A On Automatically with Timer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If Smart plug 16A is OFF, you can schedule it to turn ON automatically after a period of time defined in this parameter. The timer is reset to zero each time the device receives an OFF command, either remotely (from the gateway (hub) or associated device) or locally from the switch.Values (size is 2 byte dec):default value 00 - Auto ON Disabled 1 - 32535 = 1 - 32535 seconds. Auto ON timer enabled- for a given amount of seconds.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Auto ON Disabled </lang></description></value><value from="1" to="32535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 - 32535 seconds. Auto ON timer enabled- for a given amount of seconds.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="30" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 30 - Restore on/off status for Smart plug 16A after power failure</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter determines if on/off status is saved and restored for the Smart plug 16A after power failure.Values (size is 1 byte dec):default value 00 - Device saves last on/off status and restores it after a power failure.1 - Device does not save on/off status and does not restore it after a power failure, it remains off.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Device saves last on/off status and restores it after a power failure.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Device does not save on/off status and does not restore it after a power failure, it remains off.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="40" size="1" default="20" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 40Watt Power Consumption Reporting Threshold for Smart plug 16A</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose by how much power consumption needs to increase or decrease to be reported. Values correspond to percentages, so if 20 is set (by default), the device will report any power consumption changes of 20% or more compared to the last reading. Values (size is 1 byte dec):default value 20 0 - Power consumption reporting disabled 1 - 100 = 1% - 100% Power consumption reporting enabled. New value is reported only when Wattage in real time changes by more than the percentage value set in this parameter compared to the previous Wattage reading, starting at 1% (the lowest value possible).Power consumption needs to increase or decrease by at least 1 Watt to be reported, REGARDLESS of percentage set in this parameter.NOTE: When reporting Watts, module will automatically report also [V] (Voltage) and [A] (Amperes) </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Power consumption reporting disabled </lang></description></value><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1% - 100% Power consumption reporting enabled. New value is reported only when Wattage in real time changes by more than the percentage value set in this parameter compared to the previous Wattage reading, starting at 1% (the lowest value possible).</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="42" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 42Watt Power Consumption Reporting Time Threshold for Smart plug 16A Load</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set value refers to the time interval with which power consumption in Watts is reported (3032535 seconds).Values (size is 2 byte dec):default value 00 - Power consumption reporting on time interval disabled30 - 32535 = 30 - 32535 seconds. Power consumption reporting enabled. Report is sent according to time interval (value) set here. The device is reporting the following values (if there was a change): W, V and A.NOTE: The energy consumption (kWh) is reported regardless of the values, set in the parameters 40 and 42. The energy consumption will be reported, when it increases for at least 0,1 kWh.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Power consumption reporting on time interval disabled</lang></description></value><value from="30" to="32535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">30 - 32535 seconds. Power consumption reporting enabled. Report is sent according to time interval (value) set here. </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="50" size="2" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 50Down value</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lower power threshold used in parameter no. 52. Values (size is 2 byte dec):default value 30 = 30 W04000 = 0W4000 W Down value cannot be higher or equal to the value specified in parameter no. 51. If the set value is higher or equal to the value in parameter 51, the set command is ignored.NOTE: if parameter no. 50 value is 100W, if measured power is lower than 100W, the association is sent.Power threshold step is 1W</lang></description><value from="0" to="4000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0W4000 W power threshold</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="51" size="2" default="50" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 51Up value</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Upper power threshold used in parameter no. 52Values (size is 2 byte dec):default value 50 = 50 W04000 = 0 W4000WUp value cannot be lower or equal to the value specified in the parameter no. 50. If the set value is lower or equal to the value in parameter 50, the set command is ignored.NOTE: If parameter no. 51 value is 200W. If measured power is higher than 200W the association is sent.Power threshold step is 1W.</lang></description><value from="0" to="4000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 W4000 W power threshold</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="52" size="1" default="6" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 52 - Action in case of exceeding defined power values (parameters 50 and 51)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter defines the way 3rd association group devices are controlled, depending on the current power loadValues (size is 1 byte dec):default value 60function inactive1turn the associated devices on, once the power drops below Down value (parameter no. 50)2turn the associated devices off, once the power drops below Down value (parameter no. 50)3turn the associated devices on, once the power rises above Up value (parameter no. 51)4turn the associated devices off, once the power rises above Up value (parameter no. 51)51 and 4 combined. Turn the associated devices on, once the power drops below Down value (parameter no. 50). Turn the associated devices off, once the power rises above Up value (parameter no. 51).62 and 3 combined. Turn the associated devices off, once the power drops below Down value (parameter 50). Turn the associated devices on, once the power rises above Up value (parameter no. 51).</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function inactive</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn the associated devices on, once the power drops below Down value (parameter no. 50)</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn the associated devices off, once the power drops below Down value (parameter no. 50)</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn the associated devices on, once the power rises above Up value (parameter no. 51)</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn the associated devices off, once the power rises above Up value (parameter no. 51)</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 and 4 combined. Turn the associated devices on, once the power drops below Down value (parameter no. 50). Turn the associated devices off, once the power rises above Up value (parameter no. 51).</lang></description></value><value from="6" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2 and 3 combined. Turn the associated devices off, once the power drops below Down value (parameter 50). Turn the associated devices on, once the power rises above Up value (parameter no. 51).</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="70" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 70 - Overload safety switch</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The function allows for turning off the controlled device in case of exceeding the defined power for more than 3 seconds. Controlled device can be turned back on by S-button or sending a control frame. By default this function is inactive. Values (size is 2 byte dec):default value 014000 = 1 W4000W0 = function not activeNOTE: This functionality is not an overload safety protection, please check installation note for details.In case of overload the following message will be send towards the controller:COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATION_V5The Alarm V1 type field set to 0x00Notification Type 0x08 and 0x08 (Overload detected)NOTE: Regardless of the value set in this parameter the overcurrent protection is always active and can not be disabled. </lang></description><value from="1" to="4000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 W4000W</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function not active</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="71" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 71Power threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This functions allows setting the power threshold for triggering the Program started notification. When the threshold will be reached the notification will let the user know that the device connected to the smart plug started working.Values (size is 2 byte dec):default value 014000 = 1 W4000W0 = function not activeWhen the threshold is reached the following message will be send towards the controller:COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATION_V5The Alarm V1 type field set to 0x00Notification Type 0x0C and 0x01 (Program started)</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function not active</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="4000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 W4000W</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="72" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 72Time interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This function allows setting the time interval for triggering the Program completed notification. When the active power will fall below the power threshold set in parameter 71, the time interval will start and when it will expire the notification will let the user know that the device connected to the smart plug finished working. The time interval is useful for the devices that have pause intervals during operations. Values (size is 1 byte dec):default value 10125 = 0125 minutes0 = immediate sending of notification when active power drops bellow threshold set in parameter 71When the the time interval expires the following message will be send towards the controller:COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATION_V5The Alarm V1 type field set to 0x00Notification Type 0x0C and 0x03 (Program completed)</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">immediate sending of notification when active power drops bellow threshold set in parameter 71</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="125"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0125 minutes</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="73" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 73Turn Smart Plug OFF</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This function allows turning the Smart Plug output to OFF once the time interval is expired and the Program completed notification is sent to the controller. Values (size is 1 byte dec):default value 00function disabled1turn OFF relay once the notification Program completed is sent</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn OFF relay once the notification Program completed is sent</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="74" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter no. 74Enable/disable LED</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This function allows enabling or disabling the Smart Plug LED. In case the user doesnt want the LED indicator he can turn it OFF with this parameter.NOTE: if an overload or overcurrent occurs the red LED will still turn ON regardless of the value set in this parameter.Values (size is 1 byte dec):default value 10LED is disabled1LED is enabled</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED is disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED is enabled</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18116325"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
