<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="013C"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0029"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18116321</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">This plug-in ON/OFF switch PAN16 is a security enabled Z-Wave Plus product, based on Z-Wave Plus technology. The device will enable security mode automatically if the controller supports security mode, too. Z-Wave PlusTM enabled devices displaying the Z-Wave PlusTM logo can also be used with it regardless of the manufacturer, and can also be used in other manufacturers Z-WaveTM enabled networks. Remote On/Off control of the connected load is possible with other manufacturers wireless Controller. Each switch is designed to act as a repeater. Repeaters will re-transmit the RF signal to ensure that the signal is received by its intended destination by routing the signal around obstacles and radio dead spots. Because PAN16 supports Security Command Class, it can learn with a Secured enabled Z-Wave controller to fully utilize the device. Its functionality and supported command classes is identical when included as a secure and non-secure device. Thisplug-inON/OFFswitchisabletodetectinstancewattage(3000W/230Vac) (13Ampere)andoverloadcurrent(14.5Awithresistiveload) of connected lights or appliances. When detecting overload state, the Switch will be disabled and its On/Off button will be lockout of which LED will flash quickly.However, unplug and re-connect the switch will reset its overload condition to normal status. Adding to Z-WaveTM Network In the front casing, there is an On/Off button with LED indicator which is used to toggle switch on and off or carry out inclusion, exclusion, reset or association. When first power is applied, its LED flashes on and off alternately and repeatedly at 0.5 second intervals. It implies that it has not been assigned a node ID and start auto inclusion. Auto Inclusion The function of auto inclusion will be executed as long as the switch does not have Node ID and just plug the switch into a wall outlet. Note: Auto inclusion timeout is 2 minute during which the node information of explorer frame will be emitted once several seconds. Unlike inclusion function as shown in the table below, the execution of auto inclusion is free from pressing the On/Off button on the Switch. </lang></description><productName>Smart energy plug in switch</productName><brandName>Philio</brandName><productCode>PAN16-3</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus LifelineThe Switch can be set to send reports to associated Z-Wave devices. It supports one association group with one node support for Grouping 1. For group 1, the Switch will report its latest status to Z-Wave Controller. Grouping 1 includes, SWITCH_BINARY_REPORT, METER_REPORT, ALARM_REPORT, DEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION. </lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="720" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Watt Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If the setting is configured for 1hour (set value =720), the PAN16 will report its instant power consumption every 1 hour to Group1 node. The maximum interval to report its instant power consumption is 45 hours (5s*32767/3600=45hr). </lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">720*5s=3600s=1 hour </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="11" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Manual Switch Report mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever PAN16 manually switch on or off, it will send BINARY_SWITCH_REPORT to the node of group1. The default setting is Enable the function. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 : Disable</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 : Enable </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="6" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">KWH Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If the setting is configured for 1hour (set value=6), the PAN16 will report its Accumulated Power Consumption (KW/h) every 1 hour to Group1 node. The maximum interval to report its Accumulated Power Consumption (KW/h) is 227.55 days (10min*32767/1440=227.55 days).</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">6*10min=1 hour </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="2" default="1300" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of current for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the current of load over the preset threshold value, if the setting value is 1300, when the load current of Relay1 over this value, PAN16 will send current meter report to warn the Group1 node, the Range of the setting value is from 10 to 1300,and the default value is 1300.</lang></description><value from="10" to="1300"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1300*0.01A = 13A </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="2" default="10000" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of KWh for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the KWh of load over the preset threshold value, If the setting value is 10000, when the Accumulated Power Consumption of Relay1 over this value, PAN16 will send KWH meter report to warn the Group1 node, minimum value is 1KWh and default value is 10000 kWh.</lang></description><value from="1" to="10000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">10000*1KWH=10000KWH</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Restore switch state mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever the AC power return from lost, PAN16 will restore the switch state which could be SWITCH OFFLAST SWITCH STATESWITCH ON. The default setting is LAST SWITCH STATE. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 : Switch off </lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 : Last switch state </lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2 : Switch on</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Mode of switch off function</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">When the mode of switch On/Off is set to 0, any command of switch off will be disabled and the On/Off function of include button will be disabled. The default setting is enable mode. When manual On/Off function is disabled, the RF command can only switch On but not Off. This is useful function for keeping the device in switch on state.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 : Disable</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 : Enable</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED indication mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">1. Show Switch StateWhen switch is on, LED is on. When switch is off, LED is off. The default setting is Show Switch State. 2. Show Night modeWhen switch is on, LED is off. When switch is off, LED is on. 3. One Flash modeWhen the state of switch changes, LED will be on only one second, then LED keeps off. </lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 : Show switch state </lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2 : Show night mode</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3 : One flash mode</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto off timer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever PAN16 switches to on, the auto off timer begin to count down. After the timer decrease to zero, it will switch to off automatically. However if Auto off timer is set as 0, the auto off function will be disabled. The default setting is 0. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 : Disable auto offfunction </lang></description></value><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1s ~ 32767s </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">RF off command mode </lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever a switch off command, BASIC_SETBINARY_SWITCH_SETSWITCH_ALL_OFF, is received, it could be interpreted as 4 variety of commands. 1. Switch OffIt switches to OFF state. The default setting is Switch Off. 2. IgnoreThe switch off command will be ignored. 3. Switch ToggleIt switches to the inverse of current state. 4. Switch OnIt switches to ON state. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 : Switch off</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 : Ignore </lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2 : Switch toggle </lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3 : Switch on</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18116321"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
