<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0346"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0101"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="80"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18066168</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The new Ring Protect security system adds a simple, smart, affordable security solution for your home. Set up your Protect Security Kit, sign up for 24/7 professional security monitoring, add accessory devices to build your system, and control access to your devices through Locations and Users. Ring Protect adds a ring of security inside your home for enhanced peace of mind and protection. The Ring Protect system together with Ring's video doorbells, cameras, and accessories, creates a stronger-than-ever Ring of Security that protects your home both inside and out. Whether youre on vacation halfway around the world, or just too busy with the kids upstairs, Ring lets you watch over your home from anywhere. Because with Ring, youre always home.Ring Features:- High-definition video- Wide-angle camera lens- Two-way talk- Advanced motion detection- Infrared night vision- Video recording- Lifetime purchase protection- 24/7 Professional monitoring- Monitor your doors and windows</lang></description><productName>Ring Alarm Base Station</productName><brandName>Ring</brandName><productCode>Ring Base Station</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">This base station has Group 1 is the Lifeline group, which can hold one devices. Base station will send device reset locally notification to this group.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18066168"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
