<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="021F"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="0201"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="61"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18076176</certNumber><rfFrequency>Australia and New Zealand</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Dome Door/Window Sensor Pro is a battery powered security-enabled* Z-Wave Plus magnetic reed switch that can monitor the status of doors, windows, and anything else that opens and closes.It can also report ambient temperature levels.The Door/Window Sensor consists of two parts - the sensor, and the magnet.The sensor has a reed switch inside, which is sensitive to the magnets presence when aligned properly and within the defined distance.When the sensor and magnet are brought together or pulled apart, the sensor will report its open/close status to its Z-Wave controller, and the encrypted wireless communication* ensures that user data remains secure. Because many manufacturers use Z-Wave to communicate, the Door/Window Sensor can interact with different products of different categories. Z-Wave Plus Certified S0 Security-Enabled* Built-In Temperature Sensor Up to 250 range Ten-Year Battery Life LED Signal Strength Indication 1.25 Max distance between sensor &amp; magnet Ultra-Narrow (1/4) Magnet for Placement Between Door and Casing Monitor doors, windows, medicine cabinets, drawers, garage doors, and many other openings</lang></description><productName>Dome Door/Window Sensor Pro</productName><brandName>Dome</brandName><productCode>DMDP1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 is the Lifeline group, which can hold five members, typically including the main Z-Wave controller.The Door/Window Sensor Pro sends this group a Notification Report or a Binary Sensor Report when it is opened or closed (see Configuration Parameter 3.)It also sends this group a multilevel sensor report to report the temperature and a Battery Report in response to Battery Get commands.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 supports up to 5 members and the Door/Window Sensor Pro sends a Basic Set command to this group (or the Control Group) to directly trigger devices (like a light, chime, etc.) when the tamper switch either opens or closes. The value of the Basic Set command (e.g. brightness of the lamp) is configured using configuration parameter 07.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 3 supports up to 5 members and the Door/Window Sensor Pro sends it a NOTIFICATION_REPORT or SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT when the tamper switch either opens or closes.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 4 supports up to 5 members and the Door/Window Sensor Pro sends a Basic Set command to this group to directly trigger devices (like a light, chime, etc.) when the sensor detects the door/window opening or closing. The value of the Basic Set command (e.g. brightness of the lamp) is configured using configuration parameters 08 and 09.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="5" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 5 supports up to 5 members and the Door/Window Sensor Pro sends it a NOTIFICATION_REPORT or SENSOR_BINARY_REPORT when the sensor detects the door/window opening. </lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable LED Indicator</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter enables or disables the LED Indicator flashing to indicate opening and closing events.The Door/Window Sensor Pro will always flash the LED Indicator for inclusion, exclusion, tamper, and other system events.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Open/Close LED Indicator Disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Open/Close LED Indicator Enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Configure Open/Close Reports Sent</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter switches the Notification or Binary Sensor report sent when the door opens or closes.If this parameter is set to 01, the Door/Window Sensor Pro will report closed instead of openwhen the Magnet and Sensor are pulled apart.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reports Closed when Magnet is close</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reports Open when Magnet is close</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Switch Between Notification and Binary Sensor Command Classes</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">By default, the Door/Window Sensor Pro uses the Notification command class to communicate open/close and tamper events.If this Parameter is set to 1, the device will instead use the Binary Sensor command class.To apply this setting, the battery needs be removed and replaced!This is because the supported command classes will change according to this setting, so the device must restart to advertise its new command classes.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Both Command Classesare Used</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Notification Command Class is Used</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Binary Sensor Command Class is Used</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable Temperature Sensor</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Door/Window Sensor Pro can also monitor and report ambient temperature conditions.However, temperature sensing functionality is disabled by default to save battery life, and this configuration parameter is used to enable or disable this feature.To apply this setting, the battery needs be removed and replaced!This is because the supported command classes will change according to this setting, so the device must restart to advertise its new command classes.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Sensor Disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Sensor Enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Offset</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This Configuration Parameter can offset the temperature value reported by125 degrees to compensate for temperature variances in a room - for example, the temperature near the ceiling in a room is significantly higher than the average temperature of the same room.This Parameter accepts a signed 8-bit value with an absolute value of up to 125, and its units are Dependant on Configuration Parameter 07</lang></description><value from="-125" to="-1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">-125 to -1 degrees offset</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="125"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 - 125 degrees offset</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature Units</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Door/Window Sensor Pro can report temperature values in either Celsius or Fahrenheit, and this parameter allows the user to decide which unit is used.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature is Reported in Fahrenheit</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">emperature is Reported in Celsius</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 Basic Set Value</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the value sent by the Basic Set command to Association Group 2.The Door/Window Sensor Pro sends a Basic Set command to Association Group 2 both when the tamper switch opens and closes(for more information, see Group 2. Value is in Hexadecimal.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn Off Device</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set Device to Value</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn On Device</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Level (Group 4 Opening)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the value sent by the Basic Set command to Association Group 4.The Door/Window Sensor Pro sends a Basic Set command to Association Group 4 when the door or window opens (for more information, see Group 4 on page 14.) Value is in Hexadecimal.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn Off Device</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set Device to Value</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn On Device</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Level (Group 4 Closing)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter sets the value sent by the Basic Set command to Association Group 4.The Door/Window Sensor Pro sends a Basic Set command to Association Group 4 when the door or window closes (for more information, see Group 4 on page 14.) Value is in Hexadecimal.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn Off Device</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set Device to Value</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Turn On Device</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18076176"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
