<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0207"/><productType value="0027"/><productId value="0100"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-19016361</certNumber><rfFrequency>Indien</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Forest Shuttle L Z-wave, Shuttle S Z-wave (US) and Forest motorized curtain track systems (FMS) make an unbeatable combination when it comes to noiseless operated motorized curtains. The smooth and silent running curtain track system can, in addition to remote operation, also be operated by hand. Thanks to Forests special Touch Impulse Technology, a gentle pull on the curtain is enough to activate the motor. The Forest Shuttle L Z-wave, Shuttle S Z-Wave (US) makes sure that your curtains will always hang beautifully smooth and supple. Opened as well as closed! Touch Impulse Technology, gently pulling the curtain will activate the motor. Integrated Emergency Control ensures manual operation of the curtain in case of power failure. Modular motor, different modules can be attached for various control options: Radio Frequency, Switch, Infrared, Domotics, Building/Hotel Automation, Serial Communication, Z-Wave, etc. Forest Shuttle LZ-Wave and Shuttle S Z-wave (US) will have an internal Z-Wave receiver and BUS connection. Silent motor, speeds: 14 and 17 cm/sec., with slow start and slow stop. Full automatic setting of the limits. Stack-back position programmable to every desired setting. Forest Shuttle LZ-Wave and Shuttle S Z-wave (US) have an integrated power supply. Motor pulley connects motor and FMS track. Also available in upside down version to conceal the motor into the ceiling. Available track lenghts: 5.80 meters and 7.00 meters. FMS track and components available in white, grey and black.</lang></description><productName>Forest Shuttle LZ IN</productName><brandName>Forest Drapery Hardware</brandName><productCode>FS2Z5232000009</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-19016361"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
