<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="001A"/><productType value="0042"/><productId value="0053"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-18126337</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Eaton's Z-Wave Plus battery operated motion sensoris a versatile motion detector that can be triggered by movement or changes in light level when paired with your Home automation or a Security system.Detects motion in a space with in-built Passive Infra-red and Light SensorWhen used with a compatible Smart Hub, get alerted on your smart phone or Tablet, trigger scenes or have lights come ON automaticallyCR123A Lithium Battery included with the product ~ expected battery life of 2 yearsCan be mounted using included screws or double sided tape120 field of view with 1032 sq. ft coverage for Major motionSupports Z-Wave Plus functionality with S2 security certification</lang></description><productName>Motion Sensor</productName><brandName>Eaton</brandName><productCode>RF96PIRBMS</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic SetPIR Control</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="99" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Basic Set Level determines the value that will be sent from the Basic Set command for devicesassociated with Group 2. For a Binary Switch Device (e.g., receptacle or appliance module), it will bea simple ON command. For a Multilevel Switch Device (e.g., a dimmer), it will be set to the level setby this parameter.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic Set Level</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="6" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Sensitivity level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">In order to provide the best efficiency of the sensor, it is recommended to test the sensor withmovements from the farthest end of the coverage area at first time of use. If movements cannotbe detected consistently, simply adjust the sensitivity level with Configuration Parameter #3. Thisparameter can be configured with the value of 1 through 10, where 1 means low sensitivity and 10means high sensitivity.</lang></description><value from="1" to="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Sensitivity level low (1) to high (10)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="180" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Re-trigger Interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Re-trigger Interval Setting determines the amount of time between when the sensor will retriggera signal that motion has been detected. During this time, the sensor will not report motioneven though motion may be detected. The time interval can be set between 5 secs to 3600 secs.</lang></description><value from="5" to="3600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Time in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="20" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Lux Level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The user can set a lux level percentage which determines when the light sensor will be activated. Ifthe lux level of ambient illumination falls below this percentage, and motion is detected, the sensorwill emit a Z-Wave ON Command to the controller. Percentage can be set between 1% to 100%.</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">In percentages</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="2" default="15" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">On - Off duration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The function of on-off duration setting will be useful if the detector is connected with a module orlighting. The duration determines how long the module/lighting should stay ON. For instance, LampModule turns OFF 100 secs after it has been turned ON. This parameter can be configured with thevalue of 5 through 3600, where 5 means 5 second delay and 3600 means 3600 seconds of delay.</lang></description><value from="5" to="3600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">In seconds</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-18126337"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
