<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="018E"/><productType value="0003"/><productId value="000E"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="81"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-19066571</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">ACGS-23ZW Acoustic Glassbreak Sensor is an excellent first line of defense for perimeter protection. This wireless sensor will alert when a glass window or door is being smashed or broken, providing an extra layer of advanced security for your property.Our proprietary microphone technology recognizes acoustic patterns to provide full coverage, with a maximum of 8m radius from sensor to glass. With four selectable sensitivity levels, ACGS-23ZW can be easily adjusted to fit large or small rooms. It can also be integrated into security system to activate a siren upon glass break, thereby detering burglars and preventing a full break-in.</lang></description><productName>Acoustic Glass Break Detector</productName><brandName>Climax Technology</brandName><productCode>ACGS-23ZW</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 for LifeLine (max node = 1):Notification CC,V3 (COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATION)Battery CC (COMMAND_CLASS_BATTERY)Device Reset Locally CCNotification Report1. If Glass Break Detector is triggered, it will send a Notification Report (Type: 0x07, Event 0x06).2. If tamper is open, it will send Notification Report (Type: 0x07, Event: 0x03)3. If tamper is closed, it will send Notification Report (Type: 0x07, Event: 0x00, Parmeter:0x03).Battery Report1. If battery level changes, it will send Battery Report (0x64, 0x4B, 0x32, 0x19, or 0xFF) respectively.0x64 --- 100% Battery Full0x4B --- 75% Battery0x32 --- 50% Battery0x19 --- 25% Battery0xFF --- Battery Dead (Cut Off)Device Reset1. To perform factory reset, press and hold the Function Button for 10 seconds, the device will send a DEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION report.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 2 for Basic Set (max node = 1):BASIC CC (COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC)1. When the detector is triggered, it will send BASIC SET (0xFF). The device does NOT support Restore Event report.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-19066571"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
