<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0060"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0004"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-19056484</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The SP815 is a multifunction device with motion detector and temperature/humidity sensor. It uses Passive Infra-Red (PIR) technology to detect movement in a protected area by sensing the changes of thermal radiation caused by the moving body within or across the field of detection. Featuring dual PIR sensor designed with dual lens technology, this detector is immune to presence of pets in the home allowing your pet to move freely without causing false alarms.This product is a Z-Wave Plus enabled device and is fully compatible with any Z-Wave enabled network. The device can be set up in a Z-Wave network to communicate directly with other end devices such as smartplugs, or to report directly to a Z-Wave controller (usually a gateway).When the motion detector is triggered, an alarm signal will be emitted to the controller and the controller, after receiving the signal, will perform certain action according to its settings.The product has a built in digital temperature sensor and humidity sensor to report environmental condition of the protected area to the controller.This product supports the S2 security protocol that uses encrypted Z-Wave Plus messages to communicate to other security-enabled Z-Wave Plus products. A security-enabled Z-Wave Plus Controller must be used in order to fully utilize the security features of this product.</lang></description><productName>PET IMMUNE PIR MOTION DETECTOR</productName><brandName>Everspring</brandName><productCode>SP815-1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">PIR Control</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature and Humidity Auto Report period setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The parameter adjusts report time of temperature and humidity report.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1440"><description><lang xml:lang="en">minutes</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="15" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Re-trigger Interval Setting (for PIR sensor only)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The parameter adjusts the sleep period after the detector has been triggered. No response will be made during this interval if a movement is presented. Longer re-trigger interval will result in longer battery life.</lang></description><value from="10" to="3600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="2" default="15" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Trigger Off Interval Setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This controls how long the connected lighting will stay on after the motion is detected This is useful for Group 2 associations where the detector is connected directly to another device such as smartplugs.</lang></description><value from="10" to="3600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">seconds</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-19056484"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
