<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0159"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0055"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-19056504</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Mini Dimmer is a MOSFET-switching light device that also supports control of low-voltage halogen lamps with electronic transformers, dimmable compact fluorescent lights, and dimmable LED bulbs. It measures power consumption of the connected device. It supports push-button/momentary switches (default) and toggle switches. It can work with or without the neutral line. Qubino Mini Dimmer allows the easiest and quickest installation. It is designed to be mounted inside a flush mounting box, hidden behind a traditional wall switch. It acts as repeater in order to improve range and stability of Z-Wave network.</lang></description><productName>Mini Dimmer</productName><brandName>QUBINO</brandName><productCode>ZMNHHD1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus LifelineSupports the following command classes: Device Reset Locally: triggered upon request Meter Report: triggered according to Configuration parameters 40 and 42 Notification Report: triggered on overload/over temperature Switch Multilevel Report: triggered upon request or according to Configuration parameters 11 and 12 (note that this command class is active only in dimmer mode) Switch Binary Report: triggered upon request or according to Configuration parameters 11 and 12 (note that this command class is active only in switch mode)</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Basic OnOffSupports the following command classes: Basic set: triggered at change of output and reflecting its state</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">StartStop level changeSupports the following command classes: Start/Stop Level Change: triggered upon holding and releasing the switch connected to I1</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Multilevel setSupports the following command classes: Switch Multilevel Set: triggered at change of output and reflecting its state</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">In-wall Switch Type for Load to control I1</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">With this parameter, you can select between push-button (momentary) and on/off toggle switch types.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">push-button (momentary)</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">on/off toggle switch</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="11" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Turn Load 1 Off Automatically with Timer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If Load is ON, you can schedule it to turn OFF automatically after a period of time defined in this parameter. The timer is reset to zero each time the device receives an ON or OFF command, either remotely (from the gateway (hub) or associated device) or locally from the switch.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Auto OFF Disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="32536"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 - 32536 seconds - Auto OFF timer enabled for a given amount of seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="12" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Turn Load 1 On Automatically with Timer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If Load is OFF, you can schedule it to turn ON automatically after a period of time defined in this parameter. The timer is reset to zero each time the device receives an OFF or ON command, either remotely (from the gateway (hub) or associated device) or locally from the switch.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Auto ON Disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="32536"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 - 32536 seconds - Auto ON timer enabled for a given amount of seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="21" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable the Double click function</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">If the Double click function is enabled, a fast double click on the push-button will set the dimming level to the maximum dimming value.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">double click disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">double click enabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="30" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Restore on/off status for load after power failure</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter determines if on/off status is saved and restored for the load after power failure.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Device saves last on/off status and restores it after a power failure.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Device does not save on/off status and does not restore it after a power failure, it remains off.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="40" size="1" default="10" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Watt Power Consumption Reporting Threshold for Load</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose by how much the power consumption needs to increase or decrease to be reported. Values correspond to percentages so if 10 is set (by default), the device will report any power consumption changes of 10% or more compared to the last reading. NOTE: The power consumption needs to increase or decrease by at least 2 Watts to be reported, regardless of percentage set in this parameter.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Power consumption reporting disabled</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1% - 100% Power consumption reporting enabled. New value is reported only when Wattage in real time changes by more than the percentage value set in this parameter compared to the previous Wattage reading, starting at 1% (the lowest value possible).</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="42" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Watt Power Consumption Reporting Time Threshold for Load</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set value refers to the time interval with which power consumption in Watts is reported (032767 seconds). If 300 is entered, energy consumption reports will be sent to the gateway (hub) every 300 seconds (or 5 minutes) if there was a change compared from the last report.NOTE: Values from 1 to 29 are ignored by device due to standard recommendation.NOTE: The report will be send only if there was a change compared to the last report.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Power consumption reporting on time interval disabled</lang></description></value><value from="30" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">30 - 32767seconds. Power consumption reporting enabled. Report is sent according to time interval (value) set here.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Working mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">With this parameter, you can change the device presentation on the user interface. NOTE: After parameter change, first exclude the device (without setting parameters to default value) then wait at least 30s before reinclusion.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dimmer mode</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Switch mode (works only in 3 way wiring-connection with neutral line)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="60" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Minimum dimming value</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The value set in this parameter determines the minimum dimming value (the lowest value which can be set on the device, when, for example, dimming lights with wall switch or slider in the GUI (Gateway - hub)) (Data type 1 byte dec) default value 0 = 0% (minimum dimming value) 0- 98 = 0% - 98%, step is 1%. Minimum dimming value is set by entering a value. NOTE: The minimum level may not be higher than the maximum level!</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0% (minimum dimming value)</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="98"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0% - 98%, step is 1%. Minimum dimming value is set by entering a value</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="61" size="1" default="99" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Maximum dimming value</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The value set in this parameter determines the maximum dimming value (the highest value which can be set on the device, when, for example, dimming lights with wall switch or slider in the GUI (Gateway - hub)) NOTE: The maximum level may not be lower than the minimum level!</lang></description><value from="99" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">99% (Maximum dimming value)</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1% - 99%, step is 1%. Maximum dimming value is set by entering a value.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="65" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Dimming time when key pressed (soft on/off)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose the time during which the device will move between the min. and max. dimming values by a short press of the push-button I1.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 second</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 seconds- 127 seconds, step is 1 second</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="66" size="2" default="3" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Dimming time when key hold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose the time during which the Dimmer will move between the min. and max. dimming values during a continuous press of the push-button I1, by an associated device or through the UI controls (BasicSet, SwitchMultilevelSet).</lang></description><value from="1" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 second127 seconds</lang></description></value><value from="128" to="253"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1 minute126 minutes</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="67" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Ignore start level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose whether the device should use (or disregard) the start dimming level value. If the device is configured to use the start level, it should start the dimming process from the currently set dimming level. This parameter is used with association group 3.NOTE: Parameter is valid only in Dimmer mode. In Switch mode the parameter has no effect.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">use the start level value</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ignore the start level value</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="68" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Dimming duration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose the time during which the device will transition from the current value to the new target value. This parameter applies to the association group 3.NOTE: Parameter is valid only in Dimmer mode. In Switch mode the parameter has no effect.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">dimming duration according to parameter 66</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">from 1 to 127 seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="70" size="2" default="200" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Overload safety switch</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The function allows for turning off the controlled device in case of exceeding the defined power for more than 5s. Controlled device can be turned back on by input I1 or sending a control frame. NOTE: This functionality is not an overload safety protection, please check the technical specifications chapter for more details.In case of overload the following message will be send towards the controller: COMMAND_CLASS_NOTIFICATION_V5 The Alarm V1 type field set to 0x00 Notification Type 0x08 and 0x08 (Overload detected)</lang></description><value from="1" to="200"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1W - 200W</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function not active</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="71" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Calibration trigger</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Choose when will be the calibration procedure triggered.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">calibration done after power cycle regardless of inclusion status</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">force calibration. Calibration will start immediately</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="72" size="1" default="2" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Calibration status (read only)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">With this parameter you can check the calibration status.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">calibration was successful</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">calibration failed</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="73" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Alarm/Notification events</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the module behaviour in case it receives any Alarm/Notification events.NOTE: When value 3 is selected the default time interval of the blinking is 10 minutes. It can be stopped with a button press or sending a control frame. To adjust the time interval please refer to parameter 74Alarm/Notification time interval.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn OFF</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn ON</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">start blinking (output turns 1s ON, and 1s OFF)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="74" size="1" default="10" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Alarm/Notification time interval (dependant on parameter 73)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the time interval of the blinking state, once the module receives an alarm/notification event. Minimum step increase is 1 minute.NOTE: This parameter does not have any effect if parameter 73 is not set to value 3.</lang></description><value from="1" to="125"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1-125 minutes</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-19056504"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
