<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0159"/><productType value="0007"/><productId value="0054"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="71"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-19066549</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Qubino 3 Phase Smart Meter can be used in residential, industrial and utility applications. It measures energy directly in 2-wire networks by means of fast sampling of voltage and current signals. It calculates energy, power and power factor from the measured signals. You can control the device through the Z-Wave network. The Qubino 3 Phase Smart Meter can operate across a wide temperature range, from a chilly -15C to a scorching 55C (5F131F). Every device also acts as a repeater in order to improve the range and stability of the Z-Wave network.</lang></description><productName>3-Phase Smart Meter</productName><brandName>QUBINO</brandName><productCode>ZMNHXD1 </productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Supports the following commands: Device Reset Locally: triggered upon request Meter Report: triggered according to Configuration parameters 40,42 and 43</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="40" size="1" default="50" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Reporting on power change</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is valid for Active Power Total, Active Power Phase1, Active Power Phase2 and Active Power Phase3.Set value means percentage from 0-100 = 0% - 100% Available configuration parameters (data type is 1 Byte DEC) Default value 50 0reporting disabled 1-100 = 1% - 100% reporting enabled. Power report is send only when actual power in Watts (in real time changes for more than set percentage comparing to previous Active Power, step is 1%.NOTE: if power change is less than 5 W, the report is not send (pushed).NOTE: Device is measuring also some disturbances even if on the output is no load. To avoid disturbances: If measured Active Power (W) is below e.g. 5W-&gt; the reported value in this case is 0W</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1% - 100% reporting enabled.Power report is send only when actual power in Watts (in real time changes for more than set percentage comparing to previous Active Power, step is 1%.</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">reporting disabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="42" size="1" default="600" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Reporting on time interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is currently valid only for Active Energy Total Import/Export (kWh), Reactive Energy Total (kvarh), Total Energy (kVAh) Available configuration parameters (data type is 2 Byte DEC) Default value 600 (600 seconds - 10 minutes) 0reporting disabledEN.34 600-32535 = 600 (600 seconds32535 seconds). Reporting enabled. Report is send with the time interval set by entered value.Note: Device is reporting only if there was a change of 0.1 in EnergyNote: In the future will be possible to measure and report also Active Energy on PH1, PH2 and PH3.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reporting disabled</lang></description></value><value from="600" to="32535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">600-32535 = 600 (600 seconds32535 seconds). Reporting enabled. Report is send with the time interval set by entered value.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="43" size="2" default="600" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Other Values - Reporting on time interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is valid only for Voltage (V of ph1, ph2, ph3), Current (A of ph1, ph2, ph3), Total Power Factor, Total Reactive Power (var)Available configuration parameters (data type is 2 Byte DEC) Default value 600 (600 seconds - 10 minutes) 0reporting disabled 600-32535 = 600 (600 seconds32535 seconds). Reporting enabled. Report is send with the time interval set by entered value. Note: Device is reporting only if there was a change</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reporting disabled</lang></description></value><value from="600" to="32535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">(600 seconds32535 seconds). Reporting enabled. Report is send with the time interval set by entered value.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-19066549"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
