<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="013C"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="006A"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="81"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-19066570</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">PSM09 is only for indoor using device. PSM09 can detect the the door is open or not. The Recessed door sensor PSM09 is Base on Z-WaveTM technology. It is the Z-WaveTM plus product, it support the security, OTA. Those newest features of the Z-WaveTM technology. Z-WaveTM is a wireless communication protocol designed for home automation, specifically to remotely control applications in residential and light commercial environments. The technology uses a low-power RF radio embedded or retrofitted into home electronics devices and systems, such as lighting, home access control, entertainment systems and household appliances. Notice: if user use some command, it have to check device is security bootstrap otherwise some command cannot increment. This device is a security enabled Z-Wave Plus product that is able to use encrypted Z-Wave Plus messages to communicate to other security enabled Z-Wave Plus products. This device must be used in conjunction with a Security Enabled Z-Wave Controller in order to fully utilize all implemented functions. This product can be operated in any Z-Wave network with other Z-Wave certified devices from other manufacturers. All non-battery operated nodes within the network will act as repeaters regardless of vendor to increase reliability of the network. </lang></description><productName>Recessed Door Sensor</productName><brandName>Philio</brandName><productCode>PSM09-A</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus LifelineThis machine provides a group of groups. Each group canset 5 Nodes.Group 1: Used for event return.Report type:1. Door sensor state2.Battery state3.Reset report</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="12" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto report state time</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The interval time for auto report the door/window &amp; battery level. 0 means turn off auto report state. Units of 30 minutes.</lang></description><value from="0" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">0 means turn off auto report state. Units of 30 minutes.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-19066570"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
