<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="010F"/><productType value="0602"/><productId value="B003"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-19076606</certNumber><rfFrequency>South Korea</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">FIBARO Wall Plug is a remotely controlled plug-in switch with the ability to measure power and energy consumption. It uses a LED frame to visualize the current load and operating mode with color changing illumination. FIBARO Wall Plug makes it possible to control electrical devices in a convenient and maintenance-free way. Main features of FIBARO Wall Plug:- Compatible with any Z-Wave or Z-Wave Plus Controller.- Supports Z-Wave network Security Modes: S0 with AES-128 encryption and S2 with PRNG-based encryption.- Extremely easy installation - simply plug the device into the mains socket.- Works as a Z-Wave signal repeater.- Active power and energy consumption metering for plugged device.- Current value of the load and operating mode are indicated by the multi-color LED frame.</lang></description><productName>FIBARO Wall Plug</productName><brandName>FIBARO</brandName><productCode>FGWPx-102</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses/><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lifeline reports the device status and allowsfor assigning single device only (main controller by default).</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">On/Off (button) devices in this groupwill be switched on or off when relay status is changed using theB-button (done via BASIC SET command frames).</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">On/Off (power) devices in this groupwill be switched on or off depending on the current load (done viaBASIC SET command frames).</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Always On function</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Once activated, Wall Plug will keep the connected device constantlyON, will stop reacting to alarm frames or pushing the B-button.Always On function turns the Wall Plug into a power and energy meter.Connected device will not be turned off upon receiving an alarmframe from another Z-Wave device (parameter 31 will be ignored).In Always on mode, connected device may be turned off only afteruser defined power has been exceeded (parameter 3). In such a case,connected device can be turned on again by pushing the B-button orsending a control frame. By default, overload protection is inactive.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function inactive</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function activated</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="1" default="80" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">High priority power report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter determines the minimum percentage change in activepower that will result in sending power report to the main controllerwith the highest priority in the Z-Wave network.By default, the Wall Plug immediately sends the power report if thepower load changes by 80%.NOTEIn extreme cases, reports may be sent every second if rapid and significant power load changes occur. Frequent reporting may overload the Z-Wave network so these parameters settings should reflect significant changes in power load only.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">power change in percent</lang></description></value><value from="100" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">reports are disabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="11" size="1" default="15" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Standard power report</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter determines the minimum percentage change in activepower that will result in sending power report to the main controllerCompared to parameter 10, the maximum number of reports sent isreduced (parameter 12) to 5 in a specified time interval. In addition,the frames are not sent in EXPLORE mode, which prevents overloadingthe Z-Wave network.By default changes in power load may be reported up to 5 times per30 seconds, when power load changes by 15%.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">power change in percent</lang></description></value><value from="100" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">reports are disabled</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="12" size="2" default="30" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power reporting interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines how frequently standard power reports (parameter11) are sent. By default the Wall Plug sends up to 5 reportseach 30 seconds, provided the power load changes by 15%.</lang></description><value from="5" to="600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="13" size="2" default="10" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Energy reporting threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter specifies the minimum change in energy consumption(in relation to the previously reported), that will result in sendinga new report.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">energy reports inactive</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="500"><description><lang xml:lang="en">(0.01-5kWh, step 0.01kWh) - threshold</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="14" size="2" default="3600" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power and energy periodic reports</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines time period between reports sent whenchanges in power load have not been recorded or if changes are insignificant(not exceeding values of parameters 20, 21 and 23). By defaultreports are sent every hour.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">periodic reports inactive</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="32400"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="15" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Measuring energy consumed by the Wall Plug itself</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter determines whether energy metering should includethe amount of energy consumed by the Wall Plug itself. Results arebeing added to energy consumed by controlled device.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function inactive</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function activated</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Remember device status after a power failure</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter determines how the Wall Plug will react in the eventof power supply failure (e.g. taking out from the electrical outlet).After the power supply is back on, the Wall Plug can be restored toprevious state or remain switched off.This parameter is ignored in Always On mode - the device automaticallyturns ON after plugging it into the socket.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">device remains switched off</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">device restores the state from before the power failure</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="20" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Control of On/Off (Button) association group (2) devices</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Controlling devices with the B-Button. This parameter is inactive inAlways On mode (parameter 1).Control as the Wall Plug: switching the Wall Plug onswitch the devices on (parameter 24) switching the Wall Plug offswitch the devices off (parameter 24)Control opposite to the Wall Plug: switching the Wall Plug onswitch the devices off switching the Wall Plug offswitch the devices on</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">control as the Wall Plug</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">control opposite to the Wall Plug</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="21" size="2" default="300" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">DOWN value - On/Off (Power) association group (3)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lower power threshold, used in parameter 23. DOWN value cannotbe higher than a value specified in parameter 22.</lang></description><value from="0" to="24900"><description><lang xml:lang="en">(0.0-2490.0W, step 0.1W)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="22" size="2" default="500" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">UP value - On/Off (Power) association group (3)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Upper power threshold, used in parameter 23. UP value cannot belower than a value specified in parameter 21.</lang></description><value from="100" to="25000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">10.0-2500.0W, step 0.1W)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="23" size="1" default="6" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">The response after exceeding defined power values</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the way that 3rd association group devices arecontrolled. Depends on the actual measured power (as parameters 21and 22 settings).</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn the associated devices ON, once the power drops below DOWN value (parameter 21)</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn the associated devices OFF, once the power drops below DOWN value (parameter 21)</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn the associated devices ON, once the power rises above UP value (parameter 22)</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn the associated devices OFF, once the power rises above UP value (parameter 22)</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">combination of 1 and 4. Turn the associated devices ON, once the power drops below DOWN value (parameter 21). Turn the associated devices OFF, once the power rises above UP value (parameter 22).</lang></description></value><value from="6" to="6"><description><lang xml:lang="en">combination of 2 and 3. Turn the associated devices OFF, once the power drops below DOWN value (parameter 21). Turn the associated devices ON, once the power rises above UP value (parameter 22).</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="24" size="2" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">SWITCH ON value - On/Off association groups</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The value of BASIC SET command frame sent to the devices associatedin On/Off association groups (2, 3).On/Off (Button) association group - in accordance with parameter 20.On/Off (Power) association group - in accordance with parameter 23.NOTESetting parameter 24 to appropriate value will result in: 0 - turning off associated devices1-99 - forcing level of associated devices255 - setting associated devices to the last remembered state or turning them on</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turning off associated devices</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">forcing level of associated devices</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">setting associated devices to the last remembered state or turning them on</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="2" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Overload safety switch</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This function allows to turn off the controlled device in case of exceedingthe defined power. Controlled device will be turned off evenif Always On function is active (parameter 1).Controlled device can be turned back on via B-button or sending acontrol frame. By default this function is inactive.This functionality is not an overload safety protection nor a short circuitprotection. Circuit needs additional short circuit and overload protection.CAUTIONThe device has a protection that will turn the load off in the case of detecting currentgreater than 110% of rated current. It is a safety function and it cannot be turned off.After its activation the load can be turned on back again by pressing the B-button or sending a control frame. This function is independent of overload safety switch set inthe parameter no. 3.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">function inactive</lang></description></value><value from="10" to="30000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">(1.0-3000.0W, step 0.1W) - power threshold</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="30" size="1" default="63" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Active alarms</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Define Z-Wave network alarms to which the Wall Plug will respond.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">general alarm</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">smoke alarm</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">CO alarm</lang></description></value><value from="8" to="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">CO2 alarm</lang></description></value><value from="16" to="16"><description><lang xml:lang="en">high temperature alarm</lang></description></value><value from="32" to="32"><description><lang xml:lang="en">flood alarm</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="31" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Response to alarm frames</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines how the Wall Plug will respond to alarms (devicesstatus change).In case of values 1 or 2 the Wall Plug is operating normally and LEDring signals an alarm through time defined in parameter 32 or untilthe alarm is cancelled.In case of values 5 to 50 the Wall Plug does not report status change,power changes, ignores BASIC SET command frames. After time definedin parameter 32 or after the alarm cancellation, connected deviceis set to the previous state.NOTEIf Always On function is active (parameter 1), settings of parameter 31 are ignored.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">no reaction</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn connected device on</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn connected device off</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="50"><description><lang xml:lang="en">(0.5-50.0s, step 0.1s) - cyclically change device state with set period</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="32" size="2" default="600" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Alarm state duration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter specifies the duration of alarm state. If a device sendingan alarm frame through the Z-Wave network sets alarm duration aswell, this settings are ignored.</lang></description><value from="1" to="32400"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="40" size="2" default="25000" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Power load for violet colour</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter determines active power value, which when exceeded,causes the LED ring flash violet. Function is active only when parameter41 is set to 0 or 1.</lang></description><value from="1000" to="30000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">100.0-3000.0W, step 0.1W</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="41" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED ring colour when controlled device is on</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">When set to 1 or 2, LED ring colour will change depending on activepower and parameter 40. Other colours are set permanently and donot depend on power consumption.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">illumination turned off completely</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">colour changes continuously depending on active power</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">colour changes in steps depending on active power</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">white</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">red</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">green</lang></description></value><value from="6" to="6"><description><lang xml:lang="en">blue</lang></description></value><value from="7" to="7"><description><lang xml:lang="en">yellow</lang></description></value><value from="8" to="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">cyan</lang></description></value><value from="9" to="9"><description><lang xml:lang="en">magenta</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="42" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED ring illumination colour when controlled device is off</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the illumination colour after turning off.0 - illumination turned off completely1 - LED ring is illuminated with a colour corresponding to the last measured power, before the controlled device was turned off3 - white,4 - red,5 - green,6 - blue, 7 - yellow8 - cyan, 9 - magenta</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">illumination turned off completely</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED ring is illuminated with a colour corresponding to the last measured power, before the controlled device was turned off</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">white</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">red</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">green</lang></description></value><value from="6" to="6"><description><lang xml:lang="en">blue</lang></description></value><value from="7" to="7"><description><lang xml:lang="en">yellow</lang></description></value><value from="8" to="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">cyan</lang></description></value><value from="9" to="9"><description><lang xml:lang="en">magenta</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="43" size="1" default="2" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED ring illumination colour at the Z-Wave network alarm detection</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines the illumination colour in case of Z-Wave alarm.0 - illumination turned off completely1 - no change in colour. LED ring colour is determined by settings of parameters 41 or 422 - LED ring flashes red/blue/white3 - white,4 - red,5 - green,6 - blue,7 - yellow8 - cyan,9 - magenta</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">illumination turned off completely</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">no change in colour. LED ring colour is determined by settings of parameters 41 or 42</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED ring flashes red/blue/white</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">white</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">red</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">green</lang></description></value><value from="6" to="6"><description><lang xml:lang="en">blue</lang></description></value><value from="7" to="7"><description><lang xml:lang="en">yellow</lang></description></value><value from="8" to="8"><description><lang xml:lang="en">cyan</lang></description></value><value from="9" to="9"><description><lang xml:lang="en">magenta</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="50" size="1" default="3" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Associations in Z-Wave network security mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines how commands are sent in specified associationgroups: as secure or non-secure. Parameter is active only inZ-Wave network security mode. This parameter does not apply to 1stLifeline group.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">none of the groups sent as secure</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2nd group sent as secure</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">3rd group sent as secure</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2nd and 3rd group sent as secure</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-19076606"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
