<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0081"/><productType value="00A0"/><productId value="0001"/><libType value="06"/><protoVersion value="05"/><protoSubVersion value="02"/><appVersion value="01"/><appSubVersion value="04"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-09080006</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Sensoair measures CO2-Concentration.The intelligent air quality sensor with CO2 and VOC control for activating window-mounted and wall-mounted ventilators.The SENSOAIR gives you the green light for clean air and a healthy sense of well-being with full productivity. The intelligent air quality sensor registers many different types of pollution in the room airbefore the human body can even react and the recommended values have been exceeded. By automatically activating wall-mounted or window-mounted ventilators as needed, the SENSOAIR combats CO2, nicotine, smoke and unpleasant odours. For a quality of air that can be seen. The ventilation traffic lights integrated into the casing allow you to check the current air conditions in the room.All benefits at a glance:- Recognises many different pollutants in the room air- For simple, convenient and need-based ventilation- Elegant design, trouble-free installation- Can be used anywhere with conventional wiring or via a wireless Z-Wave connection- SENSOAIR basic table unit- SENSOAIR plus for controlling ventilation devices and motorised drives- SENSOAIR wave for integration in Z-Wave wireless systems (Only with CO2-sensor)</lang></description><productName>SIEGENIA-AUBI Sensoair</productName><brandName>SIEGENIA-AUBI KG</brandName><productCode/></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0086" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.siegenia-aubi.com/en/00002/0004/0003/0001/index.html.de"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
