<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0080"/><productType value="0004"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="05"/><protoSubVersion value="02"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-11100011</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Duco Comfort SystemThe Duco Comfort System ventilates according to "System C", and, with minimal investment and installation for optimum healthy and comfortable indoor climate. This makes it ideal for both new construction and renovation projects .The air exhaust is controlled based on moisture measurements in the wet room, bathroom and kitchen and CO 2 measurement in the living spaces. These measurements are carried out by means of sensors in the various spaces directly to the source to measure.In the toilet room to be placed presence detectors. These sensors and detectors communicate wirelessly via the Z-wave with a central afvoerbox protocol, the DucoBox, that the drainage of the polluted and controls humid air.The fresh and healthy air directly through self-regulating grills on the window or in the wall inside the house charged. There is a wide choice of self-regulating ventilation within Duco's product range. This ventilation can lead to 16 E-level points lead so it fits completely within a new house with E-level 80.&gt; Exhaust based on moisture measurements (RH) in the wet areas (bathroom and / or kitchen) and CO 2 measurement in the living spaces &gt; Measurements at the source &gt; Wireless communication between RH sensor and central vacuum cleaner, the DucoBox &gt; Direct supply of fresh self-regulating air through vents in the gable &gt; Up to 16 E-level points profit &gt; VEA approved &gt; Ideal for renovation</lang></description><productName>DUCO CO2/RH sensor</productName><brandName>Duco</brandName><productCode/></deviceDescription><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.zuurstofvooruwwoning.be/be/nl/consumenten/Ventilatiesystemen/Duco_Comfort_System/index.html"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
