<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0095"/><productType value="3103"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="52"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-12020003</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">QEES RETO Plug-in Dimmer Plus brings along comfort and elegance with an extremely easy setup and a unique design. With its help you can now wirelessly control all the dimmable loads you have inside your home.QEES RETO Plug-in Dimmer Plus is a Z-Wave-controlled 400W universal dimmer (US frequency) with schuko plug-in socket outlet, built-in power meter, multi-color LED feedback and one programmable group for retrofit installation.QEES RETO Plug-in Dimmer Pluss software can be upgraded over the air, allowing the device to receive additional features or bug fixes through firmware updates and software apps.This is a unique feature of all QEES products and it facilitates a future-proof, contemporary and flexible infrastructure solution for the building.QEES RETO Plug-in Dimmer Plus is compatible with all Z-Wave certified devices from other manufacturers. It also acts as a repeater inside your Z-Wave network increasing the range for your remote control.Like all QEES products, QEES RETO Plug-in Dimmer Plus has a self-calibrating built-in power meter and can switch off the device that otherwise would consume power when not needed.</lang></description><productName>QEES P313B Plug-in dimmer</productName><brandName>QEES ApS</brandName><productCode>313-B(KFBGLE)(WB)-A1</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0086" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.qees.eu/products/plus-retrofit-series/plugin-in-socket-outlets/plugin-in-socket-dimmer-us/product/72/106/Plus-Retrofit-Series/Plus-RETO-Plug-in/qees-reto-plug-in-dimmer-plus-us"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
