<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0129"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="0000"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="52"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="40"/><specificClass value="03"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-12050006</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Yale Real Living deadbolt and lever locks are the first products in the Yale Real Living (www.yalerealliving.com) portfolio of home control and security solutions.Available in both durable acrylic touchscreen or simple, elegant, tamper-resistant keypad, Yale's new platform of intelligent locks support Z-Wave, allowing them to integrate seamlessly into a wide range of home control and security systems.Regardless of the home control system employed, users will have access to a high degree of functionality, including the ability to lock and unlock doors from web-enabled devices or create customized entry scenes for family members, neighbors and guests. Features of Yale Real Living locks include personalized access-control scenes for up to 250 users; access to all user programmable settings via select user interfaces; plus the touchscreen versions employ voice assisted programming in English, Spanish and French.The new intelligent locks offer an elegant, next-generation home control solution for entryways and protected interior doors to make everyday living easier and safer.</lang></description><productName>Yale Real Living Touchscreen Deadbolt</productName><brandName>Yale Locks &amp; Hardware</brandName><productCode>Yale/YRD/ 220</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0086" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.yalerealliving.com"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
