<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0039"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="53"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-12050002</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">TUXWIFIW/S Connected Home Controller.Honeywells Tuxedo Touch is a 7", high-resolution graphic touchscreen that functions as an integrated security system dkeypad, home controller, camera viewer and digital picture frame in one. It a cost-effective way to capture new markets by seamlessly integrating security with cameras and Z-Wave enabled thermostats, lights, locks and shades. A built-in web server lets end-users control Tuxedo Touch anywhere in their home and view live video on up to four local cameras per screen on an iPhone, iPad, Android, BlackBerry, Internet TV or any compatible wireless mobile device.* Use either Wi-Fi or Ethernet to connect to the premises LAN.Whether controlling the security system or other functions within the home, the large graphic iconswhich also match the Total Connect interfacesimplify operation. Homeowners can receive important alerts about events remotely with Honeywell Total Connect Remote Servicesa great RMR opportunity.A digital picture frame feature can be managed by end-users with the simple insertion of an SD cardletting them create cinema-quality slideshows right at the Tuxedo Touch display. A choice of white or silver/black blend with any dcor. Tuxedo Touch is available in English, French Canadian and Spanish language options, with voice annunciation of alarm status (English only).</lang></description><productName>Tuxedo Touch WIFI, TUXWIFIW/S</productName><brandName>Honeywell Home</brandName><productCode>TUXWIFIW/S</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0043" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.security.honeywell.com/hsc/products/keypad/gr/ad/317517.html"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
