<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0063"/><productType value="5250"/><productId value="3030"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="54"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-12050027</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Schlage Its easy to remotely operate appliances, lamps and other electronics with Nexia Home Intelligence and this simple plug-in module. A Nexia outlet on one end and a regular outlet on the other end mean you dont sacrifice any plug-in space for your other electrical devices. Nexia makes it easy to manage lights and many other plug-in devices from most web-connected computers, tablets or smart phones.Remote control appliance module is plug-in simple in any AC outlet. Activate incandescent and fluorescent floor and table lamps alike. Remotely operate or schedule small compatible appliances toolike fans, video games and stereo componentsby plugging into the Nexia compatible module. Use Nexia to easily set lighting schedules, creating the appearance that someones home when the house is empty. On your way home, make lights come on to greet you. Forget to turn off a light? Pick up your smart phone and save electricity with one touch. Set Nexia to conveniently turn on lights when you enter your access code on your Schlage Home Keypad Lock.Remote management with a Nexia Home Intelligence system requires the Nexia Bridge and a monthly subscription of $8.99.</lang></description><productName> Appliance Module for Schlage</productName><brandName>Schlage </brandName><productCode>043156296347</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0086" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.nexiahome.com/Products/ProductDetail.aspx?model=043156296347"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
