<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0086"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="001D"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="54"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-13030011</certNumber><rfFrequency>Australia and New Zealand</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">We always think of tools in our house as doing things. Switches turn lights on. Remotes turn TVs off. Things do the basic stuff we tell them tonothing more, nothing less. Thats a description of a house of the past. The house of today has intelligence built in. Or at least it should. Inspired by the humble thermostat, Aeotecs Z-Wave Door &amp; Window Sensor sits as a part of our Intelligence range. Like a thermostat, weve designed it to find things out, to understand things about your home, and to then use that information to make your home more comfortable, to make your life easier. The Door &amp; Window Sensor finds out something very simplewhether a door or a window, or in fact any object in your home, is open or closed. But theres power in simplicity. Power that allows you to inform the rest of your Z-Wave network about your selected doors and windows. Like a thermostat lets your heating and cooling systems know what they should do next, Aeotecs Z-Wave Door &amp; Window Sensor does the same. Perhaps an open door means that your lights should turn on and welcome you home. Perhaps an open window means that an alarm should be trigged. Whatever it means to your home, with door and window sensors installed, your Z-Wave network will have both the power and the itelligence to do it.</lang></description><productName>Door Window Sensor G2</productName><brandName>Aeotec</brandName><productCode>DSB29-ZWAU</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0084" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC08-13030011"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
