<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0063"/><productType value="5257"/><productId value="3533"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="54"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-13050011</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">"Transform any home into a smart home with the Jasco Z-Wave Wireless Lighting Control On/Off Switch. The on/off switch replaces your current light switch, uses your existing wiring, and provides Z-Wave wireless and in-wall control of overhead lighting. The switch enables wireless control of on/off functions of direct wire incandescent, LED, xenon, halogen and fluorescent lighting. Providing ultimate flexibility, the Jasco Z-Wave Wireless Lighting Control On/Off Switch allows you to operate the switch by itself or easily integrate the switch with two-way, three-way or four-way wiring configurations by adding the Jasco Auxiliary switch for Z-Wave. Two-way wiring configuration turns the light or appliance on/off from one location. Three-way wiring configuration turns the light or appliance on/off from two separate locations. Four-way wiring configuration turns the light or appliance on/off from three separate locations. The Jasco Auxiliary Switch for Z-Wave is required for Three-way or Four-way installations. The lighting control includes a blue LED indicator light to easily locate the switch in a dark room. Take control of your home lighting with Jasco Z-Wave Wireless Lighting Controls! Z-Wave is the worlds largest ecosystem of interoperable smart home products. Z-Wave lighting controls provide an easy-to-install and affordable system to control lighting and small appliances in your home. Add Jasco Z-Wave lighting controls to a Z-Wave certified gateway to access and control your home from anywhere in the world using your smartphone, tablet or computer as a home automation command center. Never worry if you accidentally left the lights on because you can turn them off remotely or program your lights to go on/off at specific times. Create customized lighting scenes for any occasion such as a go to sleep scene or a movie night scene. Give the illusion that someone is home by programming the lights to turn on/off while you are awayperfect for deterring crime and adding additional security!"</lang></description><productName>In-Wall Decora Style ON/OFF Relay Switch, Neutral Required, White or Light Almond paddles</productName><brandName>Jasco Products Company</brandName><productCode>45709/ZW4005</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0086" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="www.ezzwave.com"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
