<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0060"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0003"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="54"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-13100004</certNumber><rfFrequency>Russia</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">"The Motion Detector is designed with two detecting sensors, Passive Infra-Red (PIR) sensor and light sensor, to detect movement within a protected area, operating at 868.42 and 869MHz. The detector can be used as a security device or home automation device.When the detector is cooperated with security appliances, the detector is acting as a security device by detecting changes in infra-red radiation levels. If a person moves within or across the devices field of vision, a trigger radio signal will be transmitted to cause full alarm condition in order to frighten intruders away. Alternatively, when the detector is worked with Z-Wave Controller , the detector can be set to perform the role of home automation device by detecting both changes in infra-red radiation levels and percentage of lux levels.Once night falls, the percentage of ambient illumination is lower than preset value. If a person moves within or across the devices field of vision, a trigger radio signal will be transmitted so as to turn connected lightings for better illumination."</lang></description><productName>Motion Detector</productName><brandName>Everspring</brandName><productCode>HSP02-A</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0084" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.everspring.com/HSP02.aspx"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
