<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0184"/><productType value="4447"/><productId value="3031"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-14090001</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The PA-100 plug-in is a non-dimming switch which plugs into a standard AC outlet, and allows remote control of On, Off lights and AC operated appliances. Compact design allows second wall AC outlet to remain free.Serves as a node to repeat the signal in the network, extending the overall Z-Wave mesh wireless network rangeThe PA-100 uses the latest 500 series Z-Wave chip for longer range, over-air-firmware update, and easier inclusion process, providing these features are also supported by the gateway or controller.</lang></description><productName>Z-Wave Plug-In On/Off Appliance Module</productName><brandName>Dragon Tech Industrial, Ltd.</brandName><productCode>PA-100</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lifeline association only supports the u0022manual resetu0022 event. For instructions on how to set lifeline associate , please refer to your wireless controller instructions.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="3" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED Configuration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter controls the state of the LED indicator in response to the state of the switch module.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The LED indicator will be OFF when the connected appliance is ON, and the LED indicator will be ON when the connected appliance is OFF.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The LED indicator will be ON when the connected appliance is ON and the LED indicator will be OFF when the connected appliance is OFF.</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The LED indicator will always be OFF, regardless of connected appliance being ON or OFF.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-14090001"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
