<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0184"/><productType value="4744"/><productId value="3032"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-14090002</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">PD-100 Plug in Dimmer Module Works with any AC operated lamps with incandescent and dimmable florescent(CFL) or LED light bulbs ON/OFF status and location LED indicator Can be controlled wirelessly or manually Plug and play, simple setup Lightweight and compact.Grounded 3-pin AC power plug to enhance safetyOver-The-Air firmware upgrade available with compatible gateway, Z-Wave static controller, PC and software Z-Wave 500 Series module inside Internal resettable fuse to protect from surge current Manual reset capability Adjustable dimming rate</lang></description><productName>Plug in Dimmer Switch</productName><brandName>Dragon Tech Industrial, Ltd.</brandName><productCode>PD-100</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lifeline association only supports the u0022manual resetu0022 event.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="10" size="1" default="3" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Duration of each level</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Indicates the time duration of each level. Each unit has 10 msec of duration.3 means that the default is set at 30 msec.By adjusting the parameter values of 9 and 10, user can control how fine or fast they can control the dim levels.</lang></description><value from="1" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">For every unit increase or descrease, the duration is increased or decreased by 10msec.Higher the number, slower the duration it takes to adjust the dim level.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED backlight for key switch</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter controls the operation of the LED backlight in conjunction with the operating state of the switch.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">LED indicator turns ON when the connected appliance is ON.LED indciator will be OFF when the connected appliance is OFF.</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">When the connected appliance is OFF, the LED indicator will be ON. When the connected appliance is ON, the LED indicator will be OFF.</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Key switch LED backlight is always OFF.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Dimming Steps</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Indicates the number of steps the lighting brightness level will change as timer runs out when pressing the rocker switch up or down.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Set preferred increments of levels.Higher the number the faster the device will change brightness level.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-14090002"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
