<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0175"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="0011"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-14090006</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">This plug-in ON/OFF switch Home Control Metering Plug is a security enabled wireless switch, based on Z-Wave Plus technology. Z-Wave Plus enabled devices displayingtheZ-Wave Plus logo can also be used with it regardless of the manufacturer, and can also be used in other manufacturers Z-Wave enabled networks. Remote On/Off control of the connected load is possible with other manufacturers wireless Controller. Each switch is designed to act as a repeater. Repeaters will re-transmit the RF signal to ensure that the signal is received by itsintended destination by routing the signal around obstacles and radio dead spots. Because Home Control Metering Plug supports Security Command Class, it can be added with a Secured controller. Its functionality and supported command classes is identical when included as a secure and non-secure device. This plug-in ON/OFF switch is able to detect instance wattage (3000W/CE/CN,1500W/UL/TW/JP) and overload current (14.5A) of connected lights or appliances. When detecting overload state, the Switch will be disabled and its On/Off button will be lockout of which LED will flash quickly. However, unplug and re-connect the switch will reset its overload condition to normal status.</lang></description><productName>Metering Plug</productName><brandName>devolo</brandName><productCode>MT02646</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="720" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Watt Meter Report Period</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter determines how often meter reporting of instantaneous watt usage is reported automatically.Each unit is 5 seconds.The maximum interval to report its instant power consumption is 45 hours (5s*32767/3600=45hr).</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enable automatic interval reporting with an interval of 5 * the value.</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable automatic interval meter reporting of Watts</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="6" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">KWH Meter Report Period:</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter controls the frequency at which the kWh value of the meter is reported to the node in association group 1.This setting is in units of 10 minutes. The maximum interval to report its Accumulated Power Consumption (KW/h) is 227.55 days (10min*32767/1440=227.55 days).</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">6*10 min=1 hour </lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable automatic interval meter kWh reporting.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="2" default="1300" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of current for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the current of load over the preset threshold value, if the setting value is 1300, when the load current of Relay1 over this value, Home Control Metering Plug will send current meter report to warn the Group1 node, the Range of the setting value is from 10 to 1300,and the default value is 1300.</lang></description><value from="10" to="1300"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1300*0.01A = 13A</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="2" default="10000" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold of KWh for Load Caution</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This is a warning when the KWh of load over the preset threshold value, If the setting value is 10000, when the Accumulated Power Consumption of Relay1 over this value, Home Control Metering Plug will send KWH meter report to warn the Group1 node, minimum value is 1KWh and default value is 10000 kWh.</lang></description><value from="1" to="10000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enable automatic warning when the accumulated kWh power consumption exceeds the setting value from 1KWh ~ 10000KWh.</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable kWh Load Caution Reporting</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Restore switch state mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Whenever the AC power return from lost, Home Control Metering Plug will restore the switch state which could be SWITCH OFFLAST SWITCH STATESWITCH ON. The default setting is LAST SWITCH STATE. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Upon the return of AC power, the switch will remain Off.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Upon the return of AC power, the switch will return to the state it was in when the power was turned off.</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Upon the return of AC power, the switch will turn On.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Mode of switch off function</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration parameter determines how the switch will respond to a received SWITCH OFF command.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">SWITCH OFF commands received are ignored.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">SWITCH OFF commands received are honored.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LED indication mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter determines the state of the LED display.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The LED follows the state of the switch.</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Night Mode - When the switch is On, the LED is Off, and when the switch is Off, the LED is On.</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Flash Mode - When the state of the switch changes, the LED will be on for one second and then will turn off.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Auto off timer</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Automatic Shut-Off Setting.This parameter determines the amount of time before the switch is automatically turned off after it has been turned on.</lang></description><value from="1" to="32767"><description><lang xml:lang="en">1s ~ 32767s for automatically turning off</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable the auto off function</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">RF off command mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter determines how the switch responds to the receipt of a SWITCH_ALL_OFF command.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">When SWITCH ALL OFF is received, the MT02646 turns Off.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">When SWITCH ALL OFF is received, the MT02646 ignores the command and does nothing.</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">When SWITCH ALL OFF is received, the MT02646 will turn On if it is Off, and will turn Off if it is On.</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">When SWITCH ALL OFF is received, the MT02646 turns On.</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-14090006"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
