<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0063"/><productType value="5044"/><productId value="3031"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="55"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-14110004</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Transform any home into a smart home with the GE Z-Wave Smart Lighting Control Lamp Module with Dimmer Control. The lamp module enables wireless control of on/off and dim functions for standard incandescent table and floor lamps, as well as dimmable fluorescent, LED and CFL fixtures and more! Use the dimmer control to customize the lighting output and create the perfect ambiance for any room. The space-saving horizontal module plugs into a standard wall receptacle without blocking the second outlet or obstructing placement of furniture. It provides a Z-Wave enabled outlet for the lamp you would like to control and one always-on, standard pass-through AC outlet for other electrical appliances. Take control of your home lighting with GE Z-Wave Smart Lighting Controls! Z-Wave is the worlds largest ecosystem of interoperable smart home products.Z-Wave lighting controls provide an easy-to-install and affordable system to control lighting and small appliances in your home. Add GE Z-Wave lighting controls to a Z-Wave certified gateway to access and control your home from anywhere in the world using your smartphone, tablet or computer as a home automation command center. Never worry if you accidentally left the lights on because you can turn them off remotely or program your lights to go on/off at specific times. Create customized lighting scenes for any occasion such as a go to sleep scene or a movie night scene. Give the illusion that someone is home by programming the lights to turn on/off while you are awayperfect for deterring crime and adding additional security!</lang></description><productName>GE Z-Wave Plug-in Smart Dimmer</productName><brandName>GE</brandName><productCode>12718/ZW3101</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0086" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.ezzwave.com"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
