<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="001E"/><productType value="0005"/><productId value="0002"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="02"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15020004</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-NET is a remote network-based Z-Wave interface for use with HomeSeer home automation systems. Since Z-NET is IP-enabled, it may be installed anywhere a network connection is available. Z-NET supports Network Wide Inclusion (NWI) for easy pairing of Z-Wave products. Multiple Z-NETs may be used together with any HomeSeer system for a centrally managed, muti-network installation; ideal for home owners with secondary residences or outbuildings (pool houses, barns, workshops, servants quarters, etc).Main Features:* Remote Z-Wave Interface for use with HomeSeer Software and HomeTrollers* Supports Z-Wave Plus (and older) Products* Ethernet (and optional WiFi) Connections Allow of Optimal Positioning in Home* Supports Network Wide Inclusion (NWI) for Easy Product Inclusion* May be Used with Other Z-NETs in Larger Homes or for Secondary Residences or Outbuildings* Includes Highly Optimized Antenna for Superior Range and Performance* Includes Easy to Use Web-Based Management Features* Provides Easy Upgrade Path from Z-Trollers, Z-Sticks, SmartSticks and Most Other Z-Wave Interfaces* Case Includes Keyhole slots for wall mounting (with your hardware)* Optional USB &gt; WiFi adapter is Available</lang></description><productName>HomeSeer Z-NET</productName><brandName>HomeSeer</brandName><productCode>Z-NET</productCode></deviceDescription><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://store.homeseer.com/store/X-P1902.aspx"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
