<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0059"/><productType value="000E"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15020011</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The Secure SSP 301 is a switch and repeater that forms part of a Z-Wave Plus home automation network. The SSP 301 is a mains powered device with EU plug type,that will switch (power On/Off) a connected appliance either by the Z-Wave network or manually by pressing its integrated button.The SSP 301 acts as a repeater in a Z-Wave network by helping messages from other devices reachtheredestinations.</lang></description><productName>SSP</productName><brandName>Secure Controls (UK)</brandName><productCode>SSP 301 EU</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Delta Based Switch Status Reporting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration enable the switch status reporting, when switch status changed for OFF to ON or ON to OFF. </lang></description><value from="0" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="2" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Time interval based Switch Status Reporting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration enable the switch status reporting based on the time interval configured. Note: Controllers may only allow configuring signed values. In order to set values in the range 32768 65520, the value sent in the application shall be equal to desired value minus 65520. For example, to set time intervalto 36000 seconds it may be needed to set a value 3600065536=29536.</lang></description><value from="0" to="65520"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Relay and LED configuration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This configuration is used to change the relay LED status when relay is open/close and also enable to whether to retain the last relay status over power cycle.0 - Relay status will not be retain over power cycle, and Relay status LED will lit when relay ON and relay status LED will off when relay OFF. 1 - Relay status will be retain over power cycle, and Relay status LED will lit when relay ON and relay status LED will off when relay OFF.2 - Relay status will not be retain over power cycle, and Relay status LED will off when relay ON and relay status LED will lit when relay OFF.3 - Relay status will be retain over power cycle, and Relay status LED will off when relay ON and relay status LED will lit when relay OFF.</lang></description><value from="0" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-15020011"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
