<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="001E"/><productType value="0004"/><productId value="0001"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15020009</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The HSM200 senses motion, temperature and light level, can function as a night light, and can also be programmed to display up to 7 different glowing colors when things happen in the home! Since the HSM200 is line powered, there are no batteries to change and the unit automatically operates as a Z-Wave network repeater.Installation is fast and easy. Just plug into any available 120v outlet and tap the button on the side to join it to your Z-Wave network. HSM200 is compatible with any HomeSeer HS3-based system, including the full line of HomeTrollers, and Z-Wave systems from 3rd parties.HomeSeer users can create events to display different colors when motion is sensed, doors are opened, water leaks are detected or just about anything else happens in the home. Color optionsinclude red, green, blue, yellow, magenta, cyan and white. The unit can also be programmed to work as a night light after hours.</lang></description><productName>Z-Wave Multi-Sensor HSM200</productName><brandName>HomeSeer</brandName><productCode>HSM200</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">This group is used to directly turn lights on or off when motion is detected. Up to four (4) Z-Wave devices can be associated in this group. The HSM200 will send a BASIC ON command to all devices that are associated in this group. Note that the Z-Wave devices in this group must be within direct range (about 30) of the HSM200. Control of nodes that are further away or blocked by metal or concrete walls should rely on the Z-Wave system controller and the home-control application for reliable operation.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="10" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">OnTime</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">OnTime sets the number of minutes that the lights stay on when motion has not been detected.A value of 0 is a special mode where the lights are constantly sent a command to turn them on whenever motion is detected. The HSM200 will NOT turn the lights off in this mode. Recommended values:5 min for hallways20 min for an office environment60 min for a library, office or other room where someone may be sitting still for a long time </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Send only ON every time motion is detected</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Minutes of No Motion before OFF sent</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="-1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">OnLevel</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">OnLevel is the value sent by the Z-Wave BASIC_SET command to all Group 2 nodes when motion is detected. A value of 0 will turn the lights off (not recommended).A value between 1 and 99 will set the dim level to between 1% and 99% (99% is full on).A value of -1 will turn the light on which depends on the device but most will set the dim level to the last dim setting.</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Dim level</lang></description></value><value from="-1" to="-1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">ON </lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="3" size="1" default="60" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">LiteMin</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">A Luminance report is sent to the system controller every LiteMin minutes if the value has changed by more than 5% since the last reading.A value of zero turns this mode off. Luminance values can still be obtained at any time by the home-control application in this mode.</lang></description><value from="1" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Minutes between light level reports</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="4" size="1" default="60" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">TempMin</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">A Temperature report is sent to the system controller every TempMin minutes if the value has changed by more than 0.5F since the last reading.A value of zero turns this mode off. Temperature values can still be obtained at any time by the home-control application in this mode.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="127"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Minutes between temperature reports</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">TempAdj</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">TempAdj is a twos-complement number that is used to adjust the temperature reading to make it more accurate. The value is in tenths of degree Fahrenheit. The temperature reading can be adjusted up to +12.7F to -12.8F. A value of 1 will adjust the temperature reading by +0.1F. A value of -1 will adjust the temperature by -0.1F. A value of 123 will adjust the temperature by +12.3F. </lang></description><value from="-127" to="128"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature adjust by 1/10th this value</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://store.homeseer.com/store/X-P1882.aspx"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
