<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0059"/><productType value="0002"/><productId value="0002"/><libType value="Routing Slave"/><protoVersion value="04"/><protoSubVersion value="52"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="04"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC08-12040002</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">CENTAURPLUS C17-ZW is a single channel central heating programmer with Z-Wave RF communication support. The CENTAURPLUS 17-ZW will act as a routing slave device in the Z-Wave networkHorstmann has introduced a new wireless version of its CentaurPlus ZW timeswitch that can save the householder up to 10% in energy costs* while being easy to install and programme.The wireless CentaurPlus C17 ZW operates with the latest Horstmann HRT4-ZW wireless room thermostat and together, the two offer a highly efficient controls package ideally suited to combi boiler installations.It is estimated that some 8 million homes* in the UK are operating central heating systems without a room thermostat as part of the controls package. Many of these are combi boiler installations where it was once considered sufficient for a time switch and TRVs on radiators to provide control. It is in fact an inefficient solution and leads to fluctuations in heating levels that can result in uncomfortable room temperatures and wasted energy consumption caused by excessive boiler cycling.By replacing the existing timeswitch with a Horstmann CentaurPlus ZW and adding its HRT-4 ZW room thermostat, a unique energy saving control solution is created to achieve and maintain optimum control of room temperature settings. The pairing process using the Z-Wave technology in both units is both simple and reliable and the resulting enhanced control of temperature settings and the boiler firing regime is both energy saving and efficient.The new CentaurPlus C17 ZW is the flagship model in a completely upgraded family of controls. As well as its wireless technology the unit now features a 24 hour BST/GMT clock and a bright backlit display to assist with ease of reading and setting. Yet it retains the industry standard 6-pin back plate that makes upgrading a process that only takes minutes for a qualified installer. Alternatively, if the previous wall plate is non standard, it can be exchanged for a new plate (supplied) using the same wiring re-connected into the correct terminals.The HRT4-ZW room thermostat uses the latest technology that interfaces perfectly with the timeswitch. Self monitoring TPI (Time Proportional Control) software in the stat makes a series of precise calculations once it has entered the control or proportional band. When set to 6 cycles per hour the software will calculate the amount of heat needed during each 10 minute period and switch the boiler on for a proportion of those 10 minutes to maintain the set temperature.This stops the wide fluctuations in temperature that can occur with conventional thermostats. The integral feature of the TPI software then fine tunes the calculations to constantly review its performance and carry out further fine adjustments if necessary.The system will now be compliant with Part L1 of the 2010 Building Regulations for existing heating systemsa relatively quick and straightforward change over that can produce significant cost savings for the householder.</lang></description><productName>Secure SCP318 Zwave Programmer &amp; Thermostat (Tx/Rx)</productName><brandName>Secure Controls</brandName><productCode>SCP318</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="0086" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><resourceLinks><manualUrl url="http://www.securetogether.eu/"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
