<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0086"/><productType value="0104"/><productId value="0038"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15060002</certNumber><rfFrequency>US</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Aeon Labs Doorbell supports playing MP3 music files with a press of this doorbell. It has a 128MB flash memory that can store up to 800 ringtones. The volume can be adjusted manually via short press on the Volume Button, also you can switch the doorbell sound to the next via long press on the Volume Button. You may change/update your doorbell ringtone at any point in time you want by connecting your Doorbell to your PC to update the sound track on your Doorbells flash memory.There is a small Wireless Button, which can trigger the doorbell on the other side of the wall to play the selected doorbell music when pressed.It also act as a repeater that forward Z-Wave command messages to destination nodes if the originating controller is out of range from the destination node.By taking advantage of the Z-Wave mesh network, commands can be routed to their destination via intermediary listening Z-Wave products. Products that are Z-Wave certified can be used and communicate with other Z-Wave certified devices.Also a tool that can be programmed, scheduled, controlled and communicated with from anywhere in the world.</lang></description><productName>Doorbell Gen5</productName><brandName>Aeotec</brandName><productCode>ZW056-A</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Group 1 is assigned to the Lifeline association group and every device has 5 nodes to associate.When the Doorbell is received the commands sent by controller to be turned on or off, the Doorbell will send a basic report of its status to the nodes in association group 1. To change what kind of signal is sent to the nodes in group 1, please see the detailed description of configuration parameter 80.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">When the Doorbell receives the Basic Set, Switch Binary Set, Switch Multilevel Start Level Change, Switch Multilevel Stop Level Change, Switch Multilevel Set commands from main controller. it will forward the Basic Set, Switch Binary Set, Switch Multilevel Start Level Change, Switch Multilevel Stop Level Change, Switch Multilevel Set to associated nodes in Group 2.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="10" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Define the function ofButton- or Button+.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to define the function of Button- or Button+.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Button- is defined to be the control item of Previous. Button+ is defined to be the control item of Next.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Button- is defined to be the control item of Next. Button+ is defined to be the control item of Previous.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="11" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Define the function of Button- and Button+ when pressing it once and long pressing it.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to define the function of Button- and Button+ when pressing it once and long pressing it.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Pressing it once, which will change the volume. Long pressing it, which will change the default ringtone.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Pressing it once, which will change the default ringtone. Long pressing it, which will change the the volume.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="2" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Set the repetitions for playing doorbell ringtone.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to set the repetitions for playing doorbell ringtone.Note: If the time of playing doorbell ringtone is more than 20 seconds, the volume of ringtone will reduce to silence no matter how many repetitions of doorbell ringtone are set. </lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">the range of repetition is 1 to 100.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="241" size="4" default="0" type="constant"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Pair the Wireless Button with Doorbell</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to pair the Wireless Button with Doorbell.Note:1. This procedure should only be used when the complimentary Wireless Button is missing or inoperable and you have another new Wireless Button that would be paired with your Doorbell.2. When the pairing is started, the blue led will blink slowly, at this time, you just need to press the Wireless Button once. If the blue led change to be solid, which means the pairing is successful. Otherwise, repeat the steps.</lang></description><value from="1431655765" to="1431655765"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Start the Wireless Button pairing mode.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="252" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable Lock Configuration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to enable/disable Lock all configuration parameters.(0 =disable, 1 = enable)</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">All configuration parameters are configurable.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">All configuration parameters are not configurable (Locked).</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="255" size="4" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Reset to default factory setting</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to reset product to default factory setting. (There are just 2 values can be used).</lang></description><value from="1431655765" to="1431655765"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Reset the product to default factory setting and be excluded from the Z-wave network.</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Resets all configuration parameters to default setting.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="42" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Get the battery status of Wireless Button.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to get the battery status of Wireless Button.Note: Just need to send the configuration parameter 42 Get command to Doorbell. The configuration report value will be the status of battery.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The current battery status is normal battery level.</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The current battery status is low battery level.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="5" size="1" default="1" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Set the default doorbell ringtone.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to set the default doorbell ringtone.</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">To set which ringtone number is the default ringtone.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="6" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Select a ringtone to play.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to select a ringtone to play, which is onlyfor customer testing the doorbell ringtone.</lang></description><value from="1" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Play the specified ringtone.</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Stop playing.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Control items</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to implement the control items.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Implement the control item of Play.</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Implement the control item of Stop.</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Implement the control item of Pause.</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Implement the control item of Next.</lang></description></value><value from="5" to="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Implement the control item of Previous.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="8" size="1" default="10" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Set the volume of ringtone.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to set the volume of ringtone.The volume has 10 levels can be set. Value=10, which is the max volume.Value=0, which is the min volume.</lang></description><value from="0" to="10"><description><lang xml:lang="en">The max volume is 10, the min volume is 0.</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="80" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/Disable to send notifications to associated devices to associated devices.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to enable/disable to send notifications to associated devices (in Group 1) when the state of Doorbell Gen5s load is changed. (0=Send nothing, 1=Send hail CC, 2=Send basic report CC).</lang></description><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Send BASIC Report Command</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Send Nothing (Disabled)</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Send HAIL Command</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="81" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Enable/disable to send notification to associated devices.</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter is used to enable/disable to send notification to associated devices (In group 1) just only when the Wireless Button's battery is in low battery status.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Disable</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Enable</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-15060002"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
