<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="010F"/><productType value="0B01"/><productId value="1002"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15080018</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">FIBARO Flood Sensor is a universal, Z-Wave compatible, flood and temperature sensor. Device can be battery (ca. 2 years battery life) or VDC powered (12 or 24 VDC). FIBARO Flood Sensor is designed to be placed on the floor or on a wall with a flood sensor probes extended by connected wire. Flood alarm is sent to Z-Wave network devices or additionally to any alarm system controller, through opening a NC contact. The device has built-in temperature sensor, monitoring temperature of e.g. floor, LED indicator, acoustic alarm, and is equipped with a tilt sensor, reporting tilt or movement e.g. when someone has taken the Sensor from its original location. LED diode signals flood, operating mode or the Z-Wave network communication range. FIBARO Flood Sensor is sink-proof, which means it drifts on the water surface and keeps on sending alarm signal in case of substantial inundation of water. Flood Sensor is compatible with any Z-Wave or Z-Wave+ Controller.https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8JRxUoHbEN8</lang></description><productName>FIBARO Flood Sensor</productName><brandName>FIBARO</brandName><productCode>FGFS-101</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lifeline reports the device status and allowsfor assigning single device only (the main controller by default- the device reports its status to the main controller).Type of frame sent by the device when the association group is activated: DEVICE_RESET_LOCALLY_NOTIFICATION; NOTIFICATION_REPORT; BATTERY_REPORT; SENSOR_MULTILEVEL_REPORT.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Flood Control is assigned to the devicestatus - sending the BASIC SET control frame to the associated devices</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Flood Alarm is assigned to the devicestatus - sending the NOTIFICATION REPORT control frame to the associateddevices.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Tamper Alarm is assigned to a TMP buttonand tilt sensor - sending the NOTIFICATION REPORT control frameto the associated devices in case a TMP button is released or a tiltsensor triggered (depending on parameter 74 settings).</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="2" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Alarm cancellation delay</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Determines time period, in seconds, by which a Flood Sensor will retainthe flood state after the flooding itself, has ceased. Sensor willkeep on reporting flooding to the main controller. This parameter settingsdo not affect acoustic and visual alarms, which turn off immediatelyafter flooding ceases.</lang></description><value from="0" to="3600"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in seconds, each 1s</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="10" size="4" default="300" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature measurement interval</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Time interval, in seconds, between consecutive measurements oftemperature done by built-in temperature sensor and battery level.If a temperature differs from previously reported by a value determinedin parameter 12, new temperature value is reported. If a batterylevel changes, the device reports a battery status change.The parameter is relevant when using a Flood Sensor in a batterypower mode - longer time interval means less frequent communicationresulting in extended battery life.After consecutive FAILED and SUCCESSFUL communication attempts,the Sensor will go to standby mode.</lang></description><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="12" size="2" default="50" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature measurement hysteresis</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Determines a minimum temperature change value (insensitivity level),resulting in a temperature report being sent to the main controller,according to the Parameter 10 settings.Please refer tp colour/Decimal value table in manual.</lang></description><value from="1" to="1000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">each 0.01</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="3" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Acoustic and visual signals On/Off in case of flooding</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The parameter allows for deactivation visual and acoustic alarm.Parameter allows for increasing a battery life. Settings changes willnot affect the Sensors communication with the main controller - commands to association groups, alarms and reports will still be sent.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">acoustic and visual alarms inactive</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">acoustic alarm inactive, visual alarm active</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">acoustic alarm active, visual alarm inactive</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">acoustic and visual alarms active</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="50" size="2" default="1500" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Low temperature alarm threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The parameter stores a temperature value, below which visual indicatorblinks with a colour determined by a Parameter 61 settings. Bydefault the visual indicator blinks blue.</lang></description><value from="-10000" to="10000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">each 0.01</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="51" size="2" default="3500" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">High temperature alarm threshold</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The parameter stores a temperature value, above which visual indicator blinks with a colour determined by the Parameter 62 settings. By default the visual indicator blinks red.Note! The main controller does not interpret negative numbers as decimals.Thats why read value may be different than entered. Negative numbers are coded in U2 standard.Please refer to Decimal/Hexadecimal (U2)/Value in controller table in manual</lang></description><value from="-10000" to="10000"><description><lang xml:lang="en">each 0.01</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="61" size="4" default="255" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Low temperature alarm indicator colour</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter stores RGB colour value.</lang></description><value from="0" to="16777215"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="62" size="4" default="16711680" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">High temperature alarm indicator colour</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter stores RGB colour value.A main controller interprets colours as a sum of it component coloursvalue. Each colours value is a number from 0 to 255.Note! A main controller interprets colours as a sum of it component coulours value. Each colours is a number from 0 to 255. Please refer to colour/Decimal value table in manual.</lang></description><value from="0" to="16777215"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="63" size="1" default="2" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Managing a visual indicator under standard operation</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter determines visual indicators operation. Set to 0 turns theindicator off, saving a battery life.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Visual indicator does not indicate the temperature</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> Visual indicator indicates the temperature (blink) every Temperature Measurement Interval (Parameter 10, constant current and battery) or Wake Up Interval (battery mode)</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Visual indicator indicates the temperature continuously, only in constant power mode</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="7" size="2" default="255" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Forced dimming level / roller blind opening level, when sending turn on / open command to 2nd association group devices</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">In case of alarm frames, alarm priority is determined.Available settings:</lang></description><value from="1" to="99"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> forced level</lang></description></value><value from="255" to="255"><description><lang xml:lang="en">turn a device on</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="73" size="2" default="0" type="range"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Temperature measurement compensation</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter stores a temperature value to be added to or deductedfrom the current temperature measured by internal temperature sensorin order to compensate the difference between air temperatureand temperature at the floor level.</lang></description><value from="-10000" to="10000"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="74" size="1" default="2" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Alarm frame sent to 1st and 4th Association Group activation (MOVEMENT_TAMPER / BUTTON_TAMPER)</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The device is able to turn on alarms resulting from sensors vibrationse.g. when the sensor is moved, or the TMP button released. </lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> tamper alarms inactive</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">button tamper alarm active</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> button tamper alarm active</lang></description></value><value from="3" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">button and movement tampers alarm active</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="75" size="4" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Visual and audible alarms duration</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">The user can silence the Flood Sensor. Because the Sensors alarmmay last for a long time, it is possible to turn off visual and audiblealarm signalling to save battery.The parameter determines time after which alarm will become quiet- still active but the device will go into battery saving mode. Visual oracoustic alarm will be reactivated after time specified in the parameter76. When alarm status ceases, alarm will be turned off immediately.The value of 0 means visual and acoustic alarms are active indefinitely.In battery power mode the Sensor will never go to sleep whichmay shorten battery life significantly.Note! Parameter 75 is ignored when parameter 2 is set to 0.Available settings:0 - alarms active indefinitely1-65535 - time in seconds</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">alarms active indefinitely</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">time in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="76" size="4" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Alarm frame / Basic Set frame retransmission time when retaining flood alarm</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Parameter determines a time period after which an alarm frame will beretransmitted. The value of 0 cancels an alarm frame retransmission.Note! In case a time period set in parameter 76 is shorter then the one specified in parameter 75, the device will not quiet the alarm, it will remain active.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">retransmission inactive</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="65535"><description><lang xml:lang="en">time in seconds</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="77" size="1" default="0" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Flood sensor functionality turned off</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Allows for turning of the internal flood sensor. Tamper and built intemperature sensor will remain active.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Default flood sensor operation (flood detection, reactions)</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Built in flood sensor TURNED OFF (does not change its state in the main controller, does not send Alarms and Basic Set frames with flood state changes. Always visible in the main controller as turned off)</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="78" size="1" default="7" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Associations in Z-Wave network security mode</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">This parameter defines how commands are sent in specified associationgroups: as secure or non-secure. Parameter is active only in Z-Wavenetwork security mode. It does not apply to 1st Lifeline group.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> none of the groups sent as secure</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="2"><description><lang xml:lang="en">2nd group Flood Control sent as secure</lang></description></value><value from="2" to="3"><description><lang xml:lang="en">group Flood Alarm sent as secure</lang></description></value><value from="4" to="4"><description><lang xml:lang="en"> group Tamper sent as secure</lang></description></value></configParam><configParam number="9" size="1" default="1" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Alarm cancelling or turning a device off (Basic) command frame deactivation</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Allows for deactivating device turn off and alarm cancellation functionsfor the devices assigned to 2nd and 3rd association group).Setting the parameters value to 0 results in stopping BASIC SET = 0and ALARM WATER = 0 control frames from being sent. After sendingflood alarm report the device will keep on reporting flooding afterthe it has ceased. Such a state can be cancelled by choosing alarmcancellation from the MENU, marked with green indicator colour.</lang></description><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en">alarm (flooding) cancellation inactive</lang></description></value><value from="1" to="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">alarm (flooding) cancellation active</lang></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-15080018"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
