<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="0115"/><productType value="0100"/><productId value="0400"/><libType value="Enhanced 232 Slave"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="01"/><appSubVersion value="10"/><basicClass value="03"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15080003</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Weather is amultisensor device monitoring outside weather and environmental conditions. It continually measures the wind speed and can, for example, trigger closing of the awning and blinds if it is too windy. It also measures the amount of rotation, enabling calculation of the wind yield per day or per year. In addition, Z-Weather includes sensors for humidity, temperature, pressure and dew point, essentially providing the core sensors of a weather station.Z-Weather is powered by a solar cell and stores energy on an internal capacitor, enabling continuous operation, even with no wind for a couple of days. It does not use any batteries and is completely maintenance free. Using the built-in solar cell it also measures the ambient light and the solar yield. This information can be used to turn on the outdoor light at dusk time and turn the light off in the morning.Z-Weathers wind yield and solar yield metering can be used as a calculation base for planning a wind generator or a solar panel on the roof of a house.</lang></description><productName>Z-Weather</productName><brandName>Z-Wave.Me</brandName><productCode>ZWeather</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Lifeline. All readings are sent on a regular schedule. The schedule time is set automatically between 5 minutes and 5 hours depending on the available energy. Lifeline is also served after the button was pushed or in case of an unscheduled wakeup (wind speed, twilight). Serves one group member.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="2" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Too windyIf the threshold value for wind (Default value: 6m/s ) is exceeded, the basic set is sent to all group members. If the threshold value is exceeded for a long time, e.g. in case of storm for a couple of hours, the basic set value is sent repeatedly upon the scheduled wake up. Because in most cases the sun does not shine in case of storm, the repeated sending schedule may be between every one hour up to every five hours.</lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="3" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">It is getting bright.Sends BASIC SET command in the morning when brightness reached trigger level (Default value: 37%) </lang></description></assocGroup><assocGroup number="4" maxNodes="5"><description><lang xml:lang="en">It is getting dark.Sends BASIC SET command in the evening when brightness reached trigger level (Default value: 37%)</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><configParams><configParam number="1" size="1" default="6" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold for too much wind</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Crossing this parameter on the rising edge, Z-Weather sends a basic set to the associated groups, serves the lifeline and sends a wake up notification.</lang></description><value from="0" to="30"><description><lang xml:lang="en">m/s</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam><configParam number="2" size="1" default="37" type="rangemapped"><name><lang xml:lang="en">Threshold for twilight</lang></name><description><lang xml:lang="en">Crossing this parameter from night to day, association group 3 is informed. Crossing this parameter from day to night, association group 4 is informed.</lang></description><value from="0" to="100"><description><lang xml:lang="en">%</lang></description></value><value from="0" to="0"><description><lang xml:lang="en"/></description></value></configParam></configParams><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-15080003"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
