<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ZWaveDevice xmlns="http://www.pepper1.net/zwavedb/xml-schemata/z-wave" schemaVersion="2"><descriptorVersion>1</descriptorVersion><deviceData><manufacturerId value="5254"/><productType value="0001"/><productId value="8510"/><libType value="Portable Controller"/><protoVersion value="06"/><protoSubVersion value="51"/><appVersion value="00"/><appSubVersion value="00"/><basicClass value="01"/><genericClass value="00"/><specificClass value="00"/><beamSensor>0</beamSensor><certNumber>ZC10-15120001</certNumber><rfFrequency>EU</rfFrequency></deviceData><deviceDescription><description><lang xml:lang="en">The ZRC-90 Scene Master is a Z-Wave Central Scene Controller. When one of the buttons on the ZRC-90 is pushed, your Z-Wave central controller will receive a signal which it can use to trigger unlimited control possibilities.With 8 buttons, each supporting a long-press capability, you can control 16 different actions in your central controller.The ZRC-90 is a great solution for triggering events more quickly than taking out your smart-phone and running a home control app.The Scene Master is ideal for kids, elderlies and guests who may not have full access to your smart homes mobile application and hence may not have the rights to switch on various lighting, heating, air conditioning and other home appliance.With a convenient snap-in wall mount, the ZRC-90 can also be removed to keep it handy while you go about your home for the ultimate in simple convenience.</lang></description><productName>ZRC-90EU</productName><brandName>Remotec</brandName><productCode>BW8510EU</productCode></deviceDescription><commandClasses><commandClass id="005e" supported="true" controlled="false"/></commandClasses><assocGroups><assocGroup number="1" maxNodes="1"><description><lang xml:lang="en">Z-Wave Plus Lifeline:Association Group-1 will be a default status report channel in ZWave+ lifeline requirement. Only one node can be assigned tothis association group.</lang></description></assocGroup></assocGroups><resourceLinks><deviceImage url="https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductImages/Index?productName=ZC10-15120001"/></resourceLinks></ZWaveDevice>
